Good evening. I'm your guest lecturer,
Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
l was expecting applause.
But I suppose stunned silence
is equally appropriate.
I agreed to speak to you
this evening...
...because I was told
you're the best and the brightest...
...of this university's
doctoral candidates.
Hmm. That's like saying
you're the most important electron...
...in a hydrogen atom. Ha, ha.
Because, you see,
there's only one electron...
...in a hydrogen atom.
Best and brightest,
my sweet patootie.
All right. Let's begin. Show of hands.
Who here is familiar with the concept
of topological insulators?
Heh. Don't kid yourselves.
I found another tweet from a student.
"Dr. Cooper has taken
a relatively boring subject...
...and managed to make it
completely insufferable.
Plus, he looks like a giant insect."
[RAJ LAUGHS]
Look. Listen to this one.
"Does Einstein's theory...
...explain why time flies
when you're having fun...
...but when you're listening to
Dr. Cooper, it falls out of the sky dead?"
[LAUGHS]
Ooh, somebody took pictures and
uploaded them to their Flickr account.
Wow. How do you get an entire lecture
hall to flip you off at the same time?
Apparently, if you're Sheldon,
all you need to do is turn your back.
[RAJ LAUGHS]
Hey, Leonard, is your Wi-Fi down?
I can't get on.
Oh, Sheldon changed the password.
It's now "Penny is a freeloader."
No spaces.
Thanks. What are you guys doing?
Sheldon gave a lecture tonight.
We're reading the reviews.
Oh, how did he do?
Picture the Hindenburg meets Chernobyl
meets Three Mile Island meets Tron 2.
That bad, huh?
Read this woman's tweet.
"Listening to Dr. Cooper has made me
wanna start cutting myself again."
Yeah. Ha-ha-ha.
Well, good evening,
Leonard, Howard, Raj.
Freeloader.
So how did the lecture go?
In a word, triumphant.
-Really? Triumphant?
-Oh, yes.
Should've seen those people.
They're thirsty for knowledge...
...drinking in my wisdom.
I may have changed a few lives today.
Oh, please, let me tell him.
I don't know.
I kind of promised Howard.
-Tell me what?
-Actually, we should share the moment.
Raj, if you would.
Oh, tweets about my lecture.
Hmm.
That's rather unfair.
That's downright cruel.
Plus, insects have six legs.
I'm not familiar
with the acronym KMN.
Oh, from the context,
we think it means "kill me now."
Well, I suppose everyone's entitled
to their own opinion.
I think I'll turn in.
I didn't wanna teach
those poopy heads anyway.
FYI,
I think that's what Darth Vader said...
...just before
he started building the Death Star.
-Sheldon still moping?
-Yeah, it's weird.
Though he didn't wanna give the lecture,
being rejected by students hit him hard.
Hmm, I know the feeling. Like
accidentally walking into a gay bar...
...then having no one hit on you.
It happened to a friend of mine.
-Are you doing okay?
-Yeah, Leonard and l are fine...
...but I think Raj
needs to meet a girl really soon.
That shouldn't be too hard.
He's a cutie.
Oh, thank you.
But cute is for bunnies.
I want to be something with sex appeal,
like a Labradoodle.
Labradoodle?
We might be starting to zero in
on your problem.
Don't you listen to them.
You've got plenty of sex appeal.
-You really think so?
-Yeah, you're a hottie.
Thanks, Bernadette.
For the record,
Labradoodles are hypoallergenic...
...which is a very sexy quality
to those troubled by animal dander.
AMY [OVER COMPUTER]:
So, what do you think?
It's a charming illusion,
but it does not cheer me up.
Not even when I do this?
[MIMICS AIR BUBBLES POPPING
UNDERWATER]
Well, that was the last arrow
in my quiver of whimsy.
Do you realize teaching
is the first thing I've failed at...
...since my ill-fated attempt
to complete a chin-up in March of 1989?
If this experience is troubling you
there are things we could do about it.
-For instance?
-The first thing that comes to mind...
...is isolating the part of your brain
where memory is stored...
...and destroying it with a laser.
Hmm.
No. One slip of the hand and I'm sitting
in the Engineering Department...
...building doodads with Wolowitz.
All right. Have you considered
improving your socialization skills...
...thus allowing you
to communicate more effectively?
Isn't that their burden?
I'm the one
with something interesting to say.
Fair enough. But in its essence,
teaching is a performance art.
In the classroom paradigm, the teacher
has the responsibility to communicate...
...as well as entertain and engage.
I sense you're trying to slow walk me
to an epiphany.
Would you mind very much
jumping to it?
Perhaps you should consider
taking acting lessons.
Acting lessons.
Interesting.
It might help if I could act
as though I care about my students...
...and whether or not they learn.
Penny.
-What?
-You're an "actress," correct?
I'm not an "actress." I'm an actress.
All right. You're an actress.
-I need you to teach me.
-You want an acting lesson?
Perhaps two.
I'd like to master the craft.
Okay, where is this coming from?
It has been suggested to me that acting
techniques could improve my lecturing.
At which, if certain tweets and blogs
are to be believed, I "suck the big one."
[LAUGHS]
I saw those. They were funny. I printed
a few out and put them on my fridge.
So when can we start?
Okay, just to be clear.
You are asking me for help
because I know something...
...that the brilliant Dr. Sheldon Cooper
doesn't.
I suppose that's one way to look at it.
I think it's the only way to look at it.
-Are you going to help me or not?
-Probably. Just enjoying the foreplay.
Does this mean
you are done mocking my career?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought making the transition
from actor to acting teacher...
...was the signal that one's career
had reached the end of the road.
-Forget it.
-l'll pay you $40.
Saturday, 9 am. Bring cash.
-Raj, l have amazing news.
-What?
Ha, ha. I just got offered a fellowship
at the Weizmann Institute in Israel.
-Dude, that's incredible.
HOWARD: I know.
The only thing is,
I'm gonna be gone for two years.
Oh, I'm gonna miss you.
-Are you going with him?
-I have to stay for school.
That's what we're here to talk to you
about. You see, Bernadette has needs.
What kind of needs?
Sexual needs.
Most of them regular,
some of them kind of messed up.
So while I'm gone,
you're gonna have to satisfy her.
What do you say?
I say okey-dokey.
What you thinking so hard about?
Just that I'm definitely not gay.
SHELDON:
Penny.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing. I was acting.
[SIGHS]
You were acting?
Yes. In preparation for today's studies,
I read Stanislavski's An Actor Prepares...
...Stella Adler's
The Technique ofActing...
...Uta Hagen's Respect for Acting,
and Henry Winkler's Eh, I'm an Actor.
Well, good for you. Come on in.
-How should we begin?
-Well, I thought we'd start...
...with some
basic movement exercises.
You know, get our bodies warmed up.
-All right.
-I just want you to relax...
...and kind of move around
in the space, you know.
Just do whatever feels natural.
-Sheldon.
-You said to do whatever feels natural.
This feels natural.
Certainly more natural
than what you're doing.
Gotta work with me. We need
to get connected with our bodies.
Penny, my body and l
have a relationship that works best...
...when we maintain a cool,
wary distance from each other.
[SIGHS]
All right,
let's just say we've warmed up.
You're the "teacher."
[SIGHS]
Okay. One of the things
that might help you...
...in connecting with students
is being a little more spontaneous.
Why don't we try
some improvisation?
Why not? It seems like you're
improvising your entire curriculum.
-This is about listening and responding.
-Gotcha.
I'm gonna create a character
and situation and justjump in.
-All right.
Action.
Okay. It's not a movie, it's improv.
So no one calls, "Action."
Hey, you taught me something.
Who would've thought it?
Ahem. Okay.
No, the shipment hasn't arrived
and I need those shoes.
They are my biggest seller.
Yes, ladies, sizes 6 through 10.
Thank you. Oh, sorry, I have to go.
I have a customer. Bye-bye.
Hi, can I help you?
I'd like a frozen yogurt, please.
Yogurt?
Um, okay. Sure. You-- Luckily,
we sell both shoes and yogurt here.
You do?
Yes. Look up at the sign and remember,
improv is always about saying yes.
All right.
[GASPS]
Yes.
It says,
"Camarillo State Mental Hospital."
What?
The only explanation
I can come up with...
...for why you think
you sell shoes and yogurt.
Okay, you know what?
Let's try a different improv.
Oh. This time, we will be two winos
living under a freeway overpass.
Oh, and we're going to use props?
You bet.
I had dreams, you know.
I was gonna be famous.
Show everybody back home
I could be someone. Now, look at me.
-Want some?
-Do you have any frozen yogurt?
I'm still not adjusted to how
the Syfy channel spells their name now.
S-Y-F-Y. That's "siffy."
Uh-huh.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Oh, my God, is he okay?
-What happened?
-Hang on, hang on.
Uh-huh.
Okay, thank you.
Howard was on his scooter
and got hit by a truck.
He's in critical condition.
Oh, no.
Did you hear? Isn't it terrible?
-Have you seen him?
-They wouldn't let me in.
Oh, my Howie.
It'll be okay.
[PHONE RINGS]
It's Howard. Ahem.
Howard, hello.
Raj, is that you?
Yeah, I'm here. How are you?
Shh. Shh. Listen to me.
I'm not gonna make it.
No, don't say that,
you're going to be all right.
Raj, I don't have time.
Now, pay attention.
My last wish
is that you look after Bernadette.
Of course. Of course.
Now when you say "look after,"
you mean....
Sexually.
Excuse me, Bernadette,
l have to hear it from him.
Sexually.
Got it. Take care.
I guess I have no choice but to make
sweet, guilt-free love to you...
-...for the rest of my life.
-That's howl heard it.
Or it could be "syfee."
-What?
-S-Y-F-Y. "Syfee."
Oh, right.
Good one.
-Did you go over the scene I gave you?
-Yes. I didn't care for it.
Okay, Cat on a Hot Tin Roof
is an American classic.
So is the McRib sandwich.
I don't care for that, either.
Ahem. Fine. What would you rather do
as a scene study?
I'm glad you asked.
I took the liberty of adapting
a Star Trek fan fiction novella...
...I wrote when l was 10
into a one-act play.
You think it's better
than Tennessee Williams?
Why don't we leave that
for future generations to decide?
"Where No Sheldon has Gone Before. "
It's the story of a young boy
who is transported...
...from the ignorant backwoods
of East Texas to the 23rd century...
...where his genius
is not only appreciated, but celebrated.
KMN.
Now, in this pivotal scene,
Sheldon's mother, played by you...
...argues with an emissary...
...of the United Federation of Planets,
Mr. Spock, the role I will bring to life.
Okay, that's fine, but let's try
and get you out of your comfort zone.
Why would we wanna do that?
It's called the comfort zone
for a reason.
Okay, the whole point
is to loosen you up a little.
I'm thinking, you'll play the role of your
mother and I will bring life to Mr. Spock.
I'm sorry. You'll be Spock?
[AS SPOCK]
It's only logical.
Very well. Ahem.
-l'll set the scene.
-All right.
East Texas. A warm summer night.
A woman, Mary, stands on a porch.
In the distance,
we hear a lonesome train whistle:
[MIMICS TRAIN WHISTLE]
The droning buzz of cicadas:
[BUZZING]
A coyote howls at the moon...
...frightening sensitive young boys
everywhere:
[HOWLS]
-Out in the woods, an owl screeches--
-Okay, we get it. You set the scene.
[HOOTS]
Okay, just read your mother's line.
[AS MOTHER] Shelly. Shelly.
How many times have I told you...
...not to leave your science-y stuff
out on the porch?
Goodness.
I'll never understand that boy.
But then again, I'm a religious nut...
...and my mind is closed
to so many things.
[MIMICS TRANSPORTER]
[AS SPOCK] Spock to Enterprise.
Transport successful.
Glory be to heaven.
Some sort of creature
just manifested out of thin air.
George, put down that Pepsi can
full of bourbon...
...that ain't fooling no one,
and get your shotgun.
Greetings, Mary Cooper.
I am Spock.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
I'm sorry, I just don't buy it.
Just keep going.
[AS MOTHER] Oh, my,
your sudden appearance startles me.
[AS SPOCK] We have been
monitoring your son, Sheldon...
...from the 23rd century...
...and we've determined
he's now ready to join us.
His unique genius is our best hope
for bringing peace...
...to a vast and troubled galaxy.
I understand.
Oh, Shelly, a man's here
to take you away to the future.
Be sure to pack clean underwear.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Okay, try that last line again...
...and this time
try choking up a little.
-[IN NORMAL VOICE] Why?
-Well, you're losing your son.
Yes, but he's going to a better place
where he won't get beat up so much.
All right, just try it my way.
Pretend you're sad to see him go.
I'm gonna lead you in. Ahem.
[AS SPOCK] His unique genius
is our best hope for bringing peace...
...to a vast and troubled galaxy.
-[IN NORMAL VOICE] That's your cue.
-l'm sorry, I just love that line.
Even the way you do it.
All right, come on. Put emotion to it.
Blah, blah, blah.
Vast and troubled galaxy, go.
[AS MOTHER] Oh, Shelly, a man's
here to take you away to the future.
[WHIMPERING]
Be sure to pack clean underwear.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
[AS CHILD]
Mommy, why are you crying?
[AS MOTHER] Because
I'm gonna miss you, Shellybean...
...even though you creep the ba-jesus
out of me.
Okay, I guess we're improvising now.
[AS CHILD] Well, I'm sorry, it's not my
fault. I'm just incredibly smart...
...and everyone around here's dumber
than a bag of rocks.
[AS MOTHER] Oh, now, don't you
start crying. You get in that spaceship.
Mommy's late for Indian bingo.
[SOBBING]
Mrs. Cooper, hey, it's Penny.
Yeah, I think I broke your son.
Hold on. Talk to your mother.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Mommy, I love you.
Don't let Spock take me to the future.
Raj, I know you've been avoiding me
and Howard...
...and I'm not leaving until you tell me
what's going on inside that head.
[BOLLYWOOD MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
[SINGING] Like the wild elephant
lam trumpeting my love for you
[SINGING] Like a hidden flower
My sweet fragrance comes into View
My heart burns for you
Like the sun at noon
My desert welcomes you
Like the rainy monsoon
You are my heart
My universe
RAJ 8: BERNADETTE:
ALL [SINGING]:
You are my heart
My universe
Dance number aside, I'm so not gay.
[English - US - SDH]