Can you believe it's been five years
since our first date?
I know.
Do you think I should start
watching The Flash TV show?
That's what you're thinking about?
Well, one of the things.
Are any of them rne?
Yes.
I thought, "I can't decide
if I should watch The Flash TV show.
I know. I'll ask Amy."
Anyway....
What are you doing?
You're right. You did kind of kill the mood.
I didn't kill anything.
You did, talking about your TV stupid show.
Excuse me.
Starting to watch a television show that might
run for years isn't a decision to take lightly.
I'm wrestling with a big
commitment issue here.
Really?
That's the commitment issue
you're wrestling with?
Sheldon, do you understand the irony...
...of your fixation
on a man with super speed...
...while after five years
all I can get out of you...
...is a distracted make-out session
on a couch?
lrony's not really my strong suit.
But I have been getting better with sarcasm
if you want to give that a try.
Oh, sure, I'd love to.
Whenever you're ready.
I don't want to rush you,
but I'm closing early tonight.
Ooh. Hot date?
No, I overheard Bernadette tell Howard
she's making him a meatloaf...
...and you don't have to not ask me twice.
If I stick a lightbulb on this...
...wouldn't it make a great lamp
for my bedroom?
You're kidding, right?
Oh, is this freaking you out?
Well, I guess I'm just more of a...
...Pottery Barn, Crate & Barrel kind of guy.
Maybe Pier 1 ifl really want to cut loose.
All right, never mind.
No, hey, you should totally get it.
-In fact, I'll buy it for you.
-Sold.
-Raj, you don't have to do that.
-Too late, no returns.
That was really intense.
Now we know. Next time we go
to the farmer's market...
...the order is petting zoo first,
then buy vegetables.
-Hey.
-Oh, good, you're here. I need your assistance.
Can it wait until I put a Band-Aid
on a goat bite?
What happened?
Your buddy got mugged
by some baby farm animals.
Been there.
-So, what do you need help with?
-Amy's mad at me, and I'm not clear why.
Okay. Were you talking
before she got upset?
-Yes.
-That's probably it.
What'd you say to her?
ljust asked her ifl should start
watching the new Flash TV series.
-And that made her angry?
-Baffling, right?
We were necking like a couple of hooligans
under the school bleachers.
I stopped so I could ask the question.
Next thing I know, goodbye,
kissy face, hello, yell-y face.
Sheldon, when you're kissing a girl,
she expects the attention to be on her.
It was. I asked her if she thought
I should watch The Flash.
Yeah, I'm tapping out. Leonard?
I guess your main concern
is the time commitment...
...of watching an entire season
of a show.
Oh, no, notjust a season.
If I'm in, I'm in for the whole run,
even if the quality declines.
I get it. Smallville almost wrecked you.
Yeah.
Exactly. You know, I waited 1!) years...
...to see a guy everyone knows can fly, fly.
What's wrong with you two? He was talking
about television during their date.
Oh, notjust date night.
Our fifth anniversary.
That's even dumber than you wondering
if being bitten by a goat...
...would give you the powers of a goat.
If that happens, don't make me wait 10 years
to watch you eat a tin can.
Have you guys noticed Emily
has a bit of a twisted side?
Because she has weird tattoos?
No, because she wants to have sex
with me in a graveyard.
One more time?
She and l were supposed to watch
the new Avengers movie tonight.
It was sold out. I said, "What else
do you want to do?" She said:
"Let's go to a cemetery
and do it on somebody's grave."
Like, a random person
or somebody she knew?
What difference does it make?
Well, if it's her father's grave
and they didn't get along...
...then you know she holds a grudge.
The only issue is that
everybody has their own thing.
As long as it's two consenting adults,
I don't see the harm.
What if it's one consenting adult
and one who pretends to consent...
...because he's afraid of being alone?
Well, then I guess bring a blanket.
The grass gets damp at night.
I don't know, guys.
Maybe this relationship isn't for me.
Maybe I should break up with her.
Heh. Right. You're gonna break up with a girl
who has sex with you. You believe this guy?
I think if Raj wants to break up
with a girl, he can do it.
-How are you saying that with a straight face?
-I don't know.
[BOTH LAUGH]
You guys are being jerks.
Buddy, other than Jenny Craig...
...you've never broken up
with a girl in your life.
You're one to talk.
Complaining about Stuart living here
the past year.
-Don't see you showing him the door.
-Not the same. Emily's a person.
Stuart's more like an infestation.
Something you spray for.
Baloney, okay? You two are as afraid
of hurting someone's feelings as I am.
That's not true.
We were just laughing right in your face.
-Thanks for cooking.
-My pleasure.
-That carrot was delicious.
-Yeah.
lwish I'd fought harder for the rest of them.
Still haven't heard from her?
No, and I'm confused.
It's been nearly 24 hours.
Amy should have figured out
she's wrong by now.
I don't think she's wrong
about you going too slow in the relationship.
Too slow?
Yeah, you haven't even slept together.
That's right. It's called foreplay.
And I could make the case that you two
aren't moving forward in your relationship.
Uh, hello?
Hello.
No, Sheldon, we're getting married.
You've been engaged for over a year.
You don't even have a wedding date.
Well, we will. We're just not in a rush.
Okay.
We're gonna set a date.
Okay, if you say so.
-Things are good right now.
-Really good.
-Focusing on myjob.
-Been busy with our paper.
-Yeah, we'll pick a date when we pick a date.
-Yeah.
Okay.
-You know, I can see why Amy's mad at you.
-Yeah, shut up, Sheldon.
Did you eat all my yogurt?
The one that makes ladies do the thing
they pretend they don't even though they do?
You know which yogurt I mean.
I didn't touch it. Must've been Stuart.
Maybe Raj is right. Maybe it's time
we tell him he needs to move.
We should've done it months ago.
I know, but his store was reopening...
...and then there were the holidays,
and then he was sick.
Yeah, right. Sick.
Look, he didn't have jaundice.
He just looks like that.
All right, tonight's the night.
Agreed. When he gets home,
I'm dropping the hammer.
I like when you take charge.
I'm not taking charge.
You're the hammer.
So why haven't we picked a date?
-You know why.
-Of course I know why. But just for fun, why?
Not in a rush, busy with work--
-Things are good right now.
-Really good.
-You still want to get married, right?
-Oh, my God, yes. Why would you even ask?
Don't know.
Because we don't have a date?
-You want a date, pick a date.
-lt's notjust the date.
We haven't talked
about anything.
Big wedding, small wedding,
indoor, outdoor.
Outdoor? Ugh.
I can RSVP no right now.
Okay, indoor it is. Big or small?
-Is your dad paying?
-I doubt it.
Okay, two friends each.
-All right, I want it in a church.
-Fine. I want black tie.
-Fine. I want to release butterflies.
-Seriously? Airborne worms?
Okay, well, then it's settled. Small indoor
church wedding, black tie, no butterflies.
-Sounds perfect.
-6 reat.
Still didn't pick a date.
-Stay out of it.
-Shut up.
EMILY: It's a beautiful night.
-Oh, yes.
We've got the moon
and the trees and...
...Elizabeth McNulty, who...
...apparently died
when she was the same age I am.
Makes you feel alive, doesn't it?
So does enjoying a meal
at a well-lit restaurant, but here we are.
You aren't scared, are you?
Of ghosts, no.
Of you, a little bit.
I'm sorry I've upset you.
-I shouldn't have asked so many questions.
-No, it's okay.
Yeah, maybe it's good
you got us talking about this stuff.
Well, look at that.
Even when I'm causing problems,
I make the world a better place.
Hey. Next, why don't we tackle
your penchant for whining...
...and Penny's love of the ol' glug-glug?
Sheldon, I think we're good for now.
Very well. So does this mean
you'll finally pick a wedding date?
Ugh. Here we go again.
Why is everyone so concerned
with us setting a date?
We're committed to each other. We're happy.
A ceremony isn't gonna change anything.
So you're never getting married?
It's his whining, isn't it?
Sheldon, I'm not a whiner.
It's amusing that he doesn't hear it.
Look, all she's saying is, we are in love.
It doesn't matter
if we get married tomorrow...
...or a year from now or 50 years from now.
Ew. Fifty? We'll be old and gross.
Yeah, but we'll be old and gross together.
My aunt and uncle were married 63 years.
Towards the end
it was like watching cheese melt.
Um, I'm free tonight.
Are you saying you wanna get married?
Vegas isn't that far away.
-l'm in. Let's do it.
-Eee-ah.
After all these years.
-l'm really happy for the two of you.
-Thank you.
Now get out of my spot.
Bernie, Stuartjust pulled up.
So remember, the key is to be firm.
-Show no weakness.
-Right.
Good luck.
Howard Joel Wolowitz, you get back here.
I never should have told you
my middle name.
STUART: Hey, guys.
-Hey.
You got a minute?
Sure. Let me just
put this stuff in the fridge.
I felt bad finishing your yogurt.
I bought more.
Howard, your favorite fruit
is in season.
Crunch Berries.
-Don't let that sway you.
-lt's hard not to.
They taste so much better
than real berries.
What's up?
So we need to talk.
You okay?
I think we should talk.
Is everything okay?
-Well, you've been living here awhile now.
-I know.
I may sell comic books at work,
but the real superheroes...
...are sitting right in front of me.
Yeah.
His middle name is David. Go.
Look, I care about you a lot...
...but we are very different people.
Are you breaking up with me?
No, no, I'm just pointing out
that you're dark on the inside...
...and I'm dark on the outside.
So anyway, what I'm trying to say is--
[PHONE RINGING]
-You need to take that?
-lt's my dad.
Probably calling to wish me
a happy birthday.
I'll call him back.
You were saying?
Look, Raj, be honest with me.
If you want to end things, do it.
Don't expect me to do it for you.
End things? I'm trying
to tell you that I love you.
HOWARD & BERNADETTE [SINGING]:
Happy birthday to you
Wow, there's a Denny's in Vegas
you can actually get married in.
Doesn't sound very romantic.
-But we could get heart-shaped pancakes.
-Heh, heh.
-l'm sure we'll find a decent chapel.
-Yeah. Ahem.
-This is crazy.
-I know.
You think people are gonna be mad?
Maybe. But this isn't
about them, it's about us.
It is.
It is about us.
And you know what the best part is?
We took our time.
We met.
We were friends for a couple years.
Then we got together.
Then we got untogether.
Then we worked out all our problems,
now we know everything about each other.
We can just go forward
with no surprises and no regrets.
Right. No surprises.
And no regrets.
Well, there is...
...one thing...
-...| feel I should tell you.
-What?
You know, so we can go into this
with no secrets between us.
What?
Remember a couple years back...
...when l was on that research ship
in the North Sea?
-Yeah?
-Okay, well, there was a lot of...
...drinking and craziness going on.
-You told me.
-Okay. Um....
Well, there was this girl.
-What did you do?
-Nothing.
Really, it was just kissing.
-And then what?
-And then nothing.
I stopped it.
But...
...it still bothers me, and...
...I wanted you to know.
[SIGHS]
All right.
-Did you ever do anything like this--?
-Nope. Never.
LEONARD:
That's too bad.
-Can I ask you a question?
-Hm.
Why are you telling me this now?
Like I said,
we're about to get married...
...and I want a clean slate. No secrets.
Really? To me, it seems like
we're about to get married...
...and you're trying to sabotage it.
-Would you rather I didn't tell you?
-No, I don't want secrets between us.
Now I'm confused.
What am I supposed to do?
Keep your mouth off other women.
I can do that.
From now on, this mouth...
...you and food. That's it.
[PENNY SIGHS]
Okay.
Yeah?
Look, I'm not happy this happened...
...but I think I can get past it.
We weren't engaged at the time, and it...
-...was just kissing.
-Right.
Just kissing.
It wasn't even very good.
She was a smoker.
-l'd just been seasick--
-Okay, that's enough. Stop talking.
So...
...we're still getting married?
Yes.
Because we love each other.
And it's the happiest day of our lives.
Don't push it.
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
-Hello.
Listen, I've been thinking
a lot about relationships...
...and how difficult they can be.
-And lthink--
-I'Ve been thinking about them too, Sheldon.
Being your girlfriend is so challenging.
Emotionally.
Physically.
I've been incredibly patient for years.
Strongly disagree. Go on.
Okay, well...
...this isn't easy to say, because...
...I love you, but...
...I need some time...
...to take a step back
and reevaluate our situation.
Oh.
[hope you understand.
Okay.
Bye, Sheldon.
Well, Gollum...
...you're an expert on rings.
What do I do with this one?
[English - us - an]