-Would you pass the mustard?
-Sure.
Hey. Wanna hear a fun fact about mustard?
Is it that the glucosinolates
which give mustard its flavor
were evolved by the cabbage family as
a chemical defense against caterpillars?
Yeah.
Well, that was fun. Good for you, Leonard.
-Hey there.
-Hey, you're early.
The movie doesn't start for an hour.
Actually, we're not going to the movies.
-We are here to kidnap you.
-(CHUCKLES)
What are you talking about?
Well, you eloped and we didn't get
a chance to throw you a bachelor party,
so there's a van downstairs
and we're here to take you
to a surprise location for the weekend.
Well, I'd hardly call this kidnapping.
Where's the blindfold?
Where's the duct tape?
Where's the part where you call me
and demand ransom
and I try to keep you on the phone but
you hang up seconds before I can trace it
and then I say,
"I'm getting too old for this crud"?
When do we leave?
-Right now.
-Yeah, Penny packed you a bag.
(CHUCKLING) Wow, okay.
You're seriously going to get in a van
and let these two take you
to an unknown destination
for an entire weekend?
Oh, notjust him, you're coming, too.
Oh, and how do you think
you're going to get me to do that?
Unhand me! This is ridiculous!
-I told you to put tape on his mouth.
-(SHELDON GRUNTS)
And I told you he bit me.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
It's bad enough
I'm being taken against my will.
I don't see why it has to be
in some hippie's mobile sex dungeon.
Well, Sheldon,
there's something about this van
that you're going to find
very interesting.
What? It runs on syphilis?
This van was owned and driven by
your personal physics hero,
Richard Feynman.
-No.
-HOWARD: Yeah.
-A buddy of mine let me borrow it.
-This was Feynman's van? That's so cool.
Yeah, nothing's been changed
since he drove it.
I bet he picked up a lot of
cute grad students in this bad boy.
Yeah, and talked about physics with them.
(GASPS)
So, are you gonna give us a clue
where we're headed?
Uh, okay. Let's see.
They've got spicy food
and there's a chance you'll get diarrhea.
lndia.
We can drive there.
Your house?
We are going to México!
Fun, I've never been there.
Leonard, don't be fooled. I'm from Texas.
"Me-he-co" is Spanish for Mexico.
What's wrong with Mexico?
Uh, mariachi bands, wild dogs, beans that
jump around 'cause there's a worm inside.
Okay, calm down.
There's a theme to this weekend.
We are going to Mexico in Feynman's van
to stay at the vacation house
Feynman bought
with the money from his Nobel Prize.
,‘Viva la lmodium! (EXCLAIMS)
Come on. Leonard's doing bachelor stuff.
You sure we can't take you
to a strip club?
No, if I wanna see a naked dancing man
| just flush the toilet
while Leonard's in the shower. (CHUCKLES)
-Hi.
-Hey.
I know we're not making a fuss, but,
in the spirit of bachelorette parties,
I made cookies
in the shape of male genitals.
You really didn't have to--
Whoa!
That is anatomic.
Thank you. The veins are gummy worms.
Oh, look, Jewish and gentile.
I had extra dough.
(PHONE CHIMES)
Oh, that's Leonard.
He said they're about to cross the border.
I hope the boys don't get too crazy
in Mexico.
Oh, yeah, right, lock up your daughters
or Sheldon might lecture them about
the North American Free Trade Agreement.
Boy, that was a long night for me.
Uh-oh.
According to this Mexican Customs website,
visitors may not bring more than
five laser discs, 20 compact discs
or 12 VHS tapes.
We don't have any of those.
How can you be sure?
Uh, VHS was king when
Feynman drove this van.
And for all we know,
there are hidden compartments
lousy with Jane Fonda workout videos.
If there was a hidden compartment,
don't you think
you'd be stuffed in it by now?
Are we all up-to-date
on our Yellow Fever inoculations?
You don't need a Yellow Fever shot
to go to Mexico.
You can never be too careful.
I got one last year
before I went to Epcot.
So, Penny, how's married life?
Oh, it's good.
Just wish Leonard
would work up the courage
to tell Sheldon he's moving in here.
You guys still aren't living together?
We are, I mean, he sleeps here,
but it's only a matter of time
before Sheldon has a bad dream
and tries to climb into bed
with the Leonard-shaped pile of pillows.
Speaking of Sheldon,
how's single life treating you?
Fine, I guess. I've been focusing on me.
l was thinking about
changing my wardrobe.
-Yes!
-Good for you!
But then I decided
I don't wanna go changing who I am
just because of some man.
-Yes.
-Good for you.
You know, it is normal to wanna change
your look after a breakup.
Actually, I was thinking
of making one small change.
-Your sweater?
-Your glasses?
-Your hair?
-Your shoes?
Piercing my ears.
Oh...
You really never had that done?
My mom said pierced ears were for whores,
pirates and genies.
Okay. Well, you're a grown woman now.
I know, but Sheldon had this clause
in the relationship agreement
forbidding cosmetic surgery
unless it's to look like a Klingon.
We'll take you to the mall to get it done.
Why? I can do it right here.
-Really? You have a piercing gun?
-PENNY: No.
All you need is a needle and an ice cube.
I've done it like a dozen times.
-Oh, I don't know.
-Oh, come on. I'll be gentle.
Let me take your ear virginity.
This party's weird.
Hey, watch your speed.
I hear Mexican police target tourists.
Oh, not a problem. If anything goes down,
we just put Koothrappali
in the driver's seat
and slap a sombrero on his head.
Dude, how many races
can you offend in a single breath?
I don't know.
Have you watched the Olympics with me?
Sheldon, can you believe that
we're driving in a van that was owned
by one of the greatest scientific minds
of the twentieth century?
It's like the Batmobile. (CHUCKLES)
lf Batman was real.
And a physicist. And his car wasn't cool.
It is extraordinary.
Perhaps some of his mojo
will rub off on us.
Maybe between this and his beach house,
we'll be inspired to greatness.
I usually don't put too much stock
in charms and talismans,
however even I must admit feeling Richard
Feynman's butt dent cupping my own bottom.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
That does get the creative juices flowing.
Hey, I have to return this van.
Keep your creative juices in your pants.
(TIRE RATTLING)
-What was that?
-I think it's a tire.
What if it's bandidos shooting at us?
What if we get kidnapped?
What if we end up in a factory
making Bart Simpson piﬁatas
for the rest of our lives?
It's the tire.
-Leonard?
-What?
I'm getting too old for this crud.
Amy, I noticed your status still says
"in a relationship" on Facebook.
You're right. I should probably let
all of my Facebook friends know.
Penny, I'm no longer in a relationship.
Did you change yours to "married" yet?
Uh, no, not yet. There's still
a few people I haven't told personally.
-Who?
-Oh, just my parents and my entire family.
(CLEARS THROAT)
-What?
-Why?
Well, I don't wanna hurt my dad.
You know, he always wanted to dance
with his daughter at her wedding.
What about your sister's wedding?
They started to but then her water broke.
(SCOFFS)
You know, if he finds out we eloped,
that's gonna break his heart.
How long do you think
you can keep it from him?
Yeah, isn't it gonna get worse
the longer you wait?
Well, not necessarily.
You know, Dad's not getting any younger.
So if I wait long enough,
I'll just tell him he walked me
down the aisle and it was magical.
When did you learn how to change a tire?
Every self-respecting gentleman
should know how,
in case he comes across a damsel
in distress by the side of the road.
If I see one scorpion, I'm getting on
someone's shoulders and never coming down.
And there's your damsel.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Wow, this one's really stuck.
Are you turning it the right way?
No, I took the other four off
and when I got to this one, I thought,
"I'm in a rut, let's shake things up."
Here, let me try.
(GRUNTING)
You're right.
It doesn't turn the other way.
There you go, you're all done.
That wasn't so bad.
(GASPS) Nice.
Boy, if my mom could see me now,
she'd lock me in the sin closet.
That's a joke, right?
Actually, the joke was on her, I could
still see the TV through the slats.
I'm starting to see why you and your mom
aren't very close.
Bet she'd still tell her
if she got married.
You're not gonna let this go, are you?
Well, it's kind of sad
that they don't know.
I mean, they love Leonard.
Fine, you want me to call, I'll call.
-(S|GHS) Why am I so nervous?
-lt's understandable.
Amy was afraid to tell her mom
she broke up with Sheldon.
Yeah. How did it go? Did she make you
crawl into the breaking-up drawer?
Uh, well, actually, to be honest,
I haven't told her yet.
You've been giving me a hard time
and you haven't even told
your mom about Sheldon?
I'm feeling a little dizzy
from all the blood loss.
I don't know what you're talking about.
(SIGHS)
Fine. I'm calling home, but when I'm done,
you're calling your mother.
Easy for you to say. You never had
to watch 60 Minutes like this.
-Hey, Daddy.
-Hey, slugger.
-How's my girl?
-Uh, good. ls Mom around?
Ah, she took your brother
out to celebrate.
He just got his tenth
one-month sober chip.
Yeah, she's gonna make him
a little necklace.
Okay. I'll talk to her later.
Uh, Dad, there's something
I need to tell you.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Leonard and I got married.
You did? When?
Last week.
I'm sorry, I should've told you.
It was a spur-of-the-moment thing.
| feel terrible.
Please don't be too disappointed.
Are you happy?
Very. Leonard is so great.
Well, then, I'm happy for you.
Aw, thank you, Daddy. That means so much.
Well, I understand it's hard
to tell someone something
if you think it's gonna upset 'em.
It is. You're the best dad ever.
Yeah, uh, hold that thought.
I've been sitting on a little news myself.
Well, what is it? (CHUCKLES)
Oh, you know that rototiller
I got for the tractor?
-No.
-Oh, you should see it.
It is a beautiful piece of machinery.
Anyway, uh...
I backed over your pet pig with it.
Moondance?
Yeah, he's not dancing anymore.
You killed my pig?
I did not kill him.
The vet took care of that.
-When?
-Oh...
Ten, 12 months ago.
You didn't tell me for a year?
Well, apple doesn't fall
far from the tree, does it?
Uh, love you, slugger. Gotta go.
Okay, Amy, your turn.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
What are you doing?
It's called Lamaze breathing.
It helps you push.
Great. He's pushing with his uterus.
There's gotta be
a smarter way of removing it.
Yeah, this is nothing more
than a physics problem.
Right. Archimedes once said,
"Give me a lever long enough
and a fulcrum on which to place it,
"and I shall move the world."
Of course, all we need is to find stuff
to make a lever big enough to fix this.
Exactly. I'll bet there's something
around here that could be a lever.
Let's see. A lever, a lever.
Everybody hold on. Let's take this problem
one step at a time.
First, we need to decide whether
we're calling it "leever" or "lever."
And the sooner we decide it's "leever,"
the sooner we can roll up our sleeves
and not "slehves" and get to work.
We're gonna be here "for-eever."
Thanks a lot, guys.
-What did we do?
-Before I made that call,
my pig was alive and happy
and rolling around in the mud.
Now he's illegally buried in our backyard
next to my great-grandmother.
Really? They didn't eat him?
No, he was a beloved member of the family.
The breakfast meat family?
It's not funny. You're up.
Call your mother.
Oh, maybe later.
Your pig dying made me sad.
-And a little hungry.
-Phone. Now.
Okay. Okay. Fine.
-Hi, Mom.
-Try dialing.
You saw that, huh?
Hi, Mom. How are you doing?
Oh, good. How's work?
That's nice.
I'm fine. Hey, listen.
I've been meaning to ask
how come Aunt Doe and Aunt Florence
never got along?
Okay. That's it, give me that.
Amy broke up with Sheldon,
she got her ears pierced
and she made us eat penis cookies.
Hang on. She wants to talk to you.
I don't think the lever's working.
What makes you say that?
There's gotta be something else
we can try.
Well, if this was Star Trek,
we could use a phaser to blast it off.
Oh, it's too broad of a beam.
You'd need something more precise,
like Superman's heat vision.
Ooh, the Green Lantern's ring could make
a big green hand that unscrews it.
Well, if you need a green hand,
why not just use the Hulk?
Oh, please. The Hulk would never get
across the border with that temper.
Guys, excuse me,
not that calling one of the Avengers
isn't a perfectly reasonable choice,
but we're scientists.
Don't you think we can figure this out
using actual science?
Yes. We could use science,
but it's your bachelor party. Lighten up.
(CLATTERING)
(TAPPING AND CLAPPING RHYTHMICALLY)
(SINGING)
We will, we will, percussive shock you
BOTH: (SINGING) We will, we will,
percussive shock you
Buddy, you're a boy, make a big noise
Playin' in the street
gonna be a big man some day
You got mud on yo' face, you big disgrace
Kickin' your can all over the place
l have an eidetic memory,
sometimes it's a curse.
(MATCH STRIKES)
I had no idea tortilla chips
were such a good fuel source.
They're basically pure hydrocarbons
soaked in fat.
Let's hope the lug nut expands.
What if that burning food
attracts animals?
We have plenty of food for the animals.
-We do?
-Yep, six-foot wiener in a Flash t-shirt.
That's not very nice.
It's a bachelor party. Lighten up.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Oh, what is that awful smell?
lt's burning salsa. I'm hoping the acidity
and salinity combined with electricity
will corrode the lug nut off.
What an innovative solution.
Perhaps I don't give your MIT education
enough credit.
Yeah, I saw it on Mythbusters.
(CHUCKLES)
(CLATTERING)
All right.
This rust combined with the aluminum
-recovered from the van is now thermite.
-(S|GHS)
Great.
Couple pinches ought to do the trick.
Is that enough to melt the lug nut?
Well, let's start small.
We can always add more.
You put up a good fight, lug nut.
But you've met your match.
(RAJ CHUCKLES)
Hey, look. The lug nut's off.
What? What are you doing back?
We got a flat
and couldn't get the tire off.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-Thank you.
Yeah, if it makes you feel any better,
l pierced Amy's ears
and her mom made her sit in my closet.
We blew up Feynman's van.
My dad killed my pig with his tractor.
I spent the night in Mexico with Sheldon.
You win.
English - SDH