I've invented a science joke...
-...would you like to hear it?
-Sure.
How many Edisons does it take
to screw in a lightbulb?
-How many?
-Who cares?
He stole the idea
and doesn't deserve his own joke.
Is that really true?
Of course.
That's how you know it's a good joke.
It not only entertains, it informs.
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
Barry, uh, how many Edisons does it take
to screw in a lightbulb?
Did you know Edison
didn't actually invent the lightbulb?
What do you want, Barry?
Just wanted to drop this off
as a little thank-you for Amy.
-What's this for?
-Your idea really helped me out.
My light-cone quantization paper's
online already.
The response has been amazing.
That's fascinating, I can't wait to read it.
Oh, no. Me, as well.
Please e-mail it to Sheldon@Bazinga.biz.
Why "dot biz"?
Because I just gave you the business.
And also, Bazinga.com was taken.
Anyway, than ks again.
Cooper, suck eggs.
Since when do you help out Barry Kripke?
I'd been thinking about a cellular approach
to neuronal connectivity...
...and thought it might have applications
to string theory.
-lt's not a big deal.
-Oh, really?
When I was doing string theory
and hit a dead end...
...why didn't you try to help me?
I did. You said the only math
biologists know...
...is if you have three frogs and one
hops away, that leaves two frogs.
That's pretty funny, that does sound like me.
But it doesn't mean you should be
standing on street corners...
...handing out your math
to whatever guy comes along.
Sheldon, we're all scientists.
I helped out a fellow colleague.
-You're being petty.
-l'm being petty?
You know Barry and l have
a professional rivalry.
You heard him, he told me to suck eggs.
If we were friends, he would've suggested
I suck something pleasant.
Why are you laughing?
Did you learn something?
Okay, Ma, say hi to Aunt Gladys.
Yeah, I love you too. Bye.
-Your mom having fun in Florida?
-Oh, she loves it.
She finally found a place where
everyone talks about how sweaty they are.
She wants us to go to the house
and check in on Stuart.
"Because he might be lonely."
She's just being nice.
I'm her son, how come she doesn't
send someone to check on me if I'm lonely?
Because you have a wife?
Yeah, well, sometimes you work late.
I know you don't like Stuart in the house...
...but the store's about to reopen,
he'll get back on his feet.
That'd be great. I'd love for things
between me and Mom to get back to normal.
Well, normal's a strong word, but sure.
-Hey.
-Hello.
-You okay?
-If I was okay...
...I would've said "Hello"
and not the more ominous "Hello."
-What's going on?
-l'm mad at Amy.
Did she leave pit stains
in your favorite crop top too?
She helped Barry Kripke make
an advancement in string theory.
Oh. That sounds like a good thing.
Well, it would be, except I left string theory...
...because I decided it was a dead end...
...and then she went behind my back
to help someone else prove me wrong.
My rival, no less.
[GRUNTS]
I'm sorry you had to see that.
I'm sorry I didn't have a camera.
Why would she do this to me?
Well, I'm sure she didn't
upset you on purpose.
Don't you say there's nothing more
important than the advancement of science?
No. I said there's nothing more important
than me advancing science.
If I'm understanding this
and all she did was help another scientist...
...l'm thinking you might have to
let this one go.
Ugh. "Let it go."
I have heard that my whole life.
Every time something upsets me,
somebody says, "Let it go."
Like it's my fault
and it's not okay to feel the way I feel.
[PENNY SIGHS]
I don't know what to tell you.
Why don't you talk to her?
Is that all you have? Shopworn tidbits
like, "Talk to her" and "Let it go"?
Gee, Penny, life's given me lemons,
what should I do?
Well, you could shove them somewhere.
Okay, now you're getting creative.
Thanks again for your help.
-No problem. Place really looks great.
-Our pleasure.
Yeah, you should have burned it down
years ago.
I keep telling you, I didn't burn it down.
We know. Because burning something
down for the insurance money is a crime.
Stuart, this place looks amazing.
-Thanks.
-You really did a nice job.
And thank you for putting up with me
staying at your mom's through all this.
I couldn't have done it otherwise.
I appreciate that.
And I'm glad you were able to--
Is that my mother's furniture?
Yeah, she said I could use it.
Doesn't it look great?
Not as great as it looks in the den,
where it belongs.
-Howie.
-Why don't you clean out the whole room?
Take the string-art clown
I made her in third grade...
...and the ribbon I got in swim class
for putting my face in the water.
What is your problem? She said it was okay.
Well, I'm her son. And I say it's not okay.
Some son. Looks like you spent
10 minutes on that clown art.
lshould've gone to an art school...
...then I could run afailed comic shop
and mooch off some guy's mother.
-Why don't we leave so you can cool off?
-Yeah, that's a good idea.
-Take him out of my store.
-Your store?
My mother gave you the money to reopen.
I'm not going anywhere.
Why don't we go get the food for the party?
-Thank you.
-Smart. It looks like we're being helpful.
When really we're just exiting
an uncomfortable situation.
Kripke. Of all the people, Barry Kripke--
Are you folding that like a crazy person
to get me to do it for you?
Oh, give me that.
Just out of curiosity...
...if I were to let something go,
how would I do that?
I don't know,
just think about something else.
-Can I think about the spiny anteater?
-Sure.
The spiny anteater...
...never went behind my back
and worked with Barry Kripke.
That didn't help at all.
You know, some people try visualization.
How does that work?
Okay.
Imagine your problems are a pen.
-Okay.
-Now, imagine you're holding that pen.
Okay.
Now, open your hand and let it go.
But I just got this pen.
It's got my initials on it and everything.
Look.
Sheldon, this isn't that hard.
-I may have a better way you can teach me.
-How?
What if I told you
that over the past few months...
...Amy has secretly been
giving you little puzzles...
...to test your intelligence
against chimpanzees in her lab?
-What? She didn't give me any puzzles.
-Are you sure?
Boy, I just can't seem
to get these scissors back together.
Can you do it?
Darn it, there's something in my eye,
and I need to sort these coins by size.
Can you help?
Penny, I really want to eat this banana...
...but it's stuck inside
this bamboo puzzle box.
Son of a bitch!
Okay. That's great. Now, let it go.
I can't believe you were testing me
against a chimp!
Excuse me, Amy was testing you,
I was rooting for you.
Good job on that banana box, by the way.
Why would she even do this?
She's been conducting
an experiment on apes...
...where they're given puzzles to solve.
l was surprised
at the complexity of the puzzles...
...and thought some humans
wouldn't solve them.
And that's when Amy said,
"Wanna make this interesting?"
Make this interesting?
You bet money on me?
No, no, we designed an experiment
involving you.
See, now, isn't that interesting?
It's not interesting, it's incredibly insulting.
Okay, maybe this will help.
Imagine you're holding a pen.
Before you go too far, not a special pen...
...with your initials engraved on it.
-That'll make the next part really hard.
-Oh, my God.
That's it. Get out.
I don't understand why you're mad at me.
You should be mad at Amy,
like I was this afternoon.
-Hey, look at that, I let it go.
-Get out!
SHELDON: Penny.
-What?
I think I left my pen in there.
I understand why you're upset...
...but he worked really hard
to get the store ready.
And it's just furniture.
It's my mom's furniture.
It belongs in the house I grew up in
next to that pile of TV Guides...
...and in plain view of what,
for a 10-year-old...
...was a quality piece of string art!
Howie, if the store succeeds...
...Stuart has a source of income
and can move out of your mother's house.
It seems some furniture
is a reasonable price to pay for that.
That is a good point.
I didn't marry you for good points.
I married you to blindly support me
no matter how ridiculous I'm being!
This is whyl had to
rewrite our wedding vows.
We're here to pick up an order
for Comic Center.
Sure. Let me go check on that.
Dude, I thinkthat's Nathan Fillion.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
And he's picking the tomatoes
out of his salad just like I do.
I always did feel a connection with him.
Oh, I have got an idea.
We're not selling his tomatoes on eBay.
No, if we got Captain Reynolds
from Fireﬂy...
...to do a signing at Stuart's store,
that would be amazing.
-That would be great.
-Should we go talk to him?
I don't know. If he's not nice...
...it's gonna make it hard for me
to watch him in anything again.
The guy who plays Jon Snow was ajerk.
We still watch Game of Thrones.
He was ajerk because you rear-ended him.
l was distracted.
It's odd seeing a member of the Night's
Watch with a kayak strapped to his car.
Come on.
Hi, excuse me. Don't mean to bother you,
but we're just really--
We're big fans of Fireﬂy. And Dr. Horrible.
Oh, I think you made a mistake.
I'm not an actor.
Don't say that.
I mean, you're not Dame Judi Dench,
but you're pretty great.
I get it. You think I'm Nathan Fillion...
...but I'm not, so if you don't mind,
I would just love to eat my lunch.
Come on. Sorry to bother you.
Don't know why he's so grumpy.
I got mistaken for that guy
in Life ofPi once, I'm still floating.
Sheldon, it's me.
Uh, hey, did you see that?
I figured out how to open
the door all by myself.
Maybe I'll fling some feces around my cage
to celebrate.
What are you talking about?
I know you've been giving me
secret puzzle tests.
-Sheldon, open the door.
SHELDON: I can't.
I'm naked.
ljust saw you.
Hang on.
Open the door now.
-Oh, hey.
-Pull up your pants!
It's not a big deal.
I run tests like this
on undergrads all the time.
If you fill out some paperwork
at the university, I can get you $5.
I don't want $5. I want my dignity.
What are we talking, like 10 bucks?
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Sorry again.
-No problem.
Uh, are you sure you're not him?
You can tell us.
We're scientists, not crazy fanboys.
All right, fine. I'm him.
And you're eating alone at a deli?
I don't buy it. You're not him.
I wanted to eat my lunch in peace...
...butl really am him,
and thank you very much for being a fan.
If you want, uh, let's take a picture.
-That would be great. Thank you.
-You bet.
Wait, hang on.
If you're really Nathan Fillion...
...what's the line from Fireﬂy
about your bonnet?
I swear by my pretty floral bonnet,
I will end you.
That's it. That's the line.
Although, I knew the line.
Doesn't make me Nathan Fillion.
-Do you want the picture or not?
-I want a picture with Nathan Fillion.
How about a picture with a guy
who looks like Nathan Fillion...
...but a little more annoyed
than Nathan Fillion usually is?
What do you think?
Eh, it's good enough for Facebook.
I can't believe they did that.
I know, it's so insulting.
At one point, they had me figure out
how to get a banana out of a puzzle box.
Wait. Sheldon gave me a banana in a box.
He was testing me too.
Unbelievable.
And how could a chimp even solve that?
That was impossible.
Really? You couldn't get it out?
-Thank you.
AMY: Wow, the store looks great.
So you guys were testing us both?
What is the matter with you?
The matter is they think they're so smart
they don't care if they hurt others' feelings.
-That's not true.
-Sounds like us.
I still don't understand why you're upset.
You solved every puzzle
faster than all of the chimps.
Well, except Barnabas,
but he was on Adderall.
I'm sorry, but it's making me crazy.
Can you please just let it go?
Oh, I can help you with that.
Imagine you're holding an ordinary pen.
While your favorite pen
is safe and secure in your pocket.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
Hold that thought. Hello?
How can I make this up to you?
The answer's in this puzzle box.
Let's see if you can open it.
You could have warned him
about the furniture.
That's what I said when we moved it.
You helped him?
No, Stuart picked out those
throw pillows all on his own.
Hey, you okay?
-No.
-What's wrong?
My mom died.
What?
[CLEARS THROAT]
That was my aunt.
Ma took a nap.
She never woke up.
Oh, my God, Howie.
I'm so sorry.
What can we do?
I don't know.
-May I say something?
-Not right now, Sheldon.
-But I think it would be comforting.
-No, it's okay.
What?
When I lost my own father...
...I didn't have any friends
to help me through it.
You do.
I really thought he was gonna say,
"Let it go."
Okay. Thanks, Bernadette. Travel safe.
Okay, bye.
Uh, they booked a flight,
they're heading to the airport now.
How's Howard holding up?
-He's hanging in there.
-How are you doing, Stuart?
I still can't believe she's gone.
I mean, that woman took me in.
If it wasn't for her,
lwould have been homeless.
One of us would have taken you in.
Yeah, I don't recall any offers.
But you know what?
I'm glad it worked out the way it did...
...because I got to know
this wonderful person.
Yeah. Mrs. Wolowitz was pretty special.
When I first moved to America...
...Howard was my only friend...
...and she made me feel
so welcome in her home.
Which says a lot,
because those first few years...
...she thought I was the gardener.
Whenever I saw her she'd say
I was too skinny and try and feed me.
She did that to me too.
Don't take this away from me.
I didn't care for her yelling.
But now that I'm not going
to hear it again, I'm sad.
If you want, I can yell at you later.
It won't be as good.
Let's have a toast.
To Mrs. Wolowitz. A loving mother...
...to all of us.
We'll miss you.
[English - us - an]