So how does this work?
I throw it like a real ball?
Yeah, nice and easy, right over the plate.
All right.
You suck, Wolowitz!
What's that about?
I'm heckling you.
It's a beloved part of baseball.
He's right.
Given that you're probably still waiting...
...to be picked for a game in fifth grade,
I'm sure you do suck.
-Hi. What's going on?
-Baseball.
Okay, this is not whatl meant
when I said go outside and play.
-He's practicing.
-For what?
The Angels wanted an astronaut to throw
out the first pitch. So guess who they called?
What? You? Really?
Well, a lot of people
who weren't available, but then me.
That's so cool. Congratulations. I guess
that makes you the athlete of the group.
Well, notjust him.
May I remind you that you're talking...
...to the seeker, beater, chaser
and water boy...
...of the third place Griffith Park Quidditch
team.
Watching your boyfriend run around
with a broomstick between his legs...
...isn't something you forget.
-Come on. Now, throw one.
-All right, here we go.
You look like ajackass!
-Cut it out. You're hurting my feelings.
-Now you know why we're not outside.
Did you enjoy my lecture?
No, and neither did our waiter.
If you're going to serve
Cornish game hen...
...you should be familiar with the history
of Cornwall or be prepared to learn it.
It's hard to argue with that.
And I know because I saw a sad man
with a pepper mill desperately try and fail.
-Hey. How was dinner?
-Good, I had Cornish game hen.
Oh, that poor waiter.
Sheldon, how about tomorrow
we see a movie?
You guys are going out
two nights in a row?
I missed a number of date nights
while I was on my train trip.
I'm contractually obligated
to make them up...
...under the terms of the relationship
agreement.
That's so hot.
It's better than hot, it's binding.
If you're free tomorrow night,
I'd love to have you join us on a double date.
Aw.
You are aware that a double date
doesn't count as two dates.
Oh.
Well, then come or don't. I don't care.
Can't believe you're sore.
Hey, even professional pitchers
need a rubdown after the game.
They throw an actual ball.
You were throwing air at a TV.
For your information,
I also gave Leonard one hell of a high five.
I'm surprised you agreed to do this
in front of a stadium full of people.
Well, they're doing Space Day and NASA
asked me. I felt like I couldn't say no.
Okay. If you want, I could help you practice.
I played a lot of softball growing up.
Thank you, that would be great.
While we're at it, maybe we can butch up
your run for when you head to the mound.
What's wrong with the way I run?
Just kidding. Nothing.
Sheldon, I'm surprised
you'd choose to go to a pub.
At our committee meeting,
Amy made a motion for a picnic in a park...
...but I tacked so many amendments
on that thing it sank like a lead balloon.
I then suggested a pub.
Yeah, which I was initially skeptical of...
...until I saw online that they serve
Yorkshire pudding.
You don't like Yorkshire pudding.
No, it's yucky, but informing people about
the history of Yorkshire is yummy, yum, yum.
After a lively debate,
that proposal passed by a two-zero margin.
Nice to see a busy couple
keep the spark of bureaucracy alive.
SHELDON:
Ignore them, Amy.
They're justjealous because they'll never
have a relationship as good as ours.
PENNY: Isn't this when he says
"bazooka" or something?
SHELDON:
I wasn't making ajoke...
...l was merely stating facts.
Amy and l
have a superior relationship to yours.
You don't honestly think that, do you?
Leonard, I assumed you knew.
The ranking of relationships
in our circle, by quality...
...is me and Amy, Howard and Bernadette,
Raj and his girlfriend...
...Penny and chardonnay, Penny and you.
LEONARD:
There isn't any ranking.
And if there were,
we wouldn't be at the bottom of it.
Yeah. And actually, I drink sauvignon blanc.
That's the part you have a problem with?
Relax.
AMY:
There they go, fighting again.
You'd never hear her
talk that way to sauvignon blanc.
So you never played baseball as a kid?
Not even Little League?
l was going to, but the day of tryouts
I found my dad's Playboy collection.
Threw my arm out.
All right, the pitcher's mound
in Major League Baseball...
...is 60 feet, six inches
away from home plate.
Great. You take this and say when to stop.
-How much further?
-Keep going.
-How about now?
-l'll let you know.
Are you saying "stop"
and we're just too far away to hear you?
Okay, stop.
Are you kidding me?
That's 60 feet.
There's no way this is 60 feet.
I'm looking at it.
You realize this isn't one of those times...
...I want you to exaggerate
how long something is.
Okay, I gotta-- I just-- I gotta ask.
What makes you think your relationship
is so wonderful and ours isn't?
For starters,
we enjoy spending time together.
So do we.
And I've seen you guys ignore each other
for hours doing totally different things.
It's called "parallel play."
Yeah, toddlers do that.
Not as well as we do.
Can you believe this guy?
He has to be the best at everything.
So what? Why do you even care?
Oh, listen to them.
Not even married and the honeymoon's over.
Whatever. You can't even go on a date...
...without checking your relationship
agreement.
If you've got a problem
basing a relationship on a contract...
...l'd like to tell you about
13 plucky colonies that entered...
...a relationship agreement
called the U.S. Constitution.
And it may not be cool to say so, but I think
that love affair is still pretty hot today.
It's a good thing I'm not wearing
flag underwear right now...
...because there's about to be a fire.
[MOUTHS]
What?
Okay. It's not that hard.
You just look to where you wanna throw it...
...step towards
where you wanna throw, and throw it.
That's your help? That's like saying,
"Here's how you fly a plane...
...get in the airplane,
know where you wanna go, and fly it."
Just throw the ball.
Let's see what we're working with.
Come on, Howard, fire it in.
Throw the damn ball!
[POP MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
So when do you guys
plan on getting married?
We're not sure.
But I want to wait long enough
to prove to my mother I'm not pregnant.
-Mayl have one of your fries?
-Of course.
Can I have a bite of your burger?
Absolutely not.
Some perfect couple.
He won't even share food with her.
It has avocado on it.
She's allergic to avocado.
Are you so jealous of our relationship
you want Amy to die?
I'm notjealous.
I just think it's silly for you...
...to compare relationships
like they're something that can be quantified.
Everything is quantifiable.
That French fry? A seven.
Spider-Man? A nine.
The number nine? Oddly, only a four.
-How ridiculous is he?
-A hundred.
Sheldon, you're just assigning random
numbers to things based on your opinion.
No, I'm not. French fries have three variables:
crispiness, saltiness and shape.
Which is why a curly fry only gets a two.
If I wanted curls for dinner
I'd order a clown wig.
Well, a relationship
is more complicated than a French fry.
Not according to the work
of Berscheid, Snyder and Omoto.
Oh, what did those rascals do now?
They developed
the Relationship Closeness Inventory...
...which predicts the stability
of a couple based on behavior.
Yeah, not to be confused with the French Fry
Goodness Inventory. That's pure Cooper.
So this is accurate?
It's been around for 25 years...
...and has been extensively
corroborated by other researchers.
Kind of takes the romance
out of relationships.
Kind of? It does it perfectly.
Sheldon and I got an 8.2 out of 1D.
Fine. We'll take it right now.
-No, don't.
-What?
-Just don't take it.
-Why not?
It's stupid.
Who cares what number it is?
-Come on, it'll be fun.
-I don't want you to.
I'm getting another drink.
Sorry.
I'm gonna let you count this as two dates.
They are a lot of work.
You think he's getting any better?
Yep.
HOWARD:
That was a close one.
Okay.
-Is it too late for him to cancel?
-I think so.
HOWARD:
Heads up. Watch out.
-Are you mad at me?
-No, stop being stupid.
Um, phew.
Is this about the test or is this about us?
I don't need a test to make me worry
about something I'm already worried about.
What are you worried about?
That we're engaged and have
nothing in common and it scares me.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
Yeah, that scares me too.
-It does?
-Sometimes.
Well, that's not good.
You being blindly infatuated with me was the
rock we were building this relationship on.
Okay, well, this might make you feel better.
Uh, we're both scared
that our marriage will be a disaster...
...and so that's something
that we have in common.
Also, we both think I'm not funny. Heh-heh.
Huh? See, you're not laughing.
[LINE RINGS]
Hey, Froo! Loops, what's up?
Hey, Mike. Listen, NASA asked me to throw
out the first pitch at an Angels game.
You got any advice?
Yeah, don't do it.
What else you up to?
Why shouldn't I do it?
There's no upside.
If you do well, no one cares.
And if you screw up,
you're an idiot on YouTube forever.
But it's for a good cause.
What about all the kids that'll be there?
That's what I'm telling you.
Kids are the worst.
My own daughter tweeted
[have a giant nose.
Well, maybe I'll do a good job. Heh.
I don't know. In space you couldn't even
toss me a pen, and that was in zero gravity.
Okay, thanks for the pep talk.
Anytime, Froot Loops.
Give your wife a hug for me.
She's so much cuter than you,
I don't know how you ever got her.
He's so nice.
Hey. Sorry about that.
No, we're sorry. We never should have been
comparing relationships in the first place.
Why? We won.
I say next we take on
Koothrappali and his dog.
Really give ourselves a challenge.
I just want to say one more thing.
Just because Penny and l are very different
people does not mean we're a bad couple.
The answer is one simple test away.
You know, it's like when lthought
there was a possum in my closet.
Did I sit around wondering? No.
I sent Leonard in
with a pointy stick and a bag.
I killed his Chewbacca slippers.
-Let's just take the test.
-No, no, I don't want to.
-Because you know we're gonna do bad.
-It doesn't matter.
I don't care if we're a 1D or a two.
Or a one. A one is possible.
Marriage is scary.
You're scared, I'm scared.
But it doesn't make me not want to do it.
ltjust makes me want to hold your hand
and do it with you.
Leonard.
It would make me so happy
if you said things like that.
We got an 8.2.
Trust me, you're happy.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
Mm. I love how they put
a waterfall at center field.
It really ties the whole stadium together.
Look at you talking sports.
This is fun, huh? Get to see our friend
throw out the first pitch...
...have a hot dog, watch the game.
Whoa.
Nobody said anything
about watching the game.
Sheldon, what did you expect?
I expected to see Howard
throw the baseball, finish my hot dog...
...and hightail it across the street
to Disneyland...
...just in time for Mickey's Soundsational
Parade.
I'll tell you what, if we stay,
I'll buy you cotton candy and a bobblehead.
Who's the bobblehead of?
Does it matter?
No, as long as it bobbles.
Howie, I am so proud of you.
Thanks, I'm proud of me too.
You ready?
-Let's do it.
ROY: All right.
[HOWARD SIGHS]
-Wish me luck.
-Go get them.
ANNOUNCER [OVER PA]:
Ladies and gentlemen...
...in honor of Space Day at Angel Stadium...
...the ï¬rst pitch will be thrown out
by NASA astronaut Howard Wolowitz.
[CHEERING]
Thank you. Thank you.
Can he really throw a ball?
-On our Ouidditch team--
-Yeah, that's a no.
l have a message
for the young people here today.
When I was asked to throw the first pitch...
...a little voice in my head
said I couldn't do it.
So I practiced and practiced,
and you know what?
That little voice, ha, was right. But...
...then I remembered that I'm not an athlete.
I'm a scientist.
So today's first pitch
will be delivered to home plate by science.
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls, I present to you...
...a working prototype of the Mars Rover.
[CROWD CLAPPING]
LEONARD: Whoa!
RAJ ESH: Wow!
Whoo!
And here's the wind-up, and the pitch.
[WHIRRING]
Why is it going so slow?
Because I'm an idiot
who didn't think this through.
Okay, new plan. We go to Disneyland...
...play hide-and-seek
on Tom Sawyer's Island...
...and then come back
and see the end of the pitch.
[CROWD BOOING]
Okay, while we're waiting for the ball
to arrive, here's some fun facts about Mars.
RAJESH:
You suck, Wolowitz!
He makes a valid point!
[CROWD CONTINUES BOOING]
Okay, booing isn't gonna
make it go any faster!
[English - us - an]