Hey!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Thank you.
What's up, Comic-Con?
-(AUD|ENCE CHEERING)
-Whnn!
All right!
We're going to have fun.
Are you guys ready?
-Yeah.
-All right.
All right. Hey, writers.
-Hi.
-Hnw's it going? All right.
-Gnnd.
So, I'm so excited
to be moderating this panel.
We're going to have a lot of fun.
I'm going to ask a
few questions, and then
I'll throw to you guys,
and we'll go back and forth.
All right. Don't mess it up.
All right. Cool.
All right.
So, I'd like to know,
where do the story ideas come from?
Well, we often make them up...
(MELISSA CHUCKLING)
...and sometimes, we will
take them from our own lives.
One that comes
to mind involved... you.
-Me?
-As Bernadette and Wolowitz.
Do you guys remember the episode
where Wolowitz comes back from space
and Bernadette wants to reconnect
romantically with her husband
but she's really sick?
That was my wedding night.
(LAUGHTER)
And lwas really sick. And I held it
together during the wedding,
and then it all started coming
out of me at the end of the night,
and l was a mess.
And my wife was saying,
"It's okay, you should go to sleep."
And all I could say was, "No,
we have to consummate the marriage."
(GROANS)
So she's a lucky lady.
And I believe the nighty I wore in
that episode
was the one you wore....
You can see the mucus stains.
So, any other stories
come from your lives?
| always wanted a tiara. So....
You would look very good in one.
I think so. A pretty princess
and this is my tiara.
Maria, you-- In the episode
where Sheldon got spanked--
Yes, the one where
Amy gets spanked, and
she's trying to get attention from
Sheldon by pretending to be sick,
was from my high school.
That was me.
l was doing a play
with a guy I really liked,
and l was trying to seduce him
backstage by exaggerating my cold.
So I'd be like, "on,
I'm shaking uncontrollably."
And he would tuck me
in with his trench coat.
It was awesome.
How does the writing process work?
Do people go off and
write a script on their own,
or does everyone
work on every script?
Since the first season,
we've written as a group.
So, we sit in a room, and a writers'
assistant has the horrible job
of sitting at a typewriter,
and writing down everything,
and getting it right.
And we start, you know,
"Fade in: Interior Leonard
and Sheldon's apartment.
Sheldon comes in...."
We do it as--
We do it together.
Sometimes in a subset
of the whole group.
Usually, it's this group of people.
I don't know how we are not all
so sick of each other at this point.
I'm sick of some of you.
There's a lot of hugging,
I know that.
-And a lot of tears.
-Yeah.
Mostly after the hugging.
There's a lot of arguing.
One of the best moments of last year
involved me making
Steve very angry...
...when he was talking about
the great episode where...
There's a letter
from Howard's father,
and there's a question
as to what's in it.
And Steve said, "Well,
maybe there's a way to do it
where we never find out
what's in the letter."
And I said, "Oh, you've got to tell
people what's in the letter."
And then, Steve said, "Remember
there are children in the room."
He said, "You--
You're a bad person."
"You're really pissing me off
right now with your rules.
Now, I'm going to find
a way to do this episode
where we don't know what
was in the letter."
And I think it's terrific.
What's harder to write,
the science, or the "geek-ery"?
We have some help with the science
at the end of the table.
Believe it or not, we're all pretty
comfortable with the "geek-ery."
(LAUGHTER)
I mean, the science
comes sometimes....
We, you know, sometimes we have
ideas from articles we've read,
or sometimes we, you know,
have a vague notion of science,
or sometimes we put brackets
that say, "Science to come,"
and we toss it over
to Dr. Saltzberg here,
for him to fill in some things.
That's right. And it's maybe not
as exciting as a wedding night,
or slapping, uh...
but I do read Physics Today.
(CHUCKLING)
And sometimes we do
our own research,
like, you remember we were looking
for spider facts for something
for the Spider-Man joke.
Like what can....
There was ajoke where
Sheldon was irritated
by the Spider-Man theme song.
And he decided there were lots
of things a spider could do
that Spider-Man couldn't.
And then we had to try to find
what those facts were.
So we were all Google-ing things.
And I found this
website that was like,
"Amazing true science facts
about spiders."
So I was reading them,
and it's like, you know,
"The tensile strength
of a spider string
contains more potential
energy than the atomic bomb."
And, "Spiders live forever."
I mean, they can be killed,
you can kill a spider,
but if you don't kill them,
they will never die.
And we were like, "These are
great facts. Write them down."
Are you guys ready
to ask some questions?
Should I throw to you guys?
Yeah? All right.
All right. Cool costume.
It's, okay,
Princess Leia in disguise.
(LAUGHTER)
(DISTORTED, INDISTINCT SPEECH)
MELISSA: What?
Yeah, my question is--
Sorry, I am so nervous.
The cast, are they
like their characters?
Are we like our characters?
What do you guys think?
Well, Mayim in real life
is a neuroscientist,
and she plays one on the show.
I don't know, are you
like your character?
l'm nothing like my character at all.
I'm actually a six foot four,
African-American dude
in real life.
(LAUGHTER)
I believe-- Kunal, I believe,
is actually lndian.
Okay. Leonard is nice
and fun to hang outwith,
-and Galecki can be a bit much.
-Galecki is a problem.
His need to be liked....
We do all get excited when
we get to hang out with Kaley.
Fun to hang outwith.
-Does that answer your--?
-That's not an acceptable answer.
-MEL|SSA: Whoa! Excuse me?
-MAN: Okay.
It's not an acceptable answer.
Really? Dude, who are you?
Reveal yourself.
-(AUD|ENCE CHEERING)
-MELISSA: Wow!
"Someone who loves you."
(LAUGHING)
Johnny Galecki, everybody.
-Come on down.
-Hey, buddy.
Johnny Galecki, everybody.
Let's hear it for him.
-(AUD|ENCE CHEERING)
-Whoo!
He is going to join this panel.
MELISSA: Oh!
All right.
I couldn't stay away.
This is so exciting. All right.
Do we have another question
from the audience?
WOMAN: Since Season One,
we've seen Penny
go from being a ditzy blonde
to being more street smart.
I want to know how that
evolution came to be.
MAN: Well, it kind of mirrored
a change in Bill's personality,
from a ditzy blonde to a....
I don't think--
You know, I think that we just
got to know Penny better.
You know I think--
I think the pilot,
is a little off the series,
but, starting with the first episode
of the series, which is episode two,
I think that's the Penny
that she always was,
but we spent more time with her.
Although, the wardrobe
was a specific request.
And that was based on her
getting a smidge of success--
I think it was around the time
she got the hemorrhoid--
When she got the
hemorrhoid commercial.
We decided she probably got
some money from that, maybe,
bought some more grown up clothes.
But there's also the thing
and that was based on actors
and actresses that we know,
where once you get--
Once you get a little bit
of success, and you realize--
You buy a Boushh costume.
Yeah, that's right.
But that you're....
I assume you guys deal with this,
which is the notion that
when you go out in public,
and you can be recognized,
you want to look... not--
You want to look reasonable.
-MEL|SSA: | always look disgusting.
-True.
I thought that was great.
l have to say that I love that
the writers wrote Penny
as a talented actress.
And, I think we all kind of expected
to see Penny fail up on that stage.
That would have been a laugh,
but it really made us root
for that character
even more than we already did.
I loved that you guys
made that choice.
I mean,
I would ask you and Melissa,
I think her career
is moving at a speed
that matches the speed
of my friends who are actors.
-Sure.
-Yeah. So--
It goes kind of slow for a while.
MELISSA: A lot of wine,
a lot of waitressing.
Um...
Let's do one more question,
and then we'll go back to me.
MAN: The actors seem to laugh
a lot at their jokes.
Is there a lot of
improvising on the show?
There is no improvising.
What these amazing writers put
in that script, is what we say,
and we get the script the night
before the table read,
and | always say, it's like Christmas
morning whenever I get that script.
| get so excited to see
what they put on the page.
But even throughout
the week. I mean--
We do find what you guys find funny.
lt's... They're brilliant at what
they do, and hilarious.
Johnny, do you have...?
Yeah, well sometimes
the writers write on the fly
during live tapings, which is very
difficult to do, obviously.
And so sometimes
the line is very new to us.
And then often, it can be
an audience's reaction
that we don't foresee throughout
the week of rehearsal.
Like, they laugh too hard.
And we need to make it less funny.
You know, it really kind of governs,
not just the pace of a scene,
but sometimes,
the entire point of a scene,
or the priorities of a scene.
And that's a lot of fun.
And then sometimes, we're just
charmed by ourselves.
(LAUGHTER)
Kunal has a particular proclivity
for laughing at his own jokes.
But as an editing style for the show,
I mean, I think one of the things
that's always weird to me in sitcoms,
is sometimes, characters
say very funny things
that the character knows
is funny,
and the people in the room
don't laugh.
-Yeah.
-And that's weird,
because usually when people say
something funny, people laugh.
So, as an editing style,
when characters are reacting with
laughter, which is natural and real,
we like to use it because that's what
would happen in the real world.
Kaley laughs a lot.
Yes.
Eric, I hear that you've said
it's a very notice-y room,
that the writers' room
is a very notice-y room.
And what does that mean?
Well, yeah, that's a paradox.
Because this is a show that...
...celebrates the outsider,
and criticizes the human propensity
to shun or make fun of the outsider.
But, if you do something
unusual in the writers' room,
like, say, trim your nails
with the office scissors,
they don't let you forget about it.
So, it is--
It has been compared by some, me,
to being examined
by a monster with 20 eyes.
One of the most amazing members
of the Big Bang production team,
is Scott London,
who is our prop master.
And at production meetings,
we say to Scott, things like,
"We'll need killer robots,"
or, "We'll need
telematic kissing-machines,"
or, "We need giant Jenga."
And, Scott, he'll just go, "About
how big do you see the Jenga?"
(MELISSA CHUCKLING)
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
"Do I need two sets? One locked in
place for a point in the game,
or do all lose?
How do you want it?"
And then he makes giant Jenga.
The giant Jenga actually
came from Johnny, right?
Yeah, my brother in Chicago, got a
hold of some wood and a table saw,
and next thing we knew,
we were playing massive
Jenga in the backyard.
By flashlight.
And when you're the size
of my brother and l,
it's a dangerous game.
-lt's played to the death.
-Pretty much.
You need to be quick, if you're
down there at the lower tiers.
Then he also has to make
all the Chinese meals
that we eat around the table.
And for good or ill,
Scott was a chef beforehand.
And so, they're absolutely delicious.
-MEL|SSA: So good. So good.
-They're so good.
And we eat much too much
in between takes,
when we really
don't need to be eating.
MELISSA: There is a lot of eating on
the show. Is that intentional?
Do you intentionally write....?
There's a lot of eating
in the writers' room.
(LAUGHTER)
"So, you know, what could they be
doing at the beginning of the scene?"
And then we're sitting and eating.
"Well, maybe they're eating."
Okay....
They're very brainy characters,
so in order to make them relatable,
we want those things that
brainy people enjoy,
as well as regular people.
And one of those is eating.
MAN: Why do you pick on
geologists so much?
(LAUGHTER)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Actually, those lines
are all Jim Parsons.
He added all that about geology,
against our wishes.
-Yeah.
-So.
You can admit it.
It's not really a science.
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
It's a-- Come on,
it's a hobby. Right?
lt's rock collecting, isn't it?
I don't--
Do-- Wait, l--
Can l-- David, do you, at UCLA, when
you're walking through the halls,
do the geologists stop you and
ask you what the heck is going on?
I've had to stay out
of the Geology building.
They actually will throw rocks
at you, is my understanding.
It's the most dangerous
science to piss off.
That's right. "Do you know
what this is? This is feldspar!"
"This is quartz!"
But they're probably
not that great at throwing.
Sorry, I can't help it.
We have a lot of geologyjokes that
we haven't put in the script yet.
Apparently, you're
hearing them all now.
You're only encouraging them.
And on that note. Hi.
MAN: Are we ever going to see
the Koothrappalis?
I think it's entirely possible.
-Yeah, we've talked about it.
-Sure.
It hasn't happened yet, but we've
definitely talked about it.
MELISSA: Will we ever see
Mrs. Wolowitz?
-We've seen--
-We've seen glimpses of her.
-Will we see--?
-Like Big Foot.
Yes.
Will we see more of her?
So there's a lot of her to see...
So, we could show parts of her,
and really drag that out
for a long time--
They need to make
wider screen televisions.
It's always thrilling
to play a character,
and then meet that
character's family members.
Much like when you sit
down with a best friend
and you meet their parents,
and you think, "Oh, boy,
that explains so much."
And it's fun, and it's interesting,
and sometimes tragic.
But always more funny,
because it's not your family.
And-- So, it's really exciting
and insightful when you get
to meet a character
that the writers have written
who gives you even more backstory,
and understanding of a character
that you've been
playing for six year, so,
I'm looking forward to meeting
Leonard's father,
I'm looking forward to meeting,
spending more time with his--
And we always talked about
Sheldon and Leonard,
having the mother
that the other wanted and needed,
and really feeling that envy
between the two characters.
So-- And they're both incredible
actresses obviously,
so the more family, as far as
I'm concerned, the better.
It just takes a story.
It's a question that we get a lot.
And the answer is that,
you can't say,
"We're going to do an episode
where we meet one
of Leonard's siblings."
You have to have a-- There has to
be a story going on with Leonard
where meeting one of his siblings
is what you want in the story.
It all-- All of these things
start with story.
You have to have-- Leonard has
to be going through something,
or the arrival of a sibling
might change something.
MAN: What about your
personal experience
made you want to write for this show?
Well, I remember when lwas applying
for thisjob, I met with Bill.
And ljust tried to do a laundry list
of all the nerdy things
I'd ever done and that succeeded.
And one of them was, when l was in
college, I went to a costume party,
and l dressed up
as The Doppler effect.
And....
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
And, since it was college, I got
increasingly drunk during the night,
and ran around going:
(MAKES DOPPLER EFFECT
HORN SOUND)
And I think it was some time after
that story that Bill said,
"You have the job."
And also, then I was like,
"This is the best job in the world."
Maria had a pretty good story when we
met with her for working on the--
Yeah, right before
my interview for this job,
my husband and l were playing
a lot of World of Warcraft
because I didn't have ajob.
And it was our anniversary,
and we didn't have any money,
because I didn't have ajob.
And I said, "Why don't we give
ourselves in-game presents?"
And I really wanted a Phantom Blade,
because my rogue had just hit 30,
or whatever that is.
And I got him a Darkmoon Faire
Amulet, I got him a Lunacy Deck.
And he got me real-life chocolates.
And l was like,
"This is not what we talked about."
(LAUGHTER)
You have the saddest story.
Didn't you have
Dungeons 8. Dragons solo set?
Some of us played Dungeons 8.
Dragons when we were kids a lot.
-But if you were me--
-Nothing geeky about that.
Well, if you had no friends,
they made something called
Dungeons 8. Dragons solo modules,
which you could play by yourself.
And it was like,
"Choose your own ending."
And poor little lonely, fat Steve
would be there rolling his dice,
in his room with his solo module.
But now | get to work
on the show, so it all worked out.
I still have no friends.
Who was the most hardcore
gamer out of all of you?
-Maria.
-Probably Maria.
-Nice.
-Yeah.
You heard her story already, right?
-Do you have to ask that question?
-Pretty hardcore.
She'll take whatever is in the
environment, and play a game with it,
whether it's a stick
or a couple of rocks.
She'll start playing with them.
-She'll spin a hoop down the street--
-Hoops.
MELISSA: That is the only
correct answer. Moving on.
Who wrote out the Roommate
and Relationship Agreements?
Because I could really
use one of those.
We kind if pieced it together
as we've gone along.
lt's ever growing, isn't it?
Yeah, it's a living document.
It's a vast document, that seems to
have what you need for the story.
Oh look, it does have that!
I did a page of it for
Entertainment—
Right.
Entertainment Weekly
published a page that I did--
And I think you could see
a page of it on the screen
in the "Shelbot" episode.
-Yeah.
-When he flashes it to Leonard.
There's a prop that you guys have.
Does it have anything in it?
The binder? Oh, yeah. Again,
Scott London, the prop master.
Yeah, it's very, very detailed.
I've made it through a page
and a half at this point.
Are there any inside jokes
between the writers,
that make it into episodes?
I'm sure there are.
That's a very reasonable question.
-Well, Bazinga was an inside joke.
-If we think of any--
-Bazinga was a--
-Yeah, the grapefruit.
Bazinga was a thing
that came from the room
from Steven Engel,
who was a writer earlier on.
Names of people, often,
names of characters are....
Howard Wolowitz was the name of my
partner in the computer business
when l was a programmer.
And so, some of those things--
There was a time when
Wolowitz was talking about
bullies that had
bullied him in high school.
And we were using
bullies from our past.
-And lthink--
-This is true.
I think Jim Reynolds
might have actually,
he put his bully's name in,
and then asked to have it removed,
-because he was afraid.
-The next day.
(LAUGHTER)
That's a good bully.
That's a bully who
was good at his job.
-l'm so desperate--
-To terrify this guy.
I'm so desperate to tell
you guys the name right now,
just to watch Jim sweat.
Don't do it.
He was scary.
MAN: Considering how chaotic
Comic-Con is,
how does Sheldon handle that,
with all of his weird idiosyncrasies?
That's a really good question.
I mean, lthink we haven't
talked about that.
But I've got to believe that Sheldon
would have a very specific plan,
where he would prepare--
He would know the experience
he's going into,
and he would have coping
mechanisms
that he would have designed
for lines and things like that.
lt's howl handle Comic-Con.
I had very specific coping
mechanisms.
I bet we're not the people to ask
in this room, that question.
I bet some of you
know the answer to that.
But I think Sheldon,
difficult situations,
Sheldon does well
if he knows what the situation
will be, and...
...develops a coping strategy,
I think.
I mean it's kind of a dull answer,
but I think that's
how he would do it.
I think he'd hate "cutsies."
-Oh, people who cut the line? Oh no.
-Sheldon wouldn't like that.
Sheldon would probably believe
that there is a citizen's arrest...
...possible.
So, he would work
the logic this way,
saying a line creates
an implied contract.
He also would find it really weird
that his face is on those giant bags.
David, I have a question for you.
How often do you change
the whiteboard?
-Oh, they change every time.
-They change--
They often are related to what
the characters are
talking about that week.
And there's also some
inside jokes for the scientists.
Didn't you have your
students there one week,
and didn't you put up the answers
to the test they had just taken?
That's right.
It took them surprisingly
long to figure it out,
which might explain how they did.
But, it's a nice way
to goose the ratings,
by making sure they have
to watch the show.
So, I think that's good.
But sometimes,
they've been very cool things.
They've been... like when they
were talking about time travel once,
-there were time travel things.
-Sure. Sure.
-So if you can--
-The solution to time travel,
is always on the board
in the Big Bang Theory.
So if anyone wants to try it--
Well, actually, it's probably the one
behind the DNA molecule
you can't read.
WOMAN: Who's idea was Amy's tiara?
I think we were going
through the story,
and it was Chuck's idea
to give her the tiara,
and lthink I kind of
vomited out the whole,
"Oh, it's a tiara. I'm a pretty
princess, and this is my tiara."
So....
Any time there's something
that's very, very female
about being satisfied by something
in the world, that's from Steve.
-That's kind of who we lean to.
-You're welcome, guys.
There are two women on the writing
staff, but then there's Steve.
You were in the pageant world
for a while, weren't you Steve?
-l was.
-Oh, that was you.
I thought Steve, was....
Life is a pageant.
Very true.
Which character ended up
getting the tenure position?
-I don't think we know who yet.
-Yeah.
But at some point, it will happen.
Some, or none?
Will, or won't?
Get, or not get tenure?
Could you guys give us a tease of
what's to come in season seven?
Johnny?
(AUDIENCE WHOOPING)
I know nothing, and you know it.
-We will see Leonard on the ship.
-Oh, we will?
-Yeah, we will.
-Fantastic.
Will I have a parrot?
-Perhaps.
-We can't give away everything.
Now that Koothrappali can speak
to women without alcohol,
we'll be poking at that a little bit.
-MEL|SSA: Nice, nice.
-Anything else?
-People will have emotions.
-I think Mayim,
Bernadette and Amy may take
their first trip away together,
without Penny along.
So, that could happen.
Wisecracks will be made.
Do you think Sheldon
and Amy will ever... (BLEEP)
In other words, "doing the nasty"?
Could you be more explicit?
Eric, when a man and a woman....
I think I'll use Sheldon words,
and say,
it is a possibility.
Possibility? All right.
Once you erotically
massage someone's nose,
it is a slippery slope.
I think we all know
what happens after that.
I believe Amy will
continue to try to get her way.
I'm pretty confident in saying that.
I don't know.
They're kind of a, sort of an
irresistible force, immovable object
thing to write.
It always baffles me, how much
Amy has gotten Sheldon to move.
-Right.
-Yeah.
That's always amazing.
But it's a very interesting
thing in the writers' room,
because with Sheldon,
you have a character who
comes from a place of "no."
"No, I'm not going to change at all."
And, it's a lot of interesting
work in the room,
for somebody to say,
"What if Amy did this?"
And at some point somebody will say
something, and then you go,
"Okay, yeah. He'd
give in at that point." Right?
I also kind of think part of the
charm of their relationship is
its, sort of, glacial pace.
I think there's such a sweetness
to that, that I don't know,
I think one of the virtues is
how slowly we move it forward.
It also gives us a way
the show can last a lot longer.
A lot of us have kids
who need to go to college.
Great.
ldeally, when you watch the show,
you should pretend it's real
to enjoy it, so,
if you are like, "I know
what's going to happen
because I went to Comic-Con,
and people wrote it,"
I think you'd enjoy the show less.
I don't know.
This is my theory.
Well, doesn't that negate
the concept of this panel?
A little.
l'm skeptical of the whole Comic-Con
thing, because I feel like....
(CHUCKLING)
When I enjoyed The Wizard of Oz,
l was a big Wizard of Oz
fan as a kid,
I kind of related to the
Cowardly Lion as a real guy.
And if I was going on some website,
and there's like,
L. Frank Baum saying,
"I think in the next one, I'm going
to do this, and this, and this,"
it would be harder for me
to relate to the Cowardly Lion
as an imaginative reality.
But didn't you go
to L. Frank Baum Conventions?
Oh, yeah.
l dressed as Tick Tock one year.
It was cool. It was a cool scene.
I can't stress enough
how much you just all entered
the Big Bang writers' room.
That's what it's like.
That is easily 30 percent of the day.
You guys, thank you so much for
your help moderating this panel.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Thank you.
GALECKI: Can ljust--
I know we're running late.
But let me take a second to say that,
you guys are... I know everyone says
they have the best fans in the world,
and they're misleading people,
because this show has
the best fans in the world.
And the fact that we all gather here
every July, just before we go back
into full-swing production in August,
you guys give us the shot in the arm,
all of us, that is like no other,
to start every new season.
So, thank you, from
the bottom of our hearts.
-Thank you so very much.
-Thank you guys.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING AND WHOOPING)
Thank you.
(English us - SDH)