50 Sheldon, there's something
I've been wanting to talk about,
but I know it's kind of a touchy subject.
Way to narrow it down to everything.
What is it?
Well, your birthday is coming up
and you've never let us celebrate it,
and l was hoping maybe this year we could.
Oh. I suppose
that's a discussion we could have.
Okay, great. I mean,
it doesn't have to be a big party
or anything. I was just--
Where'd he go?
Wait a minute.
You mention his birthday and he vanishes?
Well, where has that information been
this whole time?
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Well, where is he?
-Sheldon?
-l'll check his room.
Surprise!
-Oh, my God!
-Why?
Just one example
of how birthdays can be terrible.
Now, can we please drop this subject
and pick a new one?
You know, I suggest, "How thick can
a soup get before it becomes a stew?"
You know, that answer,
it may surprise you.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Yeah, what is the problem?
Is it about getting older?
Please, look at this porcelain skin.
I'm like a human sink.
But it's the one day a year
that's just all about you.
One day. (LAUGHS)
Right.
Can you please just tell me why?
Fine.
As you know, I have a twin sister
with whom I obviously share a birthday.
Every year we'd have a party.
No one I invited would ever come
because they didn't like me.
I'm sorry.
That part wasn't so bad,
I didn't like them either.
But then I'd inevitably spend
the whole day
being tortured by my sister's friends.
Aw. Poor thing.
When I was six, they told me
Batman was coming to my party.
I waited by the door for hours.
Closest thing to Batman I saw
was when a robin flew into the window.
You realize none of those things
would happen now?
I do.
But why do you care
if I celebrate my birthday at all?
Well,
you made my last birthday so memorable,
I wanted to return the favor.
You know, if you had a party now, you have
plenty of friends who would love to come.
And we live here, so we have no choice.
Yeah.
Very well.
You may celebrate my life
by throwing a party
with cake, presents,
and a shower of admiration and love.
But then you owe me big time.
You have any idea what
you're getting Sheldon for his birthday?
He's been fascinated
with dinosaurs lately.
Maybe we could get him a fossil.
Just don't get anything Jurassic.
He feels like that whole chunk of time
has gone Hollywood.
You know, he told a sad story
about how his sister tricked him
into thinking Batman
was coming to his party.
That's funny, let's do that.
Maybe we could get Batman
to actually show up.
You mean, some guy in a lame suit?
Or a real Batman.
Hey, Stuart,
didn't you try to get Adam West
to do a signing here once?
Yeah, but there was kind of
a scheduling conflict.
He wanted to know when he'd get paid,
and lwouldn't tell him.
Can I get his contact info?
Sure.
But just so you know, he's kind of a diva.
-He is?
-Oh, yeah.
He won't take the bus,
he won't pack his own lunch.
He won't let you spend the night
on his couch.
Okay.
So, how do you feel about party balloons?
Mylar balloons, yes.
Latex balloons, no.
Water balloons, I will jump off the roof
and aim for your car.
All right, what about music?
I enjoy marching bands
and Tibetan throat singing.
No music it is.
What kind of cake do you like?
Well, my favorite is chocolate
with strawberry frosting, three layers,
and if there's writing on it,
make sure it's not all caps.
I don't need my dessert yelling at me.
Hey, so what was Adam West like
on the phone?
Nice guy.
But it was a little weird
to hear Batman say,
"Don't ring the doorbell
or my poodles will go crazy."
You know, Adam West is my favorite Batman.
Well, after Michael Keaton, Christian Bale
and Batman from The Lego Movie.
Don't say that to him.
What? He beat out George Clooney,
and that's something.
Like, I love me some Clooney.
Don't say that to anyone.
Thank you so much for helping us, Stuart.
l was just glad to be invited.
To be honest, I don't always feel
like I'm part of the group.
Okay, sweetie, we're on the clock here.
Can you hate yourself
and frost at the same time?
Hello. Hope I'm not too early.
Not at all. Come on in.
And how is the radiant mommy-to-be?
Doing great!
-You-- You're pregnant?
-Yeah.
Sounds like something
a member of the group might know.
Yeah.
Birthday party first, pity party later.
Are you crazy?
How can you put Michael Keaton
in front of Christian Bale?
Oh, please.
Even my poodles know Bale's overrated.
Thank you!
That's why I say Keaton's number one.
He brought a sense of humor to the role.
Well, if you're gonna factor in
a sense of humor,
well, I should be at the top of the list.
It should be me, Keaton, Kilmer,
LEGO, Bale,
and that pretty boy Clooney.
Really? You're ahead of Bale?
The man who personified the words,
"I'm Batman"?
I never had to say, "I'm Batman."
I showed up, people knew I was Batman.
Everywhere I went,
on the TV show, mall openings,
Julie Newmar's bungalow.
-l'm sold. You're ahead of Bale.
-(ALL CHUCKLING)
There's another reason
I should be higher on the list.
All those other guys
had muscles built into their costumes.
All I had in my batsuit
was 100% grade A West.
Can we just all agree
we're worried about Affleck?
-Sure.
-Yeah. Of course.
What's an Affleck?
Is there a reason
I had to leave my own apartment?
Well, I think theyjust want you to see it
for the first time all decorated.
But who's gonna tell them
they're doing it wrong?
Well, I'm sure they'll ask you
to give a speech,
and that's when
you just tear them a new one.
l have to say, you--
You do look good in that suit.
Oh. Thank you.
Maybe later I'll get to see you
in your birthday suit.
But this is my birthday suit.
Are you having a stroke?
Because that's the kind of thing
that just ruins a birthday party.
So, Mother, I'm surprised you came
all this way for Sheldon's birthday.
l was happy to.
He did come to my 60th.
Oh! You had a party for your 60th?
I wouldn't call it a party.
Just a few close friends.
And your sister and brother.
You know, to be fair, we did get married
in Vegas and didn't invite her.
And I never did thank you for that, dear.
-(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
-Oh!
Penny says everyone's there.
Are you ready?
(EXHALES)
I am.
Oh!
-Wait.
-Are you all right?
No, ljust... I got a little lightheaded.
Oh. Do you need a minute?
(EXHALES)
No.
No, if I can walk past that pet shop
with the parrot in the window,
I suppose I can do this.
ALL: Happy birthday!
(CHEERING)
Speech, speech!
Come on, Sheldon. Say something.
Why, thank you all so much for coming.
Beverly, Wil Wheaton,
Adam West, for some reason.
Batman finally came to your party.
Happy birthday, Sherman.
SHELDON: Thank you.
This is all so thoughtful.
(HEARTBEAT THUMPING)
Excuse me.
I still get paid, don't I?
Okay.
I'd better go in there and talk to him.
Well, don't you think
I'm the one who should go in?
No offense, but I've known the guy
a really long time.
Well, I've, you know,
seen him without pants on.
Again, no offense, but so have I.
Well, he's seen me without pants on.
-Again, no offense--
-Okay, this is ridiculous!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
PENNY: Sheldon? Can I come in?
How do you know
I'm not using the facilities?
Because you email me
your bathroom schedule once a week
even though I've clicked "unsubscribe"
like a thousand times.
So, what's going on?
I don't know.
I looked around the room
and I saw all the faces and the presents,
and it was just too much.
| get that.
Hey, you wannajust bring
a few people in here?
You know, Wil Wheaton in the bathtub,
Batman on the toilet.
It'll be like the weirdest Comic-Con ever.
I know that you worked hard
to put this together.
I'm sorry I'm ruining it.
Oh... You're not ruining it.
Look, at some point, Raj will try
to get everyone to do the Electric Slide.
Now that will ruin it.
I don't think I can go back out there.
That's fine.
You know, I hate that your sister
and her friends used to torture you.
But what I hate even more is,
if I was there,
I would have tortured you, too.
Based on this pep talk,
I'd say you're still doing it.
My point is, there was a time
I never would have been friends
with someone like you,
and now,
you are one of my favorite people.
So, if what you need
is to spend your birthday in a bathroom,
I'm happy to do it with you.
Well, everyone will think I'm weird.
Sweetie, you are weird.
Everyone knows you're weird.
But they're all still here
because they care about you so much.
BARRY: Hello?
Some of us need to check our hair
because we might have a shot
with Leonard's mother!
-Leonard.
-Hey, hey, hey.
-lt's been a while.
-Leslie.
Well, I can't remember
the last time we talked.
So much has changed!
Has it?
Yeah. Penny and I got married.
Oh! Congratulations!
You know, actually, lthought
you'd be living with Sheldon forever.
Yeah, well...
Don't be a stranger.
Okay, everybody.
Sheldon is gonna come back out,
but I think he's a little embarrassed,
so let's all be extra nice, okay?
What are you looking at me for?
I'm a saint. (LAUGHS)
But a sinner in the sack.
Hello, everyone.
I'd like to apologize for my behavior.
I hope it hasn't put
a damper on the party.
So, just, please, enjoy yourselves.
That's good.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Oh, this is quickly getting out of hand.
lfl may, I'd like to propose a toast.
Um...
Thank you all for coming tonight.
I know it's customary
for the birthday boy to receive presents,
but I feel like I got the greatest gift
the day he was born.
-Aw!
-Hear, hear. Yes.
Amy, that was lovely.
This is fun. Let's do more.
Someone else say
something wonderful about me.
Sheldon, I don't think everyone--
Wolowitz, perfect.
Everyone listen to Wolowitz.
Okay, then, uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
Sheldon. (CHUCKLES)
We've known each other a long time,
and it is a pleasure to work with you
and call you my friend.
Little generic, keep thinking.
We'll circle back.
Wil Wheaton, go!
Sheldon, I know that we have had
our ups and downs,
but I can honestly say
that my life is so much more interesting
because you are in it.
We may have met
because you are a fan of Star Trek,
but I have become a fan of Sheldon Cooper.
Live long and prosper, buddy.
And happy birthday.
-Cheers.
-ALL: Cheers!
That's how you do it, Wolowitz!
Now you see
why he's famous and you're not.
Sheldon,
I know the future holds
great things for you,
and we all can't wait
to see what they are.
Happy birthday, dear.
ALL: Cheers!
Someone call animal control,
there's a cougar on the loose.
Barry, stop.
Seriously, Barry, stop!
And it was Gandhi who said,
"Live as if you were to die tomorrow.
"Learn as if you were to live forever."
And it was Sheldon Cooper who said,
"Let's speed this up,
a lot of people wanna talk."
In the past,
I would've said something obnoxious
like, "Happy birthday, dumbass."
But I'm not gonna do it.
You and l have both grown a lot,
and it'sjust so nice
to see you all again.
So, happy birthday, Sheldon.
You know! hate change. Say it.
Happy birthday, dumbass!
Yes!
Happy birthday, young man.
And if any of you have enjoyed
seeing me here today,
I'm also available for Comic-Cons,
bachelor parties, bar mitzvahs--
I can't think of anything to say
that hasn't already been said,
so, here's to you, Sheldon.
-Hear, hear!
-Cheers!
Thank you, Bernadette. That was perfect.
What? You gotta be kidding me!
Sheldon, we've been together so long,
it's hard to remember a time
you weren't in my life.
Believe me, I try.
You make me laugh,
you make me a better scientist,
you make me crazy.
You're more than just my roommate.
You're my brother.
Thank you.
Happy birthday, buddy.
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
Thank you. That was wonderful.
Wait, wait, wait.
Stuart didn't get to speak.
Oh. Okay. Um...
Sheldon, I've spent
most of my life feeling invisible,
-but having you and everyone--
-AMY: Hey, everybody. Listen up!
You nailed it.
I've got someone who couldn't be here
but really wanted to wish you
a happy birthday.
Hello, Sheldon.
-Professor Hawking!
-(CHUCKLES)
Happy birthday to you
Thank you so much. I can't believe that--
You're singing. Well, I'm sorry.
Happy birthday, dear Sheldon
Uh, Professor Hawking,
if you just give us one second,
we'll light the candles
and we could all sing together.
I was crushing it, but all right.
Okay. While they get the cake,
Sheldon, I just wanna say,
I hope you didn't think you were
gonna get through tonight without a hug.
You know, I used to hate these hugs.
Now they're just extremely irritating.
Ready when you are, Professor Hawking.
And a one, and a two...
ALL: (SINGING) Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Sheldon
HAWKING: ...dear Sheldon
Happy birthday to you
HAWKING: ...to you
(ALL CHEERING)
So, who's taking me home?
English