Howard's capsule should be
reentering the atmosphere any minute.
-lt'll be good to have him back.
-The Fantastic Four, reunited, ha, ha.
You had a good run, fake Wolowitz.
We'll remember you
with nostalgic fondness...
...the way we do the dial-up modem...
...the VHS tape,
or Leonard's gym membership.
We're not kicking him out.
-Stuart and l have become good friends.
-Okay, one vote for, one vote against.
-Leonard, you're the tiebreaker.
-I don't have a problem with Stuart.
He gives us a 20 percent discount
at his comic book store.
Well, I don't sell
my friendship that cheaply.
-I can go 30.
-Welcome aboard, old chum.
Okay, the NASA website says
Howard's final descent has begun.
He left a boy.
He returns a boy-sized hero.
[HOWARD SCREAMING]
Loops, calm down!
[SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
-What's that?
-The Jewish prayer for eating bread!
We don't have one
for falling out of space!
We did it.
We're on the ground.
We survived!
That was just the parachute.
We still have another six miles to go.
[SCREAMING]
WOMAN [OVER PA]:
United Airlines K9,...
Waiting for my husband.
That's nice.
He's coming back from outer space.
I think this flight is coming from Houston.
No, I mean--
Never mind.
There he is!
Howie! Howie!
REPORTERS:
Howie! Howie! Howie!
-Howie! Howie! Howie!
-Thank you. Great to be back on Earth.
Uh, I think they're here for me, Ringo.
REPORTERS:
Howie! Howie!
-Mr. Mandel, I'm your driver.
-Oh, thanks.
That nutjob was telling everybody
on the plane he's an astronaut.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too.
Where are the guys?
Oh, it's just me.
Oh, I get it. They're waiting, back home,
with a big surprise party.
Don't worry.
I can act surprised.
[GASPS]
No, I told them
they could have you tomorrow night.
Tonight, you belong to me.
[SNEEZES]
-Gesundheit. You okay?
-I am now that you're back.
Come on, let's go home,
so I can tear off those little pants.
Great. Just keep in mind astronauts lose
a lot of muscle tone in space...
...so you might have to do
most of the heavy lifting.
Now, I am very disappointed
that I won't be able to celebrate...
-...Howard's accomplishment tonight.
-Me too, but we'll see him tomorrow.
Yes, it's just that
in all the years I've known him...
...he's never had the opportunity
to receive my admiration.
l was excited to see the look
on his face when it finally happened.
You're unbelievable.
I know.
All right, Pictionary.
What are the teams?
-How about boys versus girls?
-Oh.
That hardly seems fair.
But I guess any team that I'm not on
has a decided disadvantage.
-Once again, unbelievable.
-Yeah. Once again, I know.
All right, round one. Here.
-Got it.
-Okay.
Ready, set, go!
A box?
Uh.... Window?
Batman.
Batman and Robin.
Uh, Wonder Twins, plus the monkey.
Wonder Twins,
plus the monkey and Batman.
-Gift? Present!
-Present! Yeah!
Leonard.
Now, how can you not get that?
In what universe is that a present?
It's not a present.
It's the present.
Look, there's you and me.
It's Penny and Amy.
We're playing Pictionary, in the present.
Oh, my God, we're gonna kill them.
-lt's a quark-gluon plasma.
-No.
It's asymptotically free partons
inside a quark-gluon plasma.
Nothing with quarks.
It's an observational rebuttal
of the Lambda-CDM model of the universe.
-No.
-lt's a chocolate chip cookie!
Yes!
-How could you miss that?
-Hey!
If you want someone to guess
chocolate chip cookie...
...you draw a glass of milk next to it.
-Penny got it.
-Yeah, only after I eliminated...
...all the obvious answers.
You're welcome.
LEONARD:
Oh, uh....
Sausage.
Uh.... Bratwurst?
Oh, hot dog.
-Penny, aren't you gonna draw something?
-Relax, we've got time. This is so fun.
There.
A solar system.
Uh, uh, uh....
Unidentified flying liverwurst?
Now?
Soon.
Come on, Leonard.
lam spoon-feeding this to you.
I don't know.
Casper, the alcoholic ghost?
All right, that's enough. Ahem.
AMY:
Uh, hand?
-Nail? Polish?
-Yeah!
SHELDON:
No, no, no!
The word is Polish.
See? Look.
Polish sausage!
Model of the solar system,
developed by Nicolaus Copernicus...
...a Polish astronomer. Finally, if that
wasn't enough, which it should've been...
...this is Madame Curie killing herself
by discovering radium.
Who, although she was a naturalized
French citizen, was Polish by birth!
Excuse me, the word is polish.
See? Small P.
Ah.
So it is.
I guess we both share blame on this one.
Bernie, you okay?
BERNADETTE:
Yeah, I'll be right there.
[BERNADETTE HACKING UP PHLEGM]
Did you get a sea lion while I was gone?
[IN NASAL VOICE]
It's allergies.
Okay, ha.
I took some Benadryl, I'll be fine.
So did you miss me?
Are you kidding?
Every minute of every--
[HACKING UP PHLEGM]
Oh. Ew.
Excuse me.
Sweetie, we don't have to do this now.
Yes, we do.
-You left right after we got married.
-Ha, ha.
This is like our honeymoon.
-Now, hold on to your hat.
-Oh.
Uh-oh.
-You okay?
-A little dizzy.
Must be the Benadryl.
Switch places with me.
Okay, ha.
Now...
...kiss me.
[SNORING]
Bernadette?
Bernie?
-Bernie?
-Aah!
That was amazing.
You made me feel things I nev--
Well, that was quick and a little gross.
Now I know how she feels.
Hey, Sheldon,
you're always full of fun little facts.
Where did the expression
"got your ass handed to you" come from?
Don't know.
I wonder if it's from, like, ancient Rome...
...where they'd actually chop
somebody's ass off and then go, "Here."
You know, to appease Loseroneous,
the god of losers.
I am not a loser.
Pictionary is not a true test
of any real intelligence or skill.
In all fairness,
Pictionary has verbal skills, visual skills.
A pretty well-rounded game.
Lot of big talk from a man
who can't draw a chocolate chip cookie.
Fine, pick another game.
Amy and I will beat you at anything.
All right. Let's play...
...Physics Fiesta.
-Oh, come on. What is that?
-lt's a game that I just invented...
...in which the participants answer
physics questions in remedial Spanish.
Uh....
Donde esta eI boson de Higgs?
En el acelerador de paniculas.
Bueno, mi amigo.
No, no. We're not playing
some dumb, made-up game.
All games are made up.
They're not found in nature.
You don'tjust dig in the ground...
...come across a rich vein
of Rock 'Em Sock 'Em Robots.
-Pick another game.
-Why don't we do something athletic?
Like, go over to the university pool
and play water polo?
No good, Sheldon doesn't float.
That is true.
I have a higher than normal body density.
lfl run too deep a bath, | drown.
-All right, let's keep it simple. Darts?
-No, that's not fair, either.
-Why not?
-Darts is a bar game.
You've been frequenting drinking
establishments since you were of legal age.
Yeah, that's when it started.
Well, regardless, she has a distinct
advantage in all tavern-based competitions.
Pool, beer-pong, wet T-shirt contests.
They're all out.
Okay, just for the record,
I have never entered a wet T-shirt contest.
I've won a few, but that's just
because I spill when I'm drunk.
We could go to the cadaver lab at UCLA
and play real-life Operation.
-No.
-Uh-uh.
I don't think so.
You sure?
The nose doesn't light up...
...but if the corpse is fresh enough
sometimes you can get the leg to jerk.
Hey, Ma, twinkle, twinkle,
your little star is home!
Ma, the chain's on the door!
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard? I thought
I wasn't going to see you till tomorrow!
Yeah, well, Bernie's not feeling well,
so I thought I'd stop by.
Tell you about
the greatest adventure of my life.
See if you can make me feel bad about it.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Okay! Hold on, I'm not decent!
All right.
The woman hasn't tied her robe in 20 years.
Suddenly she's not decent?
MAN: You want me to hide in the closet
or go out the back?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Shh! You need to whisper.
Ma, who's in there?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Uh, nobody! The TV is on!
MAN: I only got one sock.
Where's my other sock?
-Who is that?
MRS. WOLOWITZ: I told you, it's the TV!
Jay Leno lost a sock. It's hilarious.
If you're busy, I can come back.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Just give me a second!
Go, go, go!
[WINDOW OPENING]
-Dr. Schneider?
-Oh.
Hello, Howard.
What are you doing here?
Um.... House call.
You're a dentist.
Yes. Yes, I am.
I think he's onto us!
Okay. Glasses off.
Find Waldo.
Hurry up, find him. Find him.
-l'm trying! Don't yell at me!
SHELDON: For goodness' sake.
He's wearing a hat,
glasses and a red-striped shirt!
-I know what he looks like!
-There he is, I got him!
Yes! We win again. Yes.
How could you not find him?
Because he's hard to find!
If he was easy to find,
the books would be called There's Waldo!
Fifty-seven, 58, 59.
That's one minute.
Long division, long division. Go, go, go.
Remember, show your work.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm not okay.
Get up. We can't--
We can't lose in math!
-Thirty-seven!
-Yes!
Ready, set, wrestle.
One, two, three, pin.
Mwah.
-Stop that.
-Mwah.
-Amy, do something.
Amy. Help.
Wha--? Amy, stop that.
Amy, Penny.
Both of you, stop it.
One to beam aboard?
Oh, my God, you're back.
Oh, look at you.
You-- You look like you grew.
Yeah.
The lack of gravity did decompress my
spine, so I'm, like, an inch-and-a-half taller.
I'm going to the DMV tomorrow to get
my license changed before I shrink back.
Come in, come in. I didn't think I was
gonna get to see you until tomorrow.
Yeah, well, Bernadette's a little
under the weather and my mom's...
...kind of under my dentist.
Wait, your--
Your mother's sleeping with your dentist?
Former dentist. I need a new one
now that I know where his hands have been.
So you're wandering
all around by yourself?
That's not the hero's welcome
an astronaut should come home to.
It's okay. You know, we space cowboys
don't do what we do for glory and fame.
We leave that to your rock stars,
and your athletes...
...and your Howie Mandels.
Oh, hey, man, welcome back.
Oh, Stuart, thanks.
What are you doing here?
-I kind of live here now.
-Just until he gets back on his feet.
Which are looking pretty good
in the boots I bought him for his birthday.
[MIMICS EXPLOSION]
Ah, he's spoiling me and I love it.
Wow, ha, so you guys are, like, buds now?
Oh, yeah. We hang out all the time.
He doesn't have a girlfriend,
I don't have a girlfriend.
It's like we both had holes in our lives,
but now we fill each other's holes.
That sounds a little funny
to an American ear.
-Which part?
-Just all of it.
Okay, so, what--?
What do you guys got going on, tonight?
Raj is taking me
to the Sound ofMusic sing-along.
Sound ofMusic sing-along?
That used to be our thing, but that's cool.
Howard, it's still our thing. Come with us.
We'll get you a scalped ticket.
So I'd be sitting by myself?
We'll switch.
You'll come sit with me after intermission.
So I'd be sitting by myself
during "Edelweiss"?
No, no, you guys go.
Have fun.
-Okay. Will I get to see you tomorrow?
-Absolutely. See you, Stuart.
Yeah, yeah.
Is he taller?
At least my mother made her boyfriend
climb out the window.
All right, standard state fair
pie-eating contest rules are...
...no hands,
first one to clean the pan wins.
On the count of three.
One...
-...two--
-Wait.
I'm a little concerned.
Blueberries are rich in antioxidants.
-So?
-So with all those antioxidants...
...what if I run out of oxidants?
Sheldon, we haven't won a game all night.
You either stick your face in that pie,
or I'm gonna stick that pie in your face.
That's rude.
One, two, three, eat.
Hay. 9Uys.
guess who's back from space.
ALL:
Not now!
Oh, ow! Blueberry in my nose!
Blueberry in my nose!
Snort it down and keep eating!
[SNORTS]
You look familiar.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
ljust saw you on the news.
You're an astronaut.
Yes. Yes, I am.
Good for you. How about a piece
of cheesecake on the house?
Oh, thank you so much.
I've been having the worst night.
I just got back and my friends don't care,
my wife's sick.
-Went to my mom's--
-You want the cheesecake or not?
Yes, please.
[SINGING]
And I think it's gonna be a long, long time
Till touchdown brings me
Round again to ï¬nd
I'm not the man they think I am at home
Oh, no, oh, no
I'm a rocket man
[SNEEZES]
Perfect.
[English - us - an]