Leonard, I've been working on an opening joke
for our lecture at Berkeley.
Ooh, I like to laugh, but say it anyway.
Okay. Uh....
"What do you say to a graduate
of the UC Berkeley Physics Department?"
"I'll have fries with that." Heh.
Because his education hasn't prepared him
for a career in the sciences.
When they chase you out of there,
you have to run faster than Sheldon.
-Are you all set for your trip?
-Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, ljust restocked the old PRK.
-PRK?
-Public restroom kit.
Everything a boy needs for making pee-pee
in new and strange places.
I don't see what's crazy about bringing a
backpack with your own toilet paper and Purell.
Keep going.
And rubber gloves, air freshener...
...uh, noise-canceling headphones.
Oh, danger whistle.
Um.... Pepper spray.
Ooh, a multi-language "occupied" sign.
Let's see. We have seat protectors,
uh, booties for my shoes...
...a clothespin for my nose.
Oh, and a mirror on a stick...
...so I can make sure the person in the stall
next to me isn't some kind of weirdo.
You're still worried some Berkeley girl
is gonna steal him away?
Yes, who do you think gave him
the danger whistle?
Would you like to play a physics car game
I invented called I Can't Spy?
It's all the nail-biting tension ofl Spy...
...but the added fun of subatomic particles
and waves outside the visible spectrum.
If it's half as much fun as One Times Ten to
the Fourth Bottles of Beer on the Wall, I'm in.
I'll begin. Uh....
I can't spy with my little eye...
...something passing right through us.
That soy Frappuccino I had. Heh.
Will you please play the game?
I can't spy with my little eye
something passing right through us.
I don't know. Um....
If 65 billion solar neutrinos pass
through a square centimeter every second...
...given the surface area of this car
is about 60,000 square centimeters...
...that means 3.9 times 10
to the 15th solar neutrinos?
I don't want to play anymore.
Haven't been on a road trip in a while,
this is fun.
We get it, you won the game, stop bragging.
We wrote a paper together. Now we get to go
to a university and talk about it.
That's pretty cool.
I suppose it is.
In fact, if you'd like to celebrate
with a little music...
...l'd be okay with that.
What?
This road trip just got crazy. Ha, ha.
Play that funky music, white boy.
I'm surprised you know that reference.
What reference?
I put stickers on everything we're gonna sell.
We need help taking it all out to the driveway.
Can I be in charge of pricing?
I've been going to garage sales my whole life.
Can you believe I got these panty hose
for a nickel?
All right, Amy's in charge of pricing
and being 75.
-Hey, Penny, can you give me a hand with this?
-Sure.
We had one of these growing up.
I used to play all the time.
Oh, yeah? I love Ping-Pong.
Oh, I meant Beer Pong.
I had a table too, but I didn't have any friends,
so all I did was serve.
You can leave one side up
and play against it.
And ifl had afriend,
they might have told me that.
Excuse me, why is there a sticker on this?
It's my TARDIS from Doctor Who.
I was planning on moving it in the house.
I think you just answered
your own question.
Come on, one day this may double in value
and be worth half whatl paid for it.
We have a lot to do.
We don't need to decide this right now.
Well, I guess as long
as you're keeping an open mind.
Of course.
[WILD CHERRY'S "PLAY THAT FUNKY MUSIC"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Play that funky music right
Play that funky music, white boy
So they're requesting that the white boy
play the funky music, yes?
Yes.
And this music we're listening to right now
is funky as well?
Sure.
Let me ask you this.
Do you think this song is the music
the white boy ultimately plays?
It could be.
So it's like the musical equivalent
of Russell's paradox.
The question of whether the set of all sets...
...that don't contain themselves as members
contains itself.
-Exactly.
-Well, then I hate it.
Music should just be fun.
[MUSIC STOPS]
We're making great time.
We're gonna be there pretty early.
Will our hotel room be ready?
I doubt it.
Aren't you worried that sitting in the lobby
for a long period of time...
...might attract the attention
of the hotel detective?
If we do, we'll just tell him
to "Hit the bricks, see."
Seems a little confrontational, but all right.
You know, we won't be very far
from Skywalker Ranch.
Ah. That's true.
But it's not like we can get in there.
-Why not?
-I don't think George Lucas...
...put his headquarters in the middle of nowhere
because he wanted people dropping in.
Yoda's swamp
was in the middle of nowhere.
Tatooine was in the middle of nowhere.
Hoth was in the middle of nowhere.
That's code, Leonard.
He wants us to drop in.
We do have time.
I mean, we could drive by and just look at it.
Yes. Oh.
I'm so excited and ljust can't hide it.
Ooh. I'm about to lose control
and lthinkl like it.
What are you talking about?
So when do you guys think
you're gonna move in?
We're still figuring
how much remodeling we wanna do.
Tricky finding the balance...
...between tasteful modern
and Jewish mother tchotchke crapfest.
Have you made a decision
about the TARDIS?
I think I can sell it
if we call it "Big British Porta-Potty."
We're not selling it. It's mine.
You can'tjust decide.
How about I arm-wrestle you?
That's not fair.
It's like me challenging you
to a sexy pants contest.
-You could play Ping-Pong for it.
-I would do that.
How is that fair? You grew up with a table.
Yes, but I mostly used it as a battlefield
in an ongoing war between the Transformers...
...and the ThunderCats
for control of a bra I had found in the woods.
For every episode of Doctor Who
Leonard has made me sit through...
...I will play on your behalf
and send that TARDIS back to Gallifrey...
...where I hate that I know it belongs.
Yes, Penny plays for me.
That's not fair.
She has upper body muscles.
Dude, three-time Sanskriti School
for Well-Born Boys badminton champion.
That's right. Raj can play for me.
Oh, you just chose champions.
Like reenacting the ancient German practice
of trial by combat.
Like when the Mountain fought the Red Viper
in Game of Thrones.
-Leonard makes you watch that?
-No, I like that show.
It's got dragons and people doing it.
It's settled. Fate of Doctor Who's TARDIS will
be decided by a Game of Thrones-inspired...
...death match on the battlefield
of ThunderCats versus Transformers.
If you still have that bra,
I'll give you a nickel for it.
There it is.
It's just a gate.
On a road.
It wasn't even that hard to find.
-This is so amazing!
-I know!
-You wanna get a picture?
-I want more than a picture.
-I wanna go in.
-Well, so do I, but they'll never let us.
Is that the attitude
that helped you get Penny?
No, but I don't have three years
to make that gate feel sorry for me.
Ye-- There's a speaker box.
Drive up, push the button
and let's see what happens.
Okay, yeah. What do we have to lose? Heh.
I'm a little nervous.
Well, get over it.
Confidence is key in these situations.
Right.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
You pushed it. Are you out of your mind?
-MAN [OVER INTERCOM]: Canlhelp you?
-Uh, uh, uh....
We don't have an appointment and we don't
belong here, but we're, like, crazy big fans.
I mean, "crazy" for Star Wars crazy, not crazy
like we have a backpack full of duct tape.
Although we do have a backpack
that you really don't wanna look in.
You're blowing it.
We wanna meet George Lucas
and become his friends and play with him.
MAN: Hello?
This speaker's not working. Just pull up.
And that's how it's done.
All right, we've defeated the first challenge.
Now we must steel ourselves
to face the monster who defends the gate.
We're trying to get past a security guard,
not rescue Zelda.
I think what really needs to be rescued is
your sense of whimsy, but one quest at a time.
So, what's the plan?
I'm just gonna be honest with the guy.
Honesty will never get us in.
Well, what's your plan?
All right, my plan
is predicated on the assumption...
...that they have a nurse's office...
...and your willingness to be lightly stabbed.
-Who are you here to see?
-l'm gonna tell you the truth.
Oh, you are killing me.
We don't have an appointment.
We're just fans of Mr. Lucas' work.
We thought we'd take a shot,
see if we could get in and look around.
5°"V. guys, we get this a lot.
I can't let you in.
What if I told you
that l was the voice of Yoda?
A recording session, I must attend.
I'm sorry. Don't listen to him.
We're actually physicists.
We're giving a lecture at Berkeley later today.
We just-- We had some time to kill.
Hey, listen, you seem like decent guys.
I can't let you in,
but I've got hats and T-shirts I can give you.
Thank you so much.
See?
Maybe honesty is the--
What are you doing?
Shedding the yoke of my oppressors,
you blind, sad little man.
Don't move.
Code A-A 23. A-A 23.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Copy.
SHELDON:
I can see the ranch, Leonard.
Oh, it's rustic, it's lovely.
I'd take a picture,
but people are chasing me.
I'm gonna make it. I'm gonna make it.
They have Tasers,
but they wouldn't dare use-- Aah!
Come on, Raj.
You are the King Kong of Ping-Pong.
You are the menace of table tennis.
Put her away
because I don't have a third one.
Yes! Whoo!
Rajesh: 8, Penny: 4.
Sorry, he's really good.
Hey, Raj, if Howard can't keep the TARDIS,
how great would it look at your place?
-What?
-Yeah, what?
I don't know much about Doctor Who
but if, um...
...you were to put this right outside
your front door...
...and open up the back...
...it would be like your entire apartment
was the inside of the TARDIS.
Which is pretty cool, because on the show...
...the inside of the TARDIS
is bigger than the outside.
But then again,
I don't know much about Doctor Who.
Don't listen to her.
You and I go way back. We're like brothers.
We are. We are. Ahem.
Oh, no, what a terrible serve.
Sorry, brother.
-Eight-five.
-This is ridiculous. I want a new champion.
Amy, were you serious
about being able to serve?
Oh, it's been a long time.
I don't know. I'm probably pretty rusty.
-She's my champion.
-Well, if you can switch champions, so can I.
-I want Raj.
-Hey.
Oh, come on, like you even care.
Well, I care.
Oh, wait, no, I don't. Good luck, Raj.
-I thought our friendship meant more to you.
-So did I.
-Do you think they're gonna call the police?
-I don't know.
Maybe they'll call Imperial officers
to take us to a holding cell on the Death Star.
Oh, I think that's below the pay grade
of an Imperial officer.
-Stormtroopers are really the ones--
-Oh, shut up.
He's right.
Stormtroopers actually combine both
the function of infantry and military police. Heh.
Uh-huh. I'm normally very nice,
but you shut up too.
So, what are you in for?
Honestly, I just wanted to meet Mr. Lucas
and say thank you.
Growing up, the movies
had such an impact on my life.
I never really fit in anywhere
till I discovered the worlds he created...
...and finally found a place where I belong.
But why are you here?
Oh, I hopped afence...
...and they caught me in the sculpture gallery
making out with a Chewbacca statue.
Excuse me.
Leonard.
They have a sculpture gallery.
I talked to my supervisor
and we're gonna let you go with a warning.
But if you come back,
we'll call the police and press charges.
We understand. Thank you so much.
-Uh, what about me?
-You're not going anywhere, kissy face.
Let's go. I have to take your picture,
post it at the guard gate.
Uh, one question about that picture:
Can it be with George Lucas?
Ooh. Grumpy, you are.
Okay, this is the match that decides it all.
First to 11 wins.
Serve switches every five points.
And just so you know, when this started...
...l was going to put the TARDIS
in a discreet corner...
...but now it's going
right in the middle of the living room...
...on a rotating platform
with a sign that says "Suck it." Game on.
Except Raj is gonna win.
Isn't that right, Raj?
Yeah, I mean, her serve was pretty good.
Come on, get in her head. Be intimidating.
Okay.
I'm gonna own you, bitch.
-Raj.
-Hey.
That's not nice.
Let's just play.
One-zero. Two.
Three. Four.
Five-nothing.
Ha, ha. Wait, did you play badminton
or sadminton?
Don't listen to him. All she's got is a serve.
Now, grab a fresh tampon and put her away.
Wha--? And that's not offensive?
Where's the line?
It's in your purse. Play.
BERNADETTE:
One-five.
Two-five. Three-five.
Four-five.
Five-five.
Six. Seven.
Eight. Nine.
Ten-five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight. Nine.
Ten-ten.
That was an exciting 40 seconds.
It was, and now the serve is back to you
and the game is over.
You know, Amy, I can't help but wonder...
...how Sheldon would react
if the TARDIS was at your place.
-Don't listen to her, just hit the ball.
-Keep talking.
If this doesn't get him into your bedroom,
nothing will.
-Are you still mad at me?
-Yes.
We missed our lecture...
...we were almost arrested,
and you got me locked in a room...
...with a man who forced his tongue
down the throat of a stuffed Wookiee.
Boy, some people are just glass half-empty.
The glass is empty, Sheldon.
It's completely empty.
If you gave that glass to a man who was dying
of thirst, he would be dead. You know why?
Before I answer, was he a smoker?
I think you're looking at this all wrong.
Fine, then tell me
howl should be looking at it.
Well, not only did we go
to Skywalker Ranch, we got in.
And no one we know can say that.
And for all the times you find me irritating...
...today you got to watch someone
shoot me with a Taser.
That part was pretty good.
See?
You did flop around a lot.
I'll take your word for it,
I was too busy trying not to defecate.
You know, when they were escorting us
to the detaining room...
...I looked through a door
and I'm pretty sure I saw a display case...
...with the Ark of the Covenant. Ha, ha.
That's amazing.
And I saw Jabba the Hutt
riding on a motorcycle.
Although that was right after the Tasing,
so who can say for sure.
I guess this could count as an adventure.
It was.
And even though we're not allowed back there,
they can never take today away from us.
Unlike my sense of smell,
which hasn't returned since the Tasing.
No, I got nothing.
Amy, the Daleks are right on my tail.
Quick, we need to reset the time circuits.
Oh, no, I left my sonic screwdriver behind.
I really should have thought this through.
[English - us - an]