Did you hear about this study
that found people
that were cool and popular at 13
have problems succeeding later in life?
Hmm. I'm doing okay
and l was very popular at 13.
-In school?
-Oh, no, at home.
The servants would sing to me,
laugh at myjokes.
lwish I knew their names.
Does the study say
what happens to the unpopular kids?
You tell me. You woke up in bed with one.
Listen to this.
ljust received an email from Wil Wheaton.
Leonard Nimoy's son is working
on a documentary
that he started with his father
before he passed away.
It's about Mr. Spock
and his impact on our culture.
Why is he writing to you?
Well, they're looking for fans
to interview
-and Wil thought I'd be good for it.
-Oh. Hey, high five.
Absolutely not.
Yeah, Penny, you've spent some time
in front of the camera.
Any words of advice?
Yes, don't take your shirt off
just because the director said so.
This is a documentary about Mr. Spock.
I'm sure if there's nudity
it will be tasteful.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
(SWORDS SLASHING ON TV)
Hey, you got a minute?
Not really.
Visigoths are kinda up my butt right now.
Pause the game, Howard.
Howard? Oh-oh. Make room, Visigoths.
'Sup?
We need to talk about
redecorating this place.
(SIGHS) No, not this again.
(SIGHS) Look, | get that you grew up here,
and you're attached to things
looking a certain way,
but I want this to feel like
my house, too.
(CHUCKLING) Oh. Honey,
of course it's your house.
Why else would you be cleaning it
all the time?
(CHUCKLES)
All right, let's start over.
l'm redecorating.
The furniture, the carpeting, the walls.
l'm changing everything that depresses me
when I look at it.
Try not to be one of those things.
May I say something?
Is it about howl can't have new wallpaper
'cause your dad left
when you were little and your mom died?
Never mind.
Hello, Amy. lt's Sheldon.
Yeah, I know that we're broken up but
I'm leaving this message because
I thought perhaps
you'd like to watch me be interviewed
for a documentary about Mr. Spock.
Or as I like to call it, a Spockumentary.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah, I'm going to use that joke
in the interview,
so try to laugh
like you're hearing it for the first time.
You know, hysterically.
And with a tinge of sadness
that I'm no longer in your life.
I'm the one who thought of Spockumentary.
And I'm laughing like I did
the first time I heard it.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
-Hello.
-Hey, Sheldon.
-This is Adam Nimoy.
-Nice to meet you.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
I admire your father's work very much.
It's not every day | get to meet someone
whose life's journey began
in my hero's scrotum.
I told you, this guy is gold.
Whatcha doing?
Oh. Making myself a bologna sandwich
like my mom used to make me
after my dad left but before she died.
Okay, listen, I'm thinking that maybe
we can compromise on the house.
I'm listening.
Let's just redo one room
and see how it goes.
That is reasonable, but what room?
-How about this one?
-No way, no.
This is the room
| associate the most with my mom.
-Then how about the bathroom?
-I wanna change my answer.
Fine, then the dining room.
I guess we didn't use it very often.
Unless we had company.
Which didn't happen much after
my dad left but not at all after my mom--
Great, I'm gonna go
pick out paint samples.
All right.
We're just gonna have a conversation,
pretend the camera's not here.
All right.
But this better not be some elaborate
scheme to get me out of my shirt.
-How long have you known Adam?
-A few years.
-And what are you getting him back for?
-(CHUCKLES)
Let's start with your name and occupation.
Doctor Sheldon Cooper,
Theoretical Physicist, Caltech.
ADAM: And what is your earliest memory
of the character Spock?
The ﬁrst episode of
Star Trek: The Original Series Ieversaw
was The Galileo Seven.
Uh, Spock had just landed on the planet
Taurus II.
Then my brother came in, sat on my head
and said, "Eat farts. "
After that day I was hooked.
On Star Trek,
not my brother's sphincter-based cuisine.
What was it about Spock
that appealed to you?
I think the same thing that
appeals to people everywhere.
The dream of a cold rational world
entirely without human emotion.
Spock came from a planet
governed only by logic.
You know, on Vulcan,
when your brother asks,
"Why are you hitting yourself?"
The answer is,
"I'm not. You're moving my arm. "
To which he says, "Fascinating."
And then you both watch
educational television.
Oh. When he says things like that ljust
wanna hug him and make everything better.
-My brother was mean to me, too.
-Yeah, you probably had it coming.
Do you have any Spock collectibles?
I have many.
My most treasured is an autographed napkin
given to me
by my very thoughtful friend, Penny.
That's her over there.
Hi.
(CHUCKLES) Look at that, I'm in a movie,
my shirt stayed on.
-Can we see the napkin?
-Of course.
Excuse me. This will just take a moment.
When did we get a wall safe?
When there was no more room
in the floor safe.
When did we get a floor safe?
When we got the security camera.
There's a security camera?
Aquaman. Protecting your home since 2012.
Oh, my God,
we've done things on that couch.
Yeah, you don't have to tell me.
So, your father-in-law
is in there right now?
Yes, so back me up.
The house is good the way it is.
Okay. Got it.
-Hey, what's going on?
-Hey.
Hey, Raj, Dad and lwerejust
talking about taking down this wall.
You sure? It's a pretty great wall.
What's so great about it?
I'm sorry, I did what I could.
Seriously? You brought Raj over
to take your side?
Your dad's on your side.
He's not on my side.
He's doing all the work for free.
That is so generous of you.
I'd like to switch sides.
Look, I don't even think you can take
this wall down 'cause it's load-bearing.
Well, it's easy to find out, just go into
the crawlspace under the house and check.
When is your visa up?
Not only is it signed to me,
but this is where he wiped his mouth.
So, we are currently in the presence
of Leonard Nimoy's DNA.
Um, doesn't Adam count
as Leonard Nimoy's DNA?
No offense,
but this is pure 100 percent Nimoy.
Now, because of your mother,
you're only 50 percent.
Which isn't bad, but anything that
you wipe your mouth on gets thrown away.
Okay, enough about the napkin.
What else you hiding in there?
-Wouldn't you like to know.
-I would.
Yeah, all right, then.
See, it's just my valuables.
My passport, my will.
-You have a will?
-Yeah, my one-eighteenth scale
Wil Wheaton action figure.
Yeah, I also have the other kind of will.
And in it I will my Wil back to Wil.
-Wi|| Wil want it?
-Wil won't.
-What's that ring box?
-Oh, that is an engagement ring,
that I was going to give
my girlfriend Amy.
What?
You bought her a ring?
No, no, no, this has been in my family
for generations.
No, except for a short time when Comanches
cut off my great-great-great
grandmother's ﬁnger and stole it.
Sheldon, that's awful.
No, the Texas Rangers
tracked them down to their village
and slaughtered every last one of them.
It was a happy ending.
Well, for my nine-ﬁngered nana.
Okay, back to the ring.
Does Amy even know about this?
No, she broke up with me
before I could broach the subject.
Man, I'm sorry.
That must've been devastating for you.
No, not at all. No, I'm fine.
You know, Amy had reservations
about our relationship
so all worked out for the best.
-I know, it'sjust--
-I said I'm fine!
We've gotten a little off topic.
Allow me to make things entertaining again
in this little Spockumentary.
That was Leonard's joke.
As a child, when faced with a dilemma,
my mother encouraged me to ask,
"What would Jesus do?"
The answer to that was always,
"Love thy neighbor. "
But my neighbor had a dead tooth,
so that wasn't going to happen.
But that's why I changed it to,
"What would Spock do?"
Did you find that helpful?
Yes. No, for example, three years ago
when I discovered
Penny was eating all my Pop-Tarts,
instead of getting angry or vindictive,
you know, I got a floor safe.
I knew I could smell 'em.
-What about from when you were a kid?
-Oh, certainly.
Uh, when I was eight years old,
Billy Sparks cornered me
in the playground.
I asked myself, "What would Spock do?"
Then I grabbed Billy on his shoulder
and performed my ﬁrst Vulcan nerve pinch.
-Did it work?
-Oh, no, he broke my collarbone.
Yeah, I can still hear it click.
That must have been
very upsetting for you.
Oh, not at all. As I said,
the entire point of emulating Spock
was to rise above human emotion,
which I've spent a lifetime mastering.
Oh. (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
-Excuse me?
-l'm sorry, I'm not here.
No, you went... (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
What does... (BLOWS RASPBERRY) Mean?
-Uh...
-You did go... (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
Okay, fine.
Sheldon, I'm no expert, but aren't you
completely missing the point of Spock?
He liked to act like he had no emotions,
but he was still half-human.
Just like you.
I'm just saying, you pretend you don't,
but you have feelings
just like everybody else.
Not true. No, look at me.
I had an engagement ring to give a girl,
and instead she rejected me.
And am | emotional about that? No.
No, lam sitting here on a couch
talking about my favorite TV character
like nothing happened.
'Cause I am just like him.
All logical, all the time.
-Sweetie, you're yelling.
-Because when I speak at a regular volume
no one seems to believe me that
I've put this Amy nonsense behind me.
(DOOR SLAMS)
This documentary is gonna be awesome.
-You gonna be okay down here?
-Yeah.
| feel like an archaeologist.
Indiana Jones
and the Single Family Dwelling.
Hey. Look. Found a seashell.
-Yeah, that's a rat skull.
-Oh!
Relax, there's enough droppings down here
without you making more.
Sorry. You have a sense of where we are?
-Yeah, I think that's the den.
-Oh.
Okay. So we must be under the dining room.
Uh-huh. Yep. You know,
I know you don't wanna hear this,
but it wouldn't take that much work
to turn that den into a nursery.
-Oh, why wouldn't I wanna hear it?
-'Cause Bernie said you didn't want kids.
That's not true at all.
Well, lwish she'd get pregnant.
Believe me.
l'm climbing on top of her
every chance I get.
(EXHALES)
In a loving and respectful manner.
Oh. (CLEARS THROAT)
The point is I really do want kids.
Huh.
I don't know why she's lying to you.
She's the one who doesn't want kids.
In fact, every time I bring up the subject
she's always~
Earthquake!
Oh, my God. We're gonna die.
Aftershock!
I can't believe Sheldon was gonna ask
Amy to marry him.
I know.
I also can't believe he watched what
we did on that couch and still sits on it.
Yeah.
-Hello.
-Hey, buddy, how you doing?
Better.
-Did Wil and Adam leave?
-Yeah.
Do you think they're going to
put my outburst in the documentary?
-Oh, yeah.
-Definitely.
Well, there's no point dwelling on it.
As the Vulcans say...
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
-Do you know what that means?
-No.
Are you telling the truth?
(SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
Well, this is ridiculous.
Being upset about Amy all the time
isn't accomplishing anything.
If I wanna resolve this situation
then I need to take action.
-What are you gonna do?
-l'm going to find her
and ask her to marry me.
And if she says yes we can put this
behind us and resume our relationship.
If she says no, well then she can just...
(SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
He didn't mean that.
So, I should probably explain
whyl kinda fibbed.
That would be nice.
I told my dad that you were the one
who didn't want kids
because I didn't wanna disappoint him.
But you were okay
throwing me under the bus?
Turns out, yeah,
I didn't think twice about it.
Bernie, you don't need to worry about me.
But I don't wanna see you miss out.
Raising children was the most
rewarding experience of my life.
Oh, please.
Mom did everything, all you did was
come home from work,
sit on the couch and drink beer.
How is that raising kids?
This is really a conversation
for husband and wife. (CHUCKLES)
I'm gonna go clean up, hit the road.
If your mother asks,
I was here till 10:00.
It's interesting.
Your father didn't help around the house
and Howard doesn't help either,
so in a way,
Howard's not only like your father
but he's also like the child
that you're afraid to have.
Why are you still here?
Fine, I'll leave. But it sounds like
somebody needs a fresh diaper.
All right.
ladmit...
That I don't help out a lot. (CHUCKLES)
And I need to work on that.
But if we had a kid,
it would be different.
-Why?
-Because...
When my dad left,
I promised myself that...
If I ever had a chance to be a father...
I'd always be there.
Okay, I'll think about it.
And this is an actual
"I'll think about it?"
Not like the "Can we get a motorcycle
with a sidecar?
"I'll think about it?"
-lt's an actual "I'll think about it."
-And I really believe I'd be a great dad.
-I know you would.
-(CHUCKLES)
Speaking of making babies,
what do you say I wash up
and poke around your crawlspace?
(INAUDIBLE)
Dr. Dehner feels he isn't that dangerous.
What makes you right
and a trained psychiatrist wrong?
Because she feels. I don't.
All I know is logic.
(SCOFFS) Yeah, right.
You can just shut your feelings off.
There goes television, lying to us again.
We let you raise our children
and this is the thanks we get?
Leonard, how could I have been so foolish?
To try and follow in the footsteps of a
made-up alien race with no emotions?
(EXHALES) Well...
Now instead of idolizing
fictional characters,
you can focus on the real people
who are already in your life.
Those are very
-wise words.
-Thank you.
They'd just be so much more comforting
if they came out of a television.
English - SDH