Sheldon Cooper's descent
into madness. Day two.
It's 2:25 am.
and I feel the urge to urinate.
My normal urination time is 7:10 am.
But here I am, in the middle of the night,
struggling to keep my mind sharp,
and my pajamas dry.
It's only a matter of time
before my tenuous grasp on reality fades.
Isuppose Ishould pee
while [still know what a toilet is.
(SHELDON HUMMING)
-Since when do you hum songs?
-What are you talking about?
-You were just humming.
-Are you sure?
Sometimes, when my brain
really gets moving, it makes noise.
How does your brain feel about calculating
the surface tension of the domain walls?
Let's see.
(CONTINUES HUMMING) Hey, lwas humming.
One point for Hufflepuff.
-What song is that?
-We||... Hum it again.
Is that the SpongeBob song?
No.
Whatever, can we just get back to this?
| feel like I know what song that is,
but I can't put my finger on it.
No.
It's just an eanivorm, it'll come to you.
Okay.
No.
Is this what we're doing
the rest of the night?
(SINGING) I'm surprised you have to ask
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Hello, yes, I'm hoping you can help me.
What song is this?
(SINGING) La la la la la la la
You don't know? How dare you call
yourselves a Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?
My goodness, do you sing along
to the greatest hits of Elvis Presley
with that mouth?
Well, they were no help at all.
Which is crazy since rock and roll
is all about good customer service.
Yeah, so you have a song stuck
in your head. It happens to everybody.
Yeah, well, I'm not everybody,
I have an eidetic memory.
Ishould be able to remember
what this song is, but I can't.
Something's wrong with me.
I told you if we were patient,
he'd figure it out for himself.
Oh, I was always afraid
this day would come.
This might be the first step
of my descent into madness.
Where I gradually test the limits
of public nudity.
-Public nudity?
-Yeah, that just means going barefoot.
-DAVE: Hello.
-Hi, Dave. Uh, it's Amy.
-Oh, how are you?
-I'm fine, how are you?
Terrific, and pleasantly surprised
to hear from you,
given howl acted on our last date.
Yeah, well, we both made mistakes.
You know, I took the last breadstick,
you gushed over my ex-boyfriend
like he was Leonard Nimoy
and you were my ex-boyfriend.
So, to what do I owe the pleasure?
Well, lwas wondering if you'd like
to get dinner again sometime?
Yes, please.
Uh, great.
"Let me just check my schedule," he said,
trying to seem like a man
with things on his schedule.
-How about Saturday?
-Uh...
Let me see.
Uh, Friday, farmer's market with Jay-Z.
Sunday, piano shopping with Elton John,
Saturday works.
Uh! Did you know, at the United Nations,
there's a department
for Outer Space Affairs?
Really? Why?
They exist in case we ever make contact
with an alien civilization.
Oh, boy, that's one of those jobs
that's boring, boring, boring,
then, "Oh, God! Where's the memo
with what we do now?"
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Oh, this is cool.
So, a few weeks ago I set up a fan page
on Facebook for our band and I--
Wait a second, how could you do that
without consulting me?
It's not a big deal.
Just took, like, five minutes to set up.
That's not the point.
When we created Footprints on the Moon,
we agreed that every band decision
would be mutual.
Now you're just trying
to take over the whole thing.
You know, maybe I should go solo.
But someone joined our page.
We have an actual fan.
All right, this thing's bigger than you
and me, band's back together.
So, listen to what he wrote.
"Uh, I saw you play at the
comic book store. You guys rock."
And then there's an animated smiley face
raising the roof like this...
-We did raise the roof that night.
-Yeah, we totally did.
I mean, why do rock stars do drugs
when this feels so great?
(SINGING) Why can't I recall this song?
This is taking far too long
The urge to bang my head against the wall
again and again and again
and again and again is strong
Put on some headphones.
(SINGING) No, they make my earlobes sweat
Hey, sweetie, what don't you take a break,
and do something else for a while?
There was a project
I've been thinking about starting.
-Okay, great. What is it?
-|'|| show you.
Dear crazy, future Sheldon,
you were driven mad by an earworm.
Your mind, once your most trusted asset,
is now a sack of parrots and monkeys.
So, I'm going to tell you everything
you need to know.
Uh, ﬁrst, music is dangerous,
the movie Footloose tried to warn us,
but we wouldn't listen.
Oh, wait!
No.
I would pay $1000
to watch you cut footloose.
SHELDON: This is Penny.
She is your friend.
If she offers you food, it's safe to
take it. You probably paid for it, anyway.
So, you're really going out
with Dave again?
Why not? He's actually a very nice guy.
He spent an entire date talking
about how much he loves Sheldon.
It's nothing Sheldon hasn't done before.
Dave's just a big fan of his work.
Besides, he said
he wouldn't bring it up again.
Okay, so where's he taking you?
Oh, he's coming here.
I'm actually making dinner.
-That's a big step.
-It is?
Yeah. You're inviting him into your home.
It's intimate.
It's where your underpants live.
You know what? Good.
I mean, I tried to get back together
with Sheldon, he shot me down.
Dave likes me.
Maybe intimate is what I need.
Are you sure?
You've never really been with a man.
Do you really want to start
with one that's 6'7"?
Why not?
'Cause it's like taking
your driver's test in a bus.
Maybe we should post a comment
back to our fan and thank him.
What should we write?
How about... Oh, how about,
"We might be Footprints on the Moon, but
your kind words sent us over the moon."
Someday, you're gonna make
an amazing grandma.
What do you wanna write?
Something badass. You know, like,
"Thanks for diggin' our vibe.
We'll keep rockin' if you keep rollin'."
Dude, if I was wearing a bra,
I'd throw it at your head right now.
I'll keep rockin', you don't do that.
Okay. I posted it.
So, who is this guy?
-Let's see, his name is Trent Monaco.
-Coo| name.
Yeah. He's 24. He's a DJ.
He brews his own beer.
He's got awesome tattoos.
Dude, he's got a hot girlfriend, too.
Damn, I don't know
if he's our biggest fan or I'm his.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Hey, Trentjust liked our comment.
He is so cool! No hard feelings, but
I'm throwing my hypothetical bra at him.
(SHELDON PLAYING KEYBOARD)
Oh, my God, he won't stop.
How does he keep coming up
with new ways to be annoying?
Nobody knows, that's why he's number one.
Can you please go talk to him?
Oh, come on, I take care of him
all day long. You do it for once!
Once? Who got the gum out of his hair?
What do you want, a medal?
It was your gum.
Fine.
-I love you.
-Who cares?
SHELDON: What are you doing in my room?
I~ Stop it, that's mine!
Why are you so strong?
Problem solved.
Oh!
(SHELDON PLAYING TUBA)
Oh, yeah, he got a tuba.
Dear crazy, future Sheldon,
this is a thermostat.
It controls the temperature
of the apartment.
The ideal setting is 72 degrees.
If you ﬁnd this too cold,
then put on a jacket.
A straight jacket,
'cause 72's the best and you're crazy.
Now, this is your spot.
You're very protective of it.
When anyone else tries to sit here,
you berate them relentlessly.
And it sounds mean,
but somehow, you make it adorable.
People are also delighted
by your love of pranks.
For example, Leonard has no idea
what I did to his coffee.
It wasn't replace it with Folgers
crystals, I'll tell you that much.
Hey, can we please get back to work?
This is Leonard.
He's your best friend in the world.
Just stop, this is ridiculous.
Sometimes he gets cranky,
but you can trust him with your life.
And he does more things for you
than I can even begin to list.
Thank you.
Oh, no, he's drinking it!
Look at this.
Trent is rebuilding a vintage motorcycle.
That is so cool!
Old broken things are so much better
than new things that work.
-Who's Trent?
-Oh, he's our fan.
Fan of what?
Uh, did you forget? We're in a band.
You mean, because you played one time
in the comic book store?
And at the children's hospital
until they asked us to leave.
Hey, dude, Trentjust checked in
at the coffee shop on Fair Oaks.
Really? You wanna go down there
and meet him?
Are you stalking him? That's creepy.
It's not creepy. I built the Footprints
on the Moon fan page. Trentjoined it.
After that, all I did was
check out his profile,
go back in the archive of his feed
until I found his Twitter handle.
From there it was easy
to find him on Instagram,
Snapchat and pretty much track
his every movement.
So, if you think that's creepy,
you married the wrong guy.
Maybe I should marry Trent.
Yeah. Like she could get Trent.
(CHUCKLING)
-This is delicious.
-Thank you.
Been a long time
since I had a home-cooked meal.
When you were married,
did your wife cook?
Uh, not at first, no.
But when she started cheating on me
with the French chef,
she became quite the wiz in the kitchen.
-So, a little silver lining.
-I suppose. Yeah.
Nothing takes the sting
out of a shattered life
like a properly seasoned bowl
of onion soup.
-How long have you lived here?
-Uh...
About five years. I'm actually thinking
about moving to a better place,
now that I don't need to be so close to--
-Well, you know. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
-I do.
The brilliant physicist that I now know
lives in the area. Not that I care.
Yeah. Anyway, he doesn't drive, so
I pretty much had to take him everywhere.
Had to or got to?
Sorry.
-My fault, I brought him up.
-Yeah.
Well, let's change the subject.
No more mentions of you-know-who.
That's a cool train.
Where did you get that?
(HUMMING)
This song is never going to stop.
Have you ever dealt with something
so relentlessly irritating?
That's a trick question, right?
Now, I shouldn't be surprised.
There's a rich history of brilliant minds
descending into madness.
Come on, Sheldon,
there are plenty of smart people
who don't have mental problems.
Yeah, she's right. For every Newton
who had a psychological issue,
there's an Edison who was just ajerk.
That could totally be you.
Empedocles thought he was a god
and jumped into a volcano.
You know, Pythagoras had
an irrational fear of beans.
Tesla fell madly in love with a pigeon
who he claimed loved him back.
Maybe hejust had bread in his pocket.
The list extends outside of science.
Painters like Van Gogh and Pollock.
Chess champion Bobby Fischer.
Brian Wilson of The Beach--
I remember the song! It's called Darlin'
by The Beach Boys! Thank goodness!
I'm not crazy! I don't have
to take a pigeon as my bride!
There goes our shot
at him living on the roof.
All right, there he is.
-So, should we introduce ourselves?
-No, let him spot us.
I wonder if he's listening
to our music right now.
Could you imagine?
What a cool way for us to meet.
He's playing our song
and looks up and there we are.
His favorite two-piece
acoustic sci-fi novelty rock band.
And he's all, like, "Aren't you the guys
from Footprints on the Moon..."
Ooh! What is he doing?
-I can't watch.
-It's okay. Oh, it's okay, he's done.
Why is he looking at it?
No, he's not going to eat it, is he?
Come on, Trent, you're better than--
BOTH: No!
Let's just go.
Hey, aren't you the guys from--
-Nope!
-Never heard of them!
(DARLIN' PLAYING)
I wonder why it was this particular song
that was stuck in my head.
I don't know, it's pretty catchy.
Yeah, do you even like The Beach Boys?
They have "beach" right in the name,
what do you think?
Well, now that you can focus again,
what do you say we get back
to surface tension of domain walls?
Of course, I'm already seeing
a more efficient way of taming the--
I know why the song was in my head.
-Why?
-It's about Amy.
Okay, look. I know Amy's like an old lady,
but she's not old enough to have a song
from the '60s written about her.
It's about how she made my life better.
Consider the lyrics.
She did soften your life, didn't she?
Yes! She's like
the dryer sheets of my heart!
I have to go.
Aw.
Am I like the dryer sheets of your heart?
Better. You're the lint trap of my love.
-That's an interesting tie clip.
-Oh, thanks. It's Avogadro's constant.
It's useful for calculating the number
of atoms in a substance,
or causing regret in anyone
who asks about it.
No, I think it's neat. (CHUCKLES)
-Oh!
-Sorry, sorry!
No one's ever liked the tie clip before,
so ljust lost all control. I...
No, it's okay,
and we are on a date. I'm...
I'm just a little nervous.
Well, no need to be nervous with me.
I'm just a harmless giant
from aforeign land.
You know, I'm just being silly. I...
I don't know what I'm waiting for.
-(KNOCK ON THE DOOR)
-SHELDON: Amy. Amy. Amy.
-That's Sheldon.
-You're kidding! How's my hair?
Sheldon, this isn't a good time.
I don't care. Amy, there was a song
I couldn't get out of my head.
Eventually, I realized
the song was about you,
and like that eanivorm,
I can't get you out of my heart.
So, what I'm trying to say is,
you're my heartworm.
The metaphorical kind,
not the poodle-killing kind.
What?
If I may.
I believe what he's saying,
in a charming and delightful way,
is that he loves you and wants you back.
Dave Gibbs, huge fan of your work.
Don't mind me.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you were on a date.
No, it's okay, keep going.
Amy, if you want to be my girlfriend
again, I really want to be your boyfriend.
I really want that, too.
Good.
Because I love you.
I love you, too.
(SIGHS |N RELIEF)
Kiss her, you brilliant fool!
Well...
I'll let you get back to your date.
Get back here.
Okay, then.
|'||, uh, see myself out.
Amy, thank you for dinner.
Dr. Cooper, pleasure to meet you, sir.
Uh, if, perhaps, sometime,
you have a spare moment,
I'd love to discuss physics
or shoot the breeze, as you Yanks say.
Oh! What a lovely evening!
English - SDH