Hey, so I saw a movie trailer
the other day.
How could Batman possibly fight Superman?
I mean, isn't that dumb?
Maybe he uses Kryptonite.
Well, Batman's got a lot of money,
maybe he builds a suit
that can do everything Superman can do.
No, no, no. I've seen that movie,
it's called Iron Man.
BERNADETTE: What do you do
when Batman wins?
EMILY: Well, it depends on...
What is happening?
I don't know.
But it's beautiful.
Yeah, and now Ben Affleck is Batman?
Oh, he was great in Shakespeare in Love.
Ooh, we should
watch that next girls' night.
We could do a double-feature with
the Leonardo DiCaprio Romeo and Juliet.
Oh, I love me some Leo.
And it's gone.
Oh, hello, everyone. lam happy
to report I'm feeling much better.
-Good for you.
-Yeah, yeah.
My fever is gone,
my sinuses are pressure-free,
and my mucus is as clear
as a Yosemite waterfall.
Glad to hear it.
I'll be able to return to work tomorrow.
Yay.
Well, why isn't everyone happy?
Your little ray of sunshine
is ready to beam again.
You really don't know why?
No. But I knew that
his "yay" was sarcastic.
It was not bad for a guy whose last bowel
movement sounded like rain on a roof.
Let me refresh your memory.
Penny, rub Vicks on my chest.
Sheldon, I cooked you breakfast.
I made your bed.
I checked your mouth for thrush.
You can rub your own chest.
Sure, grope every other man on the planet
but draw the line with me.
I brought you
a little care package from work.
It's our latest anti-viral and
the best decongestant we make.
I hope laughter is the best medicine,
'cause this care package is ajoke.
-Hey, she came all the way here--
-(SNEEZES)
You're gonna wanna take these with food.
Sheldon, stop being a baby
and let Emily take a look at you.
SHELDON: She's a dermatologist.
I went to medical school.
Well, in that case, try removing
the irritating patch of brown skin
standing next to you.
Okay, here you go.
Leonard, I'm dying.
You're not dying, it's just the flu.
| asked for chicken noodle, this
is chicken and stars. It's killing me.
I never did get that
chicken noodle, did I?
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
(LINE RINGING)
-Hi, Sheldon.
-Hello.
Are you feeling any better?
Physically yes, but I'm upset because
everyone's mad at me for no good reason.
Why don't you tell me what happened,
and in a gentle, loving way,
I'll explain to you why you're wrong.
Well, you know how when you're sick,
you're allowed to be cranky
and say whatever you want
and other people's feelings don't matter?
(SIGHS) Gentle and loving,
this is gonna be tricky.
I had a 101 fever.
If that's not a time to
verbally abuse my loved ones, when is?
Sheldon, when you're sick
you can be unbearable.
And that's why your friends
have been known to work late,
or sneak out to the movies,
or stay at a neurobiology conference
three days after it's ended.
You stayed in Michigan all week
to avoid being around me?
No, no, notjust that. Imean...
Detroit is beautiful when it's sleeting.
You know, I'm not the only one
who's unpleasant when they're sick.
When Penny got food poisoning,
she threw up so loudly
I could barely hear the television.
Oh, I just heard something.
Might be hail, might be gunﬁre.
Either way, I'm gonna
go take pictures. Bye!
(LAPTOP CHIMES)
-Hey, Stuart.
-Hey.
Where's Sheldon? Still sick?
No, he's fine.
We just needed a little break.
Yeah, I get that. When I brought him
his comics the other day,
he said, "Oh, great,
death is literally at my door."
He was being ajerk to everyone,
don't take it personally.
Oh, I'm on so many antidepressants,
I couldn't if I wanted to.
Ah, lwish we could do more stuff
without Sheldon.
lwish that all the time.
Usually before I
blow out birthday candles.
You know, Amy took some time off from him.
And it really improved their relationship.
Oh, okay. As long as it doesn't end
with us having coitus with him, I'm in.
We should all take a trip or something.
You know, Penny and l have been talking
about taking a weekend in Vegas.
-Maybe we should all go.
-(S|GHS)
Bernie would love that.
Oh, oh, maybe we could get one of those
party buses to take us there.
That sounds really fun.
Yeah, that sounds fun!
A party bus party don't stop! (CHUCKLES)
Oh, when I say "party" you say "bus!"
-No. No!
So, the guys and l were talking about
renting a party bus and
everyone going to Vegas.
Ooh, that could be fun.
But just to be clear, you mean a party bus
with booze and music, right?
Not like juice boxes and video games.
Yes. And Howard's birthday
was a drop-off party,
you didn't have to stay.
-Oh, I'm in. When are we going?
-This weekend.
Oh, where are we going?
Well, Vegas, but--
Ugh, Atlantic City without the taffy?
No, thank you.
Well, that's fine, 'cause actually,
you're not invited.
(STAMMERS) Well, that's hurtful.
Oh, Sheldon, you don't even like it there.
Yeah, I can consider a place
America's urinal cake
and still enjoy the occasional visit.
Not this time.
Well, fine.
Then I'll just hang out with Wolowitz.
He's coming, too.
-Well, then Raj and l--
-Nope.
Very well, Stuart.
Oh, great! Do that.
Ugh! Stuart.
Hi, Sheldon. What's new?
Our friends are jerks and
I'm mad at all of them.
Okay, Isaid, "What's new, " but sure.
Can you believe they planned a trip
to Las Vegas and didn't invite me?
Did you refuse to apologize and act like
they were stupid for being mad?
You know, I liked it better
when there was still
a little mystery left in our relationship.
Everyone tried to take care of you and
you were nothing but mean to them.
I can't believe you're not on my side.
You know, I was on your side
when someone stole your car radio.
Who else's side could you have been on?
I don't know! A music-loving hobo
with a heart of gold?
Sheldon, I understand that you're upset
because you feel left out,
but I don't know why we're even talking
about this. Just apologize to them.
Fine, if that's what it takes
to go on their dumb trip.
Maybe you could try apologizing
because you actually feel bad.
It's called empathy.
It's something you could work on.
l have empathy. Now watch.
Leonard made me soup
and l was mean to him.
Great.
Now try it as if
this isn't your ﬁrst day as a person.
Fine. Leonard made me soup
and l was mean to him.
Hey, I felt a little something.
Wait, wait, let me try again.
Leonard made me soup
and l was mean to him.
l was mean to him.
He must've felt terrible.
Oh, now | feel terrible.
Neat!
Glad I could help.
Now let me see you feel bad for lying
and staying in Detroit
longer than you needed to.
I feel so, so bad.
Hey, we're both great at this!
Leonard, get ready for an apology.
And with the added twist of an M. Night
Shyamalan movie, I'm going to mean it.
Ah, so like every other
M. Night Shyamalan movie I've seen,
you spoil it in advance.
Hey, if you didn't know Bruce Willis
was dead the whole time, that's not on me.
Okay. Here it comes. You tried
to take care of me when l was sick
and l was mean to you.
There's no excuse for that,
and I'm truly sorry.
Thank you, I appreciate that.
And I want you to know that
that is sincere. I do feel bad.
l'm notjust saying it
to be included on your trip.
I appreciate that, too.
Terrific. Now, all that's left
is for you to invite me to come,
me to ask, "Are you sure?"
You to say, "Absolutely."
And then me to bring it home with,
"How could I say no to that face."
You're still not coming.
But I apologized and I meant it.
I know that we don't play this game
very often, but you're doing it wrong.
Sheldon, I accept your apology, but you
upset a lot of people while you were sick.
I'm not in a position
to just say you can come.
Well, all right.
What if I apologize to all of them?
Fine. If you apologize to everyone
and they all say it's okay,
then yes, you can come.
Challenge accepted! Sounds like it's time
for the Sheldon Cooper Apology Tour!
Well, I hope it's as much fun as
the Sheldon Cooper Spell-Checks
Local Menus Tour.
(LAUGHING) Oh, my goodness.
Do you remember "Comes with apsparagus"?
Howard and Bernadette,
you tried to comfort me when l was ill
and I treated you terribly. I'm sorry.
Wow. (CHUCKLES) I'm impressed.
No, no, no. Wait, I'm not done.
Allow me to underscore my sentiment
with a haunting rendition of Brenda Lee's
I'm Sorry played on the pan flute.
(PLAYING PAN FLUTE)
-Apology accepted!
-Forgiven! We forgive you.
All right. That's eight hours
of practice down the drain.
And to memorialize this occasion,
here are your commemorative T-shirts.
(HOWARD READING)
(BERNADETTE READING)
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
All you did was offer
maternal care and affection,
and all you received in return
was rude and insensitive behavior.
Can this wait?
I'm afraid it can't. The trip is tomorrow
and l have more apologies to make.
Okay, fine, I accept your apology,
now get out!
Wonderful. Now would you mind
holding up this shirt while l--
Leonard!
You brought me my comic books
when I wasn't feeling well.
That, that was thoughtful and
l was insensitive. I'm sorry.
Thank you, Sheldon. I appreciate that.
And, now, I want you to know
that I mean it.
This isn't me just wanting to
go on the trip to Las Vegas.
What trip to Las Vegas?
The one everyone's taking this weekend
on the party bus.
Of course I wasn't invited.
That would be my understanding.
On a less painful subject,
what size T-shirt do you take?
Raj, you were being a good friend
and my illness was no excuse
for my behavior.
I hope that you can accept my apology.
Of course I do.
And Emily, I'm sorry for saying
dermatologists aren't real doctors.
And I'm sure you're tired of hearing that.
Do you honestly think I hear that a lot?
Well, lwould imagine
when yourjob is popping zits
and squirting Botox into old lady faces--
Okay. Okay, the point is
that we accept your apology.
Look, maybe you do.
Hejust insulted me again.
Yeah, but he doesn't mean it.
Why are you defending him?
Well, I believe I can answer that.
Uh, like me, Raj is demonstrating empathy.
Now, why don't you accept my apology,
you receive your free T-shirt...
I hope extra small is okay,
for some reason Wolowitz took a medium.
(SCOFFS)
Well, I don't accept your apology.
What are you doing?
It's called standing up for myself.
You should try it sometime.
Fine, how about this?
You're making me uncomfortable
by prolonging this ridiculous fight
and lwish you'd stop.
You want me to stop? No problem.
No, come on. No, please don't leave.
Point of clarification, are you still
going on the trip? Because if not--
Don't worry, you're good.
I caused that fight, I feel terrible.
(STAMMERS) Wait, I can do that better.
Yeah, wow, I don't know
which one I like more.
So, was the fight really bad?
Well, no. As a fight, it was excellent.
You know, she used harsh language
and slammed the door.
Although, as I say this, that might not
have been what you were asking.
You think they'll still go on the trip?
All I know is after the fight
I went to Emily's to smooth--
-They're not going on the trip.
-No.
What is wrong with you?
Look at him.
Caring about what's wrong with me.
That is some top shelf empathy.
Hey, well, we should start a club.
You went to Emily's to apologize
and when you left she was crying.
That is true. I suppose
I should apologize again.
-ALL: No!
-Stop.
Is she okay?
Yeah. I calmed her down but
she's not going to Vegas if he's going.
Wait, that's an option?
I didn't know that was an option.
Well, that is fine, because I've decided
that I won't be joining you.
I've realized that the most genuine way
to demonstrate the remorse | feel is
to let you have this weekend
to yourselves.
That's very mature of you.
Well, I've been on
a little trip myself recently.
Not to "Sin City" but to "sincere city."
Where, instead of genital warts,
the only growth you'll come back with
is personal growth.
And there's your next T-shirt.
Ooh, check out the stripper pole.
You know what that means.
That Raj will be on it
before we make it to the freeway?
You know it! (EXCLAIMING)
(HYDRAULICS HISS)
BERNADETTE: This is so cool!
PENNY: Here's some champagne.
LEONARD: Mmm-hmm.
Well, I would like to propose a toast.
To a well-deserved weekend--
-A-ha!
-(ALL SCREAM)
What are you doing?
My plan was to jump out at the state line,
but one of my nose plugs
fell into the toilet.
You couldn't give us just one weekend?
I told him this was a bad idea.
What do we do, kick them off?
If we drop them off at a fire station,
they have to take them.
No questions asked.
Before you do,
please give me one more chance
to apologize to Emily.
on, God.
Emily, as I'm sure you know,
l'm considered an odd fellow.
But what you don't know is that
while I often say the wrong thing,
in my heart, I mean well.
I think that you are
a smart and wonderful woman.
And we all think that you can
do better than Koothrappali.
You know, Sheldon--
Shh, let him finish.
So, for all the times I've offended you,
and all the times that I'll offend you
in the future, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Good. Then I'll be leaving now.
Oh, it's okay, Sheldon, come with us.
Oh, that's very kind of you,
but I'm sure you'll all have a better time
without me. Let's go, Stuart.
-But I wanna stay.
-Stuart, now!
You know, I know he's ajerk,
but I actually feel bad for him.
And now you see the problem.
(HYDRAULICS HISS)
Come on, you pain in the ass!
That's me! Bye, Stuart.
Wait!
I'm a pain in the ass, too!
-(POP SONG PLAYING)
-Are you relieved that you and Raj
were able to patch things up?
At the moment?
No, not really.
Shake it, baby.
Whoo! Work that thing!
English - SDH