So we're doing something a little
different tonight because, um....
It's not only you guys.
We have people watching
in movie theaters from around the country.
It's pretty amazing.
It's kind of unprecedented.
Okay. So how much, if anything, does
the cast know about physics?
-I know nothing.
-Nothing.
-I know a little bit.
HELBERG: I know how to pronounce it.
-Advanced physics. I can pronounce that.
PARSONS: Heh.
-I sometimes can't pronounce it. So....
-Yeah.
[GALECKI LAUGHS]
He says "psychics" and, you know,
we forgive him.
CUOCO:
I can't even spell it.
PRADY: But you sent-- When they found
the Higgs Boson, you sent me an e-mail.
-You were very excited about it.
-Me?
-You did, remember? Heh.
-Yeah. You're right.
-So you--
-Well, I read the news. ljust--
[ALL LAUGH]
I don't necessarily know
what I'm reading.
But I knew that related to our show
and that we had really struck gold.
[ALL LAUGH]
Rumor has it-- This is Chuck and Bill.
--that you guys were together.
You're friends.
You're like, "Let's make a show."
And you went through a few other things.
And then you guys went, "I know.
Physicist. That will be hilarious."
[LORRE LAUGHS]
Well, we'd all seen A Beautiful Mind,
and what a funny movie that was.
[ALL LAUGH]
There was originally talk of:
"Could that be a musical?"
LORRE: Yeah.
-lt's Chuck's thing.
No. We were going all over the place
looking for something to do together...
...and I don't even know
why you were telling me stories...
...about computer programming
in New York in the 'SDs.
And talking about the guys that he worked
with and they were fascinating.
They were deeply troubled...
...but they were fascinating...
...and we were also working
on an idea...
...about a young woman
who's going off to the big city to--
Sounds strangely
like Mary Tyler Moore.
But to start her life and there was a
moment in the room where we went:
"What if they--?"
-What if these guys met that girl?
-Met her. Yeah.
-And then we proceeded to, uh....
-But Chuck didn't wanna work--
We had talked
about computer programmers...
...and Chuck didn't want them
to be in that world.
That was a world of commerce.
Yeah. Taking them out of the money world
of the next killer app.
Just-- They immediately
became more interesting.
Did you realize that it would be way more
awesome if you put the hottest chick...
...in the world, Kaley Cuoco, in there?
[ALL LAUGH]
You know that first scene in the pilot...
...the hello scene,
it's still one of my favorite moments.
-lt's cute.
-lt's just simply them saying hello.
And they really are incapable
of saying more than hello.
They kept saying hello.
And that was the entire encounter between
Johnny and Kaley in that first moment.
PRADY: Jim.
-And Jim.
LORRE: Oh, yeah. Jim. Jim.
-"Hello." "Hello." "Hello."
Yeah. We weren't really sure where we
were going with Sheldon at that moment.
No. ljust didn't know
why we were saying hello.
LORRE:
Yeah.
Wasn't my intention.
PERRETTE: Simon, you floating in space.
First, were you actually in space?
And second of all, if not,
how did they harness that?
I'll answer the second question. I was
not in space. I hate to spoil the illusion.
l was sitting on basically, like,
a bicycle seat...
...that really--
I feel for the cyclists out there.
[AUDIENCE LAUGH]
Yet I don't feel because it really numbed me
below the waist at a certain point.
-But....
PRADY: Chafing?
Yeah. It was, heh....
And then there were just, you know,
some teamster guys almost--
It was like a seesaw.
So it's not quite-- You know,
who were lifting me and pulling me.
And then the rest of it is just....
It was the body movement
of kind of floating.
But it's not the romantic thing
that you picture.
It's like big guys with beers on the other
end of a seesaw like, "Come on."
You know, and I'm, like, trying to
figure out how to do that and--
PERRETTE: Was there an actual apparatus
or were you green screened?
No, we were in the space station.
Like, in--
PERRETTE:
A real space station?
-No, no. Sorry. In space station set. Set.
PERRETTE: No way.
PRADY: We built it.
-I know you wish I was in space.
But, yeah, it was a set and then, yeah,
theyjust did some camera tricks...
...and they took out the seesaw,
you know, with the effects and stuff...
...so that I wasn't on a seesaw
in the space station.
-Yeah, it was great.
PARSONS: Can I add in here?
First off, watching him do that...
...you know, we can talk about
the seesaw all we want.
Everything about
his anti-gravity movement...
...if that's what it's called,
was completely him.
PERRETTE: It was amazing.
-It was absolutely astounding.
PERRETTE: It really was amazing.
PRADY: Unbelievable.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
PARSONS:
And....
Hear, hear to anti-gravity physical
movement. Lot of fans in the house.
But also, it was like we were
not working with him anymore...
...because for four episodes or so,
all of his scenes were pre-shot in there.
Every time you saw Simon on the stage,
you'd go, "Oh, God, I miss you."
You know? It was like, "I wish you'd come
back and do our show again sometime."
[ALL LAUGH]
-And-- But it was rough.
HELBERG: Everybody seemed much happ--
You guys seemed happier
when I wasn't working.
We were. We were on land.
[ALL LAUGH]
Yeah. I did. I missed everybody as well.
So it was nice to touch down.
-Okay. Johnny and Kaley.
GALECKI: Hmm?
Penny finally told Leonard
that she loves him.
That happened.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Yeah. That was cute.
[ALL LAUGH]
You know, do you wanna hear
a secret about that scene?
-We only did that in one take.
GALECKI: That's true.
It was a very special take and, um....
-Right? It was one take?
-Yeah. I think so.
Now I'm like,
"Did I just think it was one take?"
-No. It was. It was one take. Yeah.
-You're right.
-The night-- Yeah, audience. It was cool.
-Yeah.
MOLARO: Do you remember what you said
to each other right after that take?
-Because I was there. I remember.
-Yes.
What? I don't.
I came out to tell you guys,
"That was beautiful.
It's never gonna be better than that.
It's one take."
And then Kaley said to Johnny:
"I don't know about you,
but we started the scene...
...and it was like the audience
went away...
...and the cameras went away
and it was just us."
-It did. It felt like we were just really in it.
-Yeah.
NAYYAR:
As opposed to the scenes with all of us.
PARSONS: Yes.
-Yes.
[ALL LAUGH]
Oh, no, no. No, no, no.
When I'm in scenes with all of you,
I still imagine no one's there.
I'm in my scene by myself. Yeah.
PERRETTE: Melissa?
RAUCH: Hmm?
Can you tell us
about, um, Bernadette's voice?
[ALL LAUGH]
That's actually my real voice.
Um, it's actually very similar to my mother's
voice except without the Jersey accent.
If Bernadette had a Jersey accent
it would be weird. She'd be like:
[IN JERSEY ACCENT]
"Micro-organisms."
[ALL LAUGHING]
[IN NORMAL VOICE] So that-- Tonally,
it's very similar to my mother's voice.
PERRETTE:
Kunal. Raj.
[ALL LAUGH]
We pet him all day long. It's so fun.
Anyway, how does it feel to explore
this relationship with Lucy?
It's great because you play
this character for, you know, six years...
...and, in my case, like,
you grow affection for that character.
Like, you really wanna see
that character succeed.
And I've grown a lot of affection
for him and I sort of care for him...
...and it's really lovely to see him
get to explore that side of himself...
...which I think has been amiss
for so long...
...because he's been seeing the growth
of his friends.
And we can joke and laugh
and, you know...
...but I think ultimately for him,
he really wants this.
And I think he's a good guy.
Like, I think he deserves it.
So it's really fun to get to play
that side of him...
...and to see him vulnerable...
...and sort of drop
that false sense of bravado...
...although he's not really dropping it.
But, I mean, you know.
So it's really wonderful
because I care for him...
...and I don't know
if he'll succeed or not...
...but it's nice for him
to get to explore that side of him.
I think it's really sweet.
Jim and Mayim, the spanking.
[CROWD LAUGH AND CHEER]
-Just go.
PARSONS: Well....
[ALL LAUGH]
The spanking was in the script
from moment one.
It was in the table read of the episode.
However, it was off camera.
And it was like this trio of ajoke
that went on.
There were three things we did
throughout the episode...
...that were supposed to be off camera
and we would pan to these...
...I guess, monkeys in your apartment.
You know, "See no evil, hear no evil,"
whatever.
And the naughty happened off camera.
Well, throughout the taping, it was like
we were dropping one monkey scene...
...and we were doing it on camera
and we were dropping another.
And by the end of the taping, it was like:
"We're gonna do this damn spanking
on camera."
[ALL LAUGH]
And it was, I would say, one of the
hardest things I've ever had to do...
...because I found it
tremendously amusing.
[ALL LAUGH]
And I was pissed, because I thought:
"Well, damn it, I would have practiced
how to control myself...
...if I'd have known all week."
But all week,
I was slapping that ass off camera.
[ALL LAUGH]
And....
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
You have no idea how game
this one is for crap like that.
I'm not kidding.
What?
It's true.
NAYYAR:
You were lying down on that couch.
It was like, "Here it comes."
I remember being in my dressing room
while you guys were shooting that...
...because it was the end,
and I didn't know there were any--
I still thought it was off camera. I'm like,
"God, what is taking so long?"
And I come down and ljust see
this big TV with him spanking her ass.
And I'm like, "What the hell happened?"
[ALL LAUGHING]
What have I been doing?
What did I miss? It was very visual.
GALECKI: They've never requested
that many takes before.
-It was a lot of takes.
BIALIK: There was some redness.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I never saw it.
I never saw it, but I did ask her after.
And ltold her. I said,
"Look, to get the sound we want--"
I said, "You let me have it, Jim."
-lt's all in the name of art.
-That's right.
LORRE: That's wonderful.
-How did the word "bazinga" originate?
Stephen Engel. Stephen was a writer
on the show, I think, in the second--?
First-- Second season, I think.
And that was Stephen's word
for "gotcha."
And he would use it
in the writer's room.
He would often use it by--
He would put together
a hollowed-out grapefruit.
MOLARO: Yes.
-And give it to me and--
MOLARO: Scotch-tape the pieces together.
-Scotch tape it.
And then I would say, "Hmm,
this looks like a lovely grapefruit to have.
I think I'll cut into it."
And lwould open it up and it would be
empty and Stephen would say, "Bazinga."
[ALL LAUGH]
And that is the level of humor
you missed out...
...not being part of a professional
comedy writer's room.
[ALL LAUGH]
LORRE: Now it's a bee.
-Yeah. Actually that's one of my questions.
Thank you for the transition, Chuck Lorre.
There's a bee named bazinga.
MOLARO: Something bazinga. Yeah.
PRADY: Euglossa bazinga.
You brought it up and now you don't
want to talk about it?
I don't know anything about bees.
PARSONS: Well, no. No, wait, l--
Well, again, I read the news and, um....
[ALL LAUGH]
Apparently this bee has been around,
obviously, for a very long time.
And ifl understood it correctly....
MOLARO:
They were having trouble classifying it.
-They had trouble--
-Because it looked like another bee.
-It looked so similar....
-They felt it was playing ajoke on them.
HELBERG:
Don't all bees look like another bee?
[ALL LAUGH]
HELBERG: What?
-Nobody asked you. Nobody asked you.
[ALL LAUGH]
HELBERG: I don't read the news.
-Yes.
So then he revealed himself.
"Bazinga. I'm a bee. Or a new bee."
PERRETTE:
He said that? The bee said that?
-In his way.
PERRETTE: That's so cool.
HELBERG: In his own way.
PRADY: His way.
[ALL LAUGH]
NAYYAR: This is one of those times when
I'm glad I don't understand English that well.
[ALL LAUGH]
There's also an asteroid
named Sheldon Cooper.
Is a.... Yes.
PERRETTE: Really? Please don't hit Earth.
-Yeah.
PARSONS: I don't know anything about that.
-You don't know?
No, I mean I knew it existed,
but I don't know why they would do that.
This is for Kunal and Simon.
What's your favorite Raj and Howard
bromance moment?
-On or off camera?
-Yeah.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I'm trying to remember. There's so many.
NAYYAR:
The first time we kissed was really cool.
[ALL LAUGH]
HELBERG: On or off?
-Off camera.
I think, for me, the best moment
was when we were doing--
Remember that device
where you kiss into one--?
GALECKI: Oh, yeah.
MOLARO: That was pretty good.
Uh, yeah. There was actually....
GALECKI: That was hard
to keep a straight face through.
I, like, transcended even
trying to keep a straight face.
I literally, I think, in the run-through,
I started crying and....
[ALL LAUGH]
And I, like, lost track
of what my job was...
...and why people wanted to watch that...
...and there was a prop guyjust like,
you know, like, just was spraying...
-...disinfectant.
-Antiseptic.
"I don't want these lips to be too germ--"
Like--
This is disgusting at its core.
So you can clean the lips all you want.
-We have an open sort of-- We like--
NAYYAR: It's not too open.
Well....
[AUDIENCE LAUGH]
I also like-- There was a moment where
we're eating cake...
...and you say something
about parking in the garage.
Parking it in the rear
of your garage or something.
GALECKI:
Or the dream you had, the tunnel.
I had a dream where I had a house
and you had a house.
And it's funny because they were
connected, and my backyard....
Your front yard was connected
to my backyard.
[ALL LAUGH]
And then I ask him,
"What do you think that means?"
[ALL LAUGH]
-And then In
-You face is like:
And then I just have to look at Kunal...
...and count down until
he starts laughing hysterically.
-Yeah, I'm the worst.
-At his own line.
[ALL LAUGH]
Jim, how did you develop
Sheldon's laugh?
I do not know. I really don't.
I don't know, but I know they won't quit.
They won't let me quit doing it.
[ALL LAUGH]
There are times
when we'll be in the writer's room...
...and we'll be pretty sure
that Jim will be able to invent something.
And we'll put in the script that--
My favorite moment was...
...when they were going to go cheer up
Leonard, I think...
...and they said, "Smile."
And what we wrote in the stage
direction was something like:
"Sheldon smiles. It's unpleasant."
[ALL LAUGH]
And we thought, you know,
he'll come up with something or he won't.
If he doesn't, we'll write something else.
Then we came down to the stage.
Well, that's the kind of direction
I really respond to.
That general--
It's when it gets specific, it sends me
to YouTube and I'm like--
What was--? There was a recent one.
Even today you wanted me to sing
something like a soul singer...
...and I thought, "Well, I don't know
what that exactly means.
I've heard soul. But do it? No."
[ALL LAUGHING]
But we also--
When we wrote theremin in for Jim...
...and he went and learned
to play the theremin.
Of course we wrote harp in for Mayim
and she went to learn to play the harp.
But the theremin is an almost
impossible instrument to play.
And then you were so upset.
"I'm not that good a theremin player,"
you'd say.
That brought me to tears. I won't lie.
I'm not exaggerating.
That one made me cry.
MOLARO: When Sheldon is playing
the theremin in the show...
...Jim is playing the theremin.
We did not go and add that in later.
-That is real.
-I don't know if it's impressive actually.
MOLARO: It's very impressive.
-l'm not sure.
Did you really eat the blueberry pies?
PARSONS: Yeah.
-That was awful.
PARSONS: I mean, we--
-That look fake to you?
PERRETTE: No, it didn't look fake.
-Yeah.
-That's what scares me. It looked real.
-That was no CGI.
When we first started, no one told me
not to try and breathe through my nose.
[ALL LAUGH]
-And I'm there-- I'm highly allergic.
-You would think it's common sense.
Sorry.
Highly allergic person. Remember my eyes
were watering for weeks after.
-I had blueberry in my eyes.
-We all hurt.
I kept them open. It was terrible.
GALECKI: I think that was more
traumatizing for Jim and l than the girls.
-None of us wanted to see that play.
-Why was it more traumatizing for you?
Well, we were just more vocal about
our complaints, maybe that was it.
-Men usually are.
-Yup. That was really unpleasant.
-That was gnarly.
-Yeah.
-We did it two days in a row.
-I know. I remember.
[ALL LAUGH]
The flash mob. Kaley.
It had just been a dream of mine
to do a flash mob.
And I said, "Guess what?
You're all doing it with me."
I had this idea for many moons,
many years, many seasons.
I thought, "Gosh that would
be so awesome."
So I kind of asked around the crew...
...if they'd be interested and they were like,
"Oh, my God, that would be so fun."
Sol kind of told the cast, like kind of--
Yeah, I did tell them we're doing this.
I said, "I wanna surprise the writers.
We'll do it in front of a live taping."
I didn't know how, but my sister happens to
be an incredible dancer and choreographer.
So I called her.
I'm like, "Okay, I have this idea.
I wanna do a flash mob
with our entire crew...
...in front of a taping in like two weeks.
Here are the songs."
I sent her six songs
because I wanted it to be really long.
And I'm like,
"You think you can put this together?"
She called me back in 30 minutes.
She goes, "I have it."
And put herself on her phone to show me.
I'm like, "You don't have it."
She did the whole thing.
She had done the whole thing.
And came the next day and our crew
took a long lunch and we learned it.
And the guys and the girls,
we all learned it and we did it.
And it was the best moment
of my whole life!
And we didn't tell anyone.
We didn't tell the writers.
It was funny,
because it was the end of a show.
So the show had wrapped,
but we all went into the living room set.
Everyone was like,
"We didn't write another scene."
You know, we're sitting in there
like ready to go.
And then the music started
and it was magic.
PERRETTE: It's pretty amazing. Yeah.
You guys were--
-It is the best thing I've ever done.
PERRETTE: You got good moves.
-Jim Parsons stood in the background.
-He didn't get a lot of time to learn it.
-He was very busy that week.
-Kaley was very kind and said:
-I said, "You gotta be in this. We gotta do--"
-"Here's the deal.
Would you please just stand there...
...and watch us...
...and when the whole thing's over,
just go, 'Bazinga.' Or not.
You say whatever you want."
And I said, "It's a deal."
-l was very grateful for my choreography.
CUOCO: And Johnny had a solo.
-Yeah.
NAYYAR: Johnny had a solo.
Johnny had a solo.
-Well, I wouldn't call it a solo.
-Nobody else spun on their butt.
GALECKI: No.
PERRETTE: It was pretty amazing.
It's really all I could contribute.
But you came to rehearsal
and you were surprised.
-The last day.
-He thought it was just ridiculous.
Kaley kept coming, saying, "Come on.
You have to come down for rehearsal."
I said, "No. No.
-No, I don't."
-"I have a life to live."
[BOTH LAUGH]
But I came down
and I saw the last rehearsal.
All of a sudden, after rolling
my eyes for two weeks, I said:
-"I really wanna be a part of this."
-Yeah. It was so fun.
NAYYAR: It was amazing--
-But I don't have time to learn...
...so I'm just gonna come in
and do a back spin...
...which I usually save for weddings.
[ALL LAUGH]
So that was my little contribution.
I didn't wanna be left out.
It was amazing watching the crew.
CUOCO: Oh, yeah.
PARSONS: Rehearse.
-White male dropping it like it's hot.
CUOCO: In the corners too.
It was so cute that night,
because it was the taping.
So if you were behind the scenes
or near craft service or walking around...
...you saw someone back there going...
PARSONS: Yes.
-...trying to memorize their moves.
PARSONS: Secretly. It was to be a surprise.
-Secretly.
Melissa and l were practicing
in my room.
I kept saying, "Melissa, I don't know it.
Please come and show me."
It's really actually touching
for me to watch it.
It's such a testament
to how much we all...
...the crew included,
just love spending time together.
I mean in season six, to give your
lunches up to stay later after rehearsal...
...for dance rehearsal for a flash mob.
You would think after six years,
you'd go, "I'm out of here.
-l've got family members."
CUOCO: Everyone stayed, by the way.
Everyone on that crew.
It was just amazing.
That's evidence
of how incredible our work place is.
CUOCO: And a little tidbit,
because I love my sister.
After the flash mob,
Chuck loved her too...
...and she ended up choreographing
for Two and a Half Men...
-...that dance number that they did.
-Yeah. Well, she killed it.
-It was like 50 dancers and she just--
PERRETTE: She's a cool girl.
CUOCO: It was awesome.
-She's amazing.
PERRETTE: Very cool.
-Amazingly talented.
-She was in the clips that we played earlier.
CUOCO: Yup.
-She's the girl who says yes...
CUOCO: The Valentine's Day episode.
...to the wedding proposal...
-...is Kaley's sister Bri.
CUOCO: Yeah.
GALECKI: Oh, yeah.
CUOCO: They've been very good to her.
I know, isn't that cute?
The bitch stole my man.
[ALL LAUGHING]
How do you all keep straight faces when
you're shooting really, really funny scenes?
-I mean--
CUOCO: We don't. Well, he doesn't.
HELBERG: Kunal doesn't.
CUOCO: No. But it's so cute.
-I love that about you.
-I think that my cast mates are very funny.
CUOCO: You're laughing at your own jokes.
GALECKI: No, your own jokes crack you up.
No. But I think it's charming
and very cute when you laugh.
-Thank you.
-Sometimes it is contagious to yourself.
-Yeah.
-It just-- It catches on.
If you could have any item from the set
in your own home, what would it be?
-I think about this a lot. It makes me sad.
PARSONS: You do?
No. I think of like, you know,
at the end of a show and, like, you know--
-What am I gonna steal?
-Yeah. Yeah.
[ALL LAUGH]
Gonna steal. That's amazing.
You guys had the sword from the
Game of Thrones in the guys' apartment.
GALECKI:
Where would you put that?
Not that computer I carry.
That is the heaviest laptop.
-It is.
-Yeah.
The curse words that have flied--
Flew out of my mouth during taping...
...when l have to get that damn thing
in a bag.
So that's what I'm not taking.
[ALL LAUGHING]
You know, when I'm kind of pacing around
and running my lines...
...I found myself in front of the refrigerator
in our apartment set staring...
...at this takeout menu of Thai food.
I don't know-- And I catch myself
staring at it for like 20 minutes...
...while I run my lines thatl had.
-lt's the most inane food in the world.
BIALIK: It's got crazy typos.
It's like candied, curry Indian shrimp.
We're gonna fight for that takeout menu.
PARSONS:
Well, that would be nice.
You know, something matted
and framed and hang that up.
-That sword, no.
GALECKI: Yeah, I don't want the sword.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
How much Klingon did you speak
before The Big Bang Theory?
I'd never even heard it spoken before
The Big Bang Theory. I've learned so much.
Jim is Klingon in the scene and Jim said:
"Well, I hope there isn't a lot. I mean,
I know a little. I can ask for directions.
I can get a room in a hotel.
But I hope it's not a lot."
What about the Star Trek makeup
when you guys got lost in the car?
That was-- Wow.
GALECKI: The makeup?
-Kunal's was the hardest.
It was long. I got to set at 5 a.m.,
and we finished--
-I took it off at like 8 p.m., I think.
-That doesn't sound as bad...
-...as we thought it might.
NAYYAR: Yeah, I know.
CUOCO:
Everyone's like:
The thing is I couldn't talk
because I had the mustache--
GALECKI: It was fantastic.
CUOCO: Yeah.
So if you watch the episode....
-l'm talking like this the whole episode--
HELBERG: Isn't that how you talk?
-I thought that's how you talked.
-Well, I bobble my head a little more.
PRADY:
Thought that's how he talked.
That was the hardest thing,
is the mustache was tickling my....
HELBERG: He said it. Mustache.
PARSONS: Mustache.
This was all a ploy
to get him to say "mustache."
- Mustache.
- Ah.
lt'sjust like being back home.
Where did the "Soft Kitty, Warm Kitty"
song originate?
This is from my daughter's preschool
in Sherman Oaks.
And they used to sing "Soft Kitty"
and I'd never heard it before...
...and I guess it was from Australia
and one of the teachers had heard it there.
GALECKI: But then Bill came down
to the stage with a recorder...
-...to play us the melody.
PARSONS: Oh, my God. He's right.
I had wiped that out of my head, Johnny.
We're all staring
at him playing the recorder...
...and he stopped and looked
at us and said:
"If any of you wondered
why I'm the writer on a nerd show...
...this might answer your question."
How about the Smurf makeup?
I'm curious. How about the Smurfs?
GALECKI: That was so cool.
RAUCH: I'm still wiping it off.
-Like, I'm still finding it in places.
-That was quite an ordeal.
You had a hilarious moment.
We both had to sit next to each other.
There's just a point where you just start
to, like, go into kind of a meditative state...
...because you're just sitting there.
It's hour two...
...and it's just a guyjust rubbing
as hard as he can...
...and you're already blue and you don't
know how much bluer you can get.
[ALL LAUGHING]
But they're convinced it's gonna be
another hour and a half of blueness.
And then they had to take it off and l was
sitting next to Melissa and I finished first.
-But then you later realized....
-Oh, all right.
-We're gonna get intimate.
-Maybe I shouldn't.
Keep it here and in the movie theaters.
-And online and it'll follow me.
HELBERG: I'm sorry.
Okay, so they're taking it off
and it was hours of getting this stuff off...
...and it was getting late into the night,
and l have really sensitive skin.
So they're like packing me
with like hot towels, and it's--
I'm starting to fall asleep
and it's two dudes...
...and then my regular makeup artist,
who went out of the trailer, heh...
...to get some more hot towels.
And I'm in a body suit...
...underneath this dress and they're like:
"Could you just lift up your legs...
...to get the rest of the makeup
out from under your legs?"
Sol lift my legs up and close my eyes
and I hear one of the guys go: "Ha, ha."
And I just thought, "Oh, they're just
telling jokes back and forth...
-...to each other."
HELBERG: Makeup humor.
And then I look in the mirror and l was like,
"What's that? What is that?"
And I was like, "Dear, Lord Jesus!
That's my business!"
[ALL LAUGHING]
I, uh, I had totally exposed myself.
And then I put my legs down and then just
looked at them and said, "Long night."
[ALL LAUGHING]
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING
AND CHEERING]
I haven't actually been to y'all's set,
but that's just one little thing of stairs...
...you have to keep going around
and around in. Right?
PARSONS: Just one.
NAYYAR: Yeah.
It's disgusting, because Johnny likes
to chew gum before the scenes...
...and he sticks the gum--
When you go down there's nothing
except just a wooden wall.
And there's nothing on the wall
but a wall of Johnny's gum for six years.
RAUCH:
How do you know that was Johnny?
And I swear to God, there was one pecan,
that's been lying on the floor for six years.
HELBERG:
Yeah.
[ALL LAUGHING]
HELBERG: It's growing other pecans though.
-Exactly.
They don't want to kill it.
I think what's sad is how easy
it was to get up those stairs season one.
It's not so easy anymore. Sometimes
we're like, "God, is anyone else winded?
I'm dying."
Didn't think about that a few years ago.
Before this night ends, we have
to say thank you to everyone here.
This is so thrilling for us that you
care enough to go out and do this.
Thank you.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING]
Whoo!
Ourtime is up.
And you guys have been so amazing.
GALECKI: Thank you all.
PERRETTE: Such a great audience.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.