Have you guys seen
this feature that lets you talk to Siri
without pressing any buttons?
No, how does it work?
You just say,
"Hey, Siri, what time is it?"
SIRI: The time is 6:37 p.m.
So now anyone can control your phone?
Hey, Siri, show me pictures
of naked grandma butts!
-Nice try, it only recognizes my voice.
-Oh, cool.
(MIMICS RAJ) Hey, Siri, show me
pictures of naked grandma butts!
(SCOFFS) I don't sound like that.
SIRI: Here are some images
of naked grandma butts.
Hey! Good news, everybody.
Now that I'm no longer with Amy,
I have an extra ticket
to the annual Thanksgiving lunch buffet
at the aquarium cafeteria.
Who wants it?
You realize you won't be going alone.
I'll be there the whole time.
Providing fish and pilgrim facts.
Can you people hear me?
Well, we're having everyone over.
-Yeah, Leonard and l are cooking all day.
-Otherwise, we'd love to.
-But we can't. Mmm-hmm.
-Poor us.
And Raj and l are volunteering at the soup
kitchen feeding food to the homeless.
Oh, Howard, what about you?
Oh, I can't, I'm going
to the soup kitchen, too.
You said that sounded
like the worst thing ever.
If you can't support me when I'm lying,
why are we married?
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Hi, Sheldon, what's up?
Well, I'm calling because
Thanksgiving is coming up
and I wanted to offer you
the aquarium tickets.
No one can go with you?
No, they'd rather spend the holiday
with each other
than find out if this
is the year I finally touch a starfish.
Anyway, I wouldn't want the tickets
to go to waste,
so take whomever you'd like.
Oh?
Okay, thank you.
And feel free to tell your guest
that the Myanmar catfish
is also known as the pilgrim fish.
In case the turkey's dry
and you need something juicy.
Sheldon, I can tell you want to go,
so if you'd be comfortable with it,
maybe we could go as friends.
You don't think that will be awkward?
Well, it is Thanksgiving
in an aquarium cafeteria,
so I'm gonna go out
on a limb here and say yes.
But if you mean between us,
I think it'll be ﬁne.
Very well, then.
I'll see you on Thanksgiving morning.
See you then.
Oh, forget what I said
about the Myanmar catfish.
My list of marine-themed
pilgrim facts is pretty short.
Did you know they served shellﬁsh
and eel at the ﬁrst Thanksgiving?
And there goes my list.
So, how does this work?
The soup kitchen manager assigns
the jobs and the shifts are six hours.
-(BUZZ|NG)
-Six hours?
(SIGHS) I don't wanna
complain for that long.
Do you ever do anything for anyone else?
I happen to be a giving
and generous lover.
Are you and | close
enough for me to say that's creepy?
We are and I believe the word you're
looking for is... (GROANS |N DISGUST)
-Uh, can I help you?
-Hi, we'd like to volunteer.
Oh, I appreciate you guys coming down,
but we already have enough people.
Any other day, please, come back.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, okay.
Wipe that smug smile off your face.
Maybe I'm happy that so many people
turned up to help the less fortunate.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you and | close enough for me to say--
That he's an ass? He beat you to it.
Uh, l was wrong.
A large group had to cancel.
Oh, great, we'd love to help!
Wipe that smug smile off your face.
(CHUCKLES) I can't!
Look at us! Our first Thanksgiving
as husband and wife.
-I know, lfeel so grown up.
-Uh, sweetie, you are grown up.
Really? How many grown-ups do you know
who have Mr. Spock oven mitts?
Hey, the recipes are on my iPad.
Will you pull 'em up?
-Yep. What's the code?
-My birthday.
It's not working.
It's just four digits.
The month and day.
Nope.
Let me see.
Yeah. There.
What number were you putting in?
Uh...
-You don't know my birthday, do you?
-Yes, I do.
-When is it?
-May.
May what?
I'm not gonna say your password out loud,
that is not secure.
You don't know
your own husband's birthday!
-You don't know everything about me.
-Your birthday is December second.
You grew up on Perkin Street.
The last four digits of your social
are seven-six-two-one.
And the odds of me letting
you forget this are zero! (CHUCKLES)
Oh, look at us, our last Thanksgiving
as husband and wife.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Ready for the aquarium?
-I am.
And in an effort to reduce awkwardness
as we learn how to function as friends,
I printed out a list of safe topics
for polite conversation.
If that makes you more comfortable.
If there were a list of things
that make me more comfortable,
lists would be on the top of that list.
Okay, now, oh, since last we spoke,
have you acquired any pets?
No. You?
No.
Um, since last we spoke,
have you planned or gone on any vacations?
I might go visit my aunt next week.
-Your aunt in Modesto?
-No. The one in Bakersfield.
Bakersfield, | see.
Where has this list been all my life?
We're gonna have you washing dishes.
Uh, aprons and rubber gloves are here.
Just scrape, wash and stack.
If you need me, I'll be around.
So we don't even get to be
up front where the action is?
What difference does it make?
I don't know. I was hoping some poor kid
would come up to me and say,
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
"Please, sir. lwant some more."
You're in a soup kitchen,
not a production of Oliver!
(IN NORMAL ACCENT)
It's not like I'm expecting them to sing.
Then the next day was 73 degrees,
then the day after that was 72,
and then it was 72 again,
then it was 74,
and that brings us to today, at...
l'd wear shorts if I had a pair, 78.
Are we done discussing the weather?
I don't know if I'd call it "discussing,"
you kind of sat back
and let me do all the work.
Let's see what's next on the list. Oh!
Uh, do you whittle,
and if so what kind of knife do you--
Sheldon!
We've known each other a long time.
We are perfectly capable
of having a conversation
without relying
on a list off the Internet.
All right, what should we talk about?
I don't know, just ask me
whatever comes to mind.
Very well.
I know you've been seeing other men.
Have you had coitus with any of them?
Man, I walked right into that one.
Next, we need a teaspoon of pepper,
which I believe was also the name
of your childhood dog.
Fine, you think you know so much?
-Who's my favorite Spice Girl?
-Baby.
-Who's my favorite member of NSYNC?
-Justin.
-Who's my favorite Backstreet Boy?
-(SCOFFS) Nice try, NSYNC forever.
Damn it!
(CHUCKLES) Face it, you can't stump me.
lam the king of husbands.
I know you don't like that lingerie
that I got you on Valentine's Day,
I know you hate the word "moist,"
I know you don't--
Hang on, wait, wait.
Why don't I like the lingerie you got me?
Because it's orange and you think
it makes you look like a slutty carrot.
Interesting. I never told you that.
-Sure, you did.
-No, I never told anyone that.
But I did write it in myjournal.
(IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE) What?
I didn't know you had ajournal.
I also know your voice
gets higher when you're lying.
(IN LOW-PITCHED VOICE) No, it doesn't.
-Huh, this reminds me of high school.
-You worked in a restaurant?
No, lwas in India.
It was humid and smelled funny.
All right, lthink I'm getting
into a groove here. This isn't so bad.
Yeah, only five hours
and 40 minutes to go.
We've only been doing this 20 minutes?
You know, I read that washing dishes
can be an excellent form of meditation.
The key is that while washing the dishes,
one should only be "washing the dishes."
Just because you have that accent
doesn't mean what you say isn't stupid.
No, seriously,
it's about being present in the moment.
Focusing on the feeling of the warm water.
The smell of the detergent,
the sound of the dishes squeaking
and following your own breath.
It's about simply being.
Huh? (CHUCKLES)
Okay, I'll try it.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
-I need three people out front.
-|'|| do it!
RAJ: Me!
EMILY: Right here!
No fair, I was meditating!
Oh, come on, don't be mad.
It was a long time ago
and it was an accident.
How can reading myjournal be an accident?
I didn't even know what it was. I saw it
on your nightstand, I picked it up.
Well, when you realized what it was,
why didn't you stop?
(SCOFFS) You know me,
I'm a big ol' bookworm.
-Let's just finish cooking.
-(STUTTER|NG)
Let me make this up to you.
Sometimes, I keep an onlinejournal.
I want you to read something that I wrote.
Really, I'm fine.
Uh, okay, then I'll just read it to you.
It's from the day that we first met.
(CLEARS THROAT)
-"Beauty, thy name is Penny--"
-Oh, God, stop.
I don't want you to read
something you think'll just butter me up.
I wanna hear
the most recent thing you wrote.
Fine.
(HUMMING AWKWARDLY)
"Penny's beauty, like our love,
grows more with each passing day."
Does it really say that?
Why would I lie?
"OMG, OMG, We're so close to
the new Star Wars. I can't take it. Gah."
"Gah"?
Well you didn't read it right.
The new Star Wars is coming, gah!
l'm sensing things have gotten awkward.
No, it's okay.
If we're friends,
we should be able to talk about anything.
All right.
So, you had some questions
about me seeing other people.
-Just a few.
-Go ahead.
How many dates have you been on?
Who were they with?
Where did you go? Where did you meet them?
Did you sleep with them?
And how much longer to the aquarium?
I'm getting kind of hungry.
Let's see... (SIGHS)
I've been on six dates
with three different people.
It was either for coffee or dinner.
One I met at a bookstore
and two I met online.
I haven't slept with anyone,
the aquarium is 40 minutes away,
and there's a baggie of Cheerios for you
in the glove compartment.
Is that regular or Honey Nut?
I mixed them.
You mixed them. No wonder gentleman
callers are pounding down your door.
Do you have any questions for me?
Just one.
Are you doing okay?
I am.
Good.
(STUTTERS) I want you to be happy.
I believe you.
l'd believe you more if you threw
a few Apple Jacks in here.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
You gotta be kidding me.
Sorry?
-(SHUDDER|NG) You're Elon Musk.
-I am.
(STUTTERING) What are you doing here?
l'm washing dishes.
Well, l was on the turkey line,
but I got demoted
for being too generous with the gravy.
Oh, man... (CHUCKLING)
What an honor to meet you.
(GASPS) I'm such a fan of Tesla
and SpaceX. All your companies.
-Howard Wolowitz, Caltech.
-Nice to meet you, Howard.
Feels great to come down here
and help the less fortunate, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Nothing better than helping people.
Which is something I realized
when lwas viewing Earth
from the deck
of the International Space Station
where I spent two months
as a payload specialist,
ajob l was qualified for
because I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
And I thought I ladled the gravy on thick.
Sorry. lt'sjust... You're you...
(CHUCKLES)
And I really want you to adopt me.
Well, you're here on Thanksgiving,
so you're probably a good person.
Oh, I made my wife come down, too.
You think you might ever
get back out to space?
Is that ajob offer?
'Cause I really wanna go to Mars.
Assuming I can bring my wife.
She hardly takes up any room.
She's basically a carry-on.
Well, we're not quite there yet,
but we're always looking for engineers.
So let me give you my email,
we can stay in touch.
Thank you.
(HOWARD GASPS)
Oh, look.
Someone hardly touched their pumpkin pie.
Want to share it with me?
A partially eaten piece of pumpkin pie
from a homeless shelter?
With Elon Musk? You bet I do!
You know, for a Thanksgiving buffet in an
aquarium cafeteria, that was really bad.
You're just upset
'cause they ran out of pilgrim hats.
They gave one to that baby,
he wasn't even awake.
Well, it wouldn't be a holiday
without you being mad at a baby.
Oh, would you care to play
an ocean-themed game | invented?
-Sure, what is it?
-lt's called Food, Friend, Fight.
One of us chooses three aquatic creatures
and the other one must decide
which he would eat, befriend, or battle.
So it's like Kiss, Marry, Kill.
What is that?
It's a game where
you're given three people
and you choose
which one you'd kiss, marry, or kill.
Well, my game is better because instead
of marrying someone, you get to eat them.
Let's just play.
I'll start you off easy.
Electric eel, puffer fish, shrimp.
Hmm.
Well, I wouldn't fight the eel
because I know it can generate
enough current to kill a horse.
So I'd eat the eel, fight the shrimp,
and befriend the puffer fish
because it would be nice to have
company on those days | feel bloated.
-Very well done.
-Thank you.
Okay, your turn.
Um... Seal, hagfish...
SpongeBob SquarePants.
Well, I'd befriend SpongeBob, but he's not
real, so I can't do that, can I?
But you can pal around with a hagfish?
Hey, let's not pull at that thread.
Okay, I'll fight SpongeBob.
Because he's so friendly,
we'll just end up tickling each other.
Um, l'll befriend the seal
because he's trainable,
which was the problem I'm having
with my current friends.
Which means I'll have to eat the hagfish.
Isn't that gross?
A hagfish can produce enough mucus
to fill a bucket in a minute.
I know. It makes its own gravy,
it'll slide right down.
I miss this.
How can you miss a game
you've never played before, silly?
(AMY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Guess sometimes I'm silly.
Hey, where'd you go?
I can't tell if the turkey's done.
LEONARD: Be right there.
-Hi, lover.
-(GASPS)
What are you doing?
I'm sorry about the journal
and I want to make it up to you,
so I'm going to let you post
a shame photo of me on Facebook.
lam not putting that on the Internet!
I don't want people to see this.
I don't want to see it!
(CHUCKLES) You don't want people
to see what, huh? A little bit of this?
Oh...
Some of this?
And since it's Thanksgiving,
an extra helping of this.
Happy Thanks--
I'm glad you had a nice time with Amy.
Uh-- Me, too. It's comforting to know that
she and l are able to function as friends.
Well, I've never been friends
with any of my exes.
Oh, I'm sure you and Leonard
will be able to pull it off.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh, it's my friend Amy.
-Hello.
-Hi, Sheldon
I'm just driving home from my mother's.
-Did you have a nice time?
-I did.
Um...
Listen, I really enjoyed
spending this morning with you.
Oh, well, I can't take all the credit.
It was pretty funny when that one
anchovy started going the wrong way.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
It was. Uh, listen...
lwas thinking that, um, maybe I'm ready
to be your girlfriend again.
Oh?
I thought we were just friends.
We are. But I was hoping, maybe--
Amy, I excel at many things,
but getting over you wasn't one of them.
I think I need to just be your friend.
Okay. I understand.
SHELDON: Good.
Oh, I watched a video
of the hagﬁsh producing mucus,
so I'm going to change
my answer and eat SpongeBob.
(SHAKILY) Okay, sure.
English - SDH