I recently read that during World War II...
...Joseph Stalin had a research program
to create super soldiers...
...by having women impregnated
by gorillas.
What a sick use of science.
Hey, as long as the baby's healthy.
I wonder if Stalin considered
any other animals.
Hippos are the deadliest creature.
A half-human, half-hippo soldier
would be pretty badass.
Yes, but when they're hungry, hungry,
you can stop them with marbles.
Yeah, the correct animal
for interspecies super soldier is koala.
You would wind up with an army so cute,
it couldn't be attacked.
But half-man, half-owl can fly--
The answer is cuddly soldiers
with big flat noses. Moving on.
-So, Penny, when's the newjob start?
-Next Monday.
Did you look over the materials I gave you?
-Uh, not yet, but I will.
-Great. When?
I said I'll get to it.
I'm sensing awkwardness. Am I right?
Yes.
Swish.
I don't want to be pushy, but you've
never done pharmaceutical sales before.
You could use this time to get a head start.
The first few weeks will be training.
They'll tell me everything I need to know.
Imagine how impressed they'd be if you
showed up familiar with the material.
So, what, you want me
to be like a teacher's pet?
Couldn't hurt.
I don't know. Who here has ever been hurt
because they were the teacher's pet?
It's like the rest of the class
wanted Ms. McDonald to forget the quiz.
Mrs. Davis...
-...guess who.
-Dr. Cooper.
That's right. Good job.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hello. Uh....
You wanted to see me?
-Yes, welcome back.
-Thank you.
I assume you'd like to reopen
our dialogue...
...about the university forcing me
to continue with string theory?
You mean the dialogue that went,
"Please. No. Please. No. Please. No."?
That's the one.
I believe you went last, so please?
Dr. Cooper, while you were away...
...we came up with a solution that would
allow you to change your field of study.
Wow.
Pouting and running away actually worked.
I must say that may not be a lesson
you want to reinforce with me.
So, um, what is the solution?
Currently, you're being paid under a grant
to specifically research string theory.
If we promote you to junior professor,
you'll be able to choose...
...whatever field of research you'd like.
But if I'm a professor...
-...then I'll have to teach a class.
-That is correct.
So your solution is to promote me...
...and pay me more money...
...so that I can impart my knowledge
to the next generation of scientists?
Yes.
You people are sick.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey, ready to go to lunch?
Give me a minute. I'm stimulating
the pleasure cells of this starfish.
-I need to turn it off.
-What if you don't?
l have to sit through lunch knowing this
starfish is having a better day than lam.
ls Bernadette meeting us at the restaurant?
-No, actually, I didn't invite her.
-How come?
Ever since she helped me get this job,
she won't stop bugging me.
Well, I think she just wants you to do well
and she's worried you won't...
...because you were just
a stunningly poor waitress.
That is not true.
I'm still waiting on my mini corn dogs
from two years ago.
I told you they'll be right out.
Okay, so no Bernadette.
Well, you saw her the other night.
Am I wrong?
No, ljust--
I feel kind of uncomfortable talking
about her like this.
Usually when someone's
being talked about behind their back...
...it's me and it's right in front of my face.
-l'm sorry. ljust need a little break from her.
-I understand.
You know...
...there is some research that indicates...
...that sharing negative attitudes
about a third party...
...can be a powerful bonding force
between two friends.
-So, what are you saying?
-l'm saying, in the spirit of science...
...what is that little skank's problem?
So I've been trying to come up with
a cute couple's nickname for me and Emily.
What do you like better? Emipali?
Or Kooth rapemily?
Why is it your last name
and her first name?
Well, her last name is Sweeney, and
something just didn't seem right about...
...Kooth rapeeney.
Hey, how'd it go with Human Resources?
Awful. They're allowing me
to move on from string theory...
...but they made me ajunior professor
and are requiring me to teach a class.
I don't understand.
Why is it bad you have to teach?
What a stupid question.
The kids are gonna love him.
I can't believe I have to waste my time
babysitting a bunch of grad students...
...who probably think dark matter
is what's in their diapers.
This might not be that bad.
-You like telling people they're wrong.
-Wrong.
Just because I enjoyed that one
doesn't mean I always do.
You enjoy giving people grades.
A valid point, but unoriginal. B-minus.
And you love the sound of your own voice.
Well, of course I do. Listen to it.
It's like an earful of melted caramel.
Most importantly, this will let you
move on and study dark matter.
[SIGHS]
It is true that many of my heroes
have taken students under their wings.
Feynman. Einstein. Professor X.
Humorously, in the case of Professor X...
...some of his students actually had wings.
That's rich. Heh-heh.
I'll use that one to lighten the mood
after my entire class fails the midterm.
Measuring starfish serotonin levels...
...in response to 1.2 molar stimulation
of pleasure cells.
You like that, don't you?
That's right, say my name.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
-Hey.
-Hey, what's going on?
Not much. You wanna get a drink later?
Just the two of us?
-No Penny?
-Not tonight. I'm a little frustrated with her.
Because you got her the job, and she
should be working harder to prepare?
So it's not just me. You see it too.
I do. I see it.
It's driving me crazy.
Just this afternoon,
I saw an Instagram that instead of studying...
...she went out to lunch
and got a manicure.
That's outrageous.
-I know.
-If she doesn't do well...
...this could reflect poorly on you.
Exactly. Does she not realize it?
Or does she not care?
I don't know.
The important thing is, I am here for you...
...so we can mutually disparage
this unpleasing third party.
Hey, we just wanted to see how your class
was going. Where is everybody?
There is no class.
Did you send everyone
to the principal's office already?
No one signed up.
Well, that's not your fault.
I called the department secretary
to see what happened.
Apparently, I have a reputation
for being obnoxious.
[HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
What?
Hey, Sheldon, I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
Now I can devote all my time to dark matter.
-Oh, you bought cookies for everyone?
-Oh, yes.
Fig Newtons. l was going to ask them...
...which scientist both helped
to develop calculus...
...and had a famous cookie named after him.
Then after someone said Newton,
l was going to tell them they're wrong.
The cookies are named
after a town in Massachusetts.
And then I'd throw the cookies away.
Hey, what if I took your class?
Why would you do that?
-Why would you do that?
-What is wrong with you?
I've been thinking about getting my
doctorate, and he wants to teach. Why not?
Oh. Howard, I appreciate the gesture.
But this is a graduate-level physics class.
I don't think you'd understand
a single thing I was talking about.
Ask, "Why not?" again. I've got an answer.
Sheldon, I'm more than smart enough
to take your class.
[CHUCKLING]
No.
Yes.
How would you determine the ground state
of a quantum system with no exact solution?
Guess a wave function, vary its parameters
until I found the lowest energy solution.
Hmm.
Do you know how to integrate X squared
times E to the minus X without looking it up?
I'd use Feynman's trick,
differentiate under the integral sign.
Okay.
SHELDON:
Uh....
What is the correct interpretation
of quantum mechanics?
Every interpretation gives the same answer
to every measurement. They're all correct.
You believe in the many worlds
interpretation, so I'll say that.
Now do you think I'm smart enough?
Oh, come on. You might have gone
to school for a couple more years than me.
But guess what,
engineers are just as smart as physicists.
Ah! You take that back.
So after drinks with Bernadette, I get home,
and Penny calls to complain about her.
And while I'm taking to Penny,
I get a text from Bernadette.
I am trying to prepare my lesson plan
for Howard.
Why are you telling me this?
Because it's taken 15 years,
but high school is finally awesome.
I love them both...
...but I'm in the center now,
and I love that even more.
Amy, please.
lam trying to figure out a way...
...to intellectually emasculate
a dear friend of mine.
-But I'm just--
-Not now.
You better watch that attitude, buddy.
You're dating the popular girl now.
[DOOR OPENS]
You're up late.
I'm working on my lesson plan
for Wolowitz.
He is going to be so lost.
Look at this section over here.
Even I don't really understand it.
Sheldon, why are you doing this?
I'm a teacher, Leonard. It's myjob.
No, why are you going to so much trouble
to prove that you're smarter than Wolowitz?
Oh, it's no trouble. It's actually a pleasure.
Wanna know what I think?
I think the idea that someone could be
as smart as you or even smarter...
...scares the pants off you,
and you can't deal with it.
Interesting point.
But you're suggesting that l have emotional
issues below my consciousness...
...which drive my behavior.
Thus causing me to lash out
at anything or anyone...
...that threatens my intellectual superiority.
Might be something to think about.
-Leonard.
-Yeah.
Howard's allergic to peanuts.
How can I use that against him?
Hey.
Okay, now that everyone's here,
we can begin.
Before we do, I just talked to Leonard.
And, heh, if you're gonna spend
all your time trying to belittle me...
...by making this class unnecessarily hard,
then I'm out.
If you're interested in making
a sincere effort to be a good teacher...
...then I'm willing to give this a shot.
I suppose that's a fair request.
There's no reason we both can't benefit
from this experience.
-Okay.
Well, then, first things first.
Are you familiar
with the Brachistochrone Problem?
-I am.
-Good.
And how it relates
to the calculus of variations?
-lt's an inverted cycloid.
-Wonderful.
-Now what about Euler-Lagrange theorems?
-That's where I'm a little fuzzy.
Ha! I knew it. All right. Now.
We have a lot of information
to cover before your first test.
Which, by the way, is in eight minutes.
The good news is I'm grading on a curve,
so you're pretty much guaranteed a C.
[SINGING]
All I do is win, win, win, no matter what
What are you doing?
Everybody's hands go up, up
And they stay there
-What are you doing?
-If you're gonna be a crappy teacher...
...then I'm gonna be a crappy student.
Ungh, ungh, Ludacris going in on the verse
'Cause I never been defeated and I--
Stop it.
This is a classroom.
This is not American Bandstand.
Okay, now where was I?
Let's see. Oh, yes, over here.
What are you doing now?
I'm making a straw.
-Why?
-So I can shoot you with a spitball.
You're not going to do that,
and I'll tell you why.
This is an institution of higher learning.
I am your professor, and you're going
to treat me with the prop---
[GAGS]
You shot your spit in my mouth.
Is that gonna be on the test?
Because I don't think I can do that again.
Hey, girlfriend. Can I get a "what what"?
What?
Close enough. Um....
lwasjust calling
to see what you were up to.
Thought maybe we could hit up Color Me
Mine. Maybe sneak in some pinot gris?
Oh, thanks, but I'm gonna stay in
and go over the stuff Bernadette gave me.
Oh.
Oh, I hear you.
Try and get that nag off your back, right?
I mean, you're not a bicycle.
Why she riding you like that?
I think she was just trying to help.
Plus, I really want to do well at this job.
Okay, good luck, and call me later.
You know, if you decide
she's a bitch or something.
Hey, girlfriend.
-Hey, Amy.
-Tonight. You. Me. Color Me Mine.
Maybe we sneak in some pinot.
Make it Color Me Wine.
That sounds fun, but I promised Penny
I'd come by and help her study.
Well, good luck getting her to do that. She's
probably out getting another manicure.
You remember when she did that?
You remember?
l was probably being too hard on her.
We talked. We're good.
Oh, great. I'm happy for you guys.
When the two of you aren't getting along,
it puts me in a really weird position.
Don't worry. Everything's back to normal.
You mean like where she's nice
to your face? Okay, got it. Bye.
Hey, boyfriend.
Can't talk. Spitball. Probably gonna die.
[GURGLING]
-Well?
-Sheldon, I promise...
...your uvula does not have an STD.
Are you sure?
It doesn't feel as innocent as it used to.
You reported me to Human Resources?
You violated the sanctity of my mouth.
Well, I dropped your class,
so I hope you're happy.
I told you, you weren't smart enough
to take it.
I'm smart enough. Asking me about a topic
I'm not familiar with doesn't prove anything.
I could do the same to you.
-Try me.
-Okay.
You enjoy making fun
of engineering so much.
How do you quantify the strength
of materials?
Young's modulus.
-Is that right?
-Yeah.
Okay, how do you prevent
eddy currents in a transformer?
Laminate the core material.
-Come on, give him a hard one.
-That was a hard one.
All right, how does the flow rate
in a pipe depend on its diameter?
[CHUCKLING]
You don't know, do you?
[SHELDON GASPS]
What's the matter, smart guy?
Don't know Poiseuille's Law?
[COUGHING]
Thank goodness, I got it.
Now I can quit checking my stool.
Okay, what are the potential side effects
for our erectile dysfunction drug?
-Headaches, dizziness, and nausea.
-Yes.
Those are also the side effects...
...of having a 75-year-old man
with an erection climb on top of you.
-Want to stop here?
-Uh, no, I can keep going.
No, you got this.
Let's go for a drink. I'll call Amy.
Good. She seemed like
she really wanted to go out tonight.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, girl.
Okay, next question. For the Butterfinger...
...how long is a galactic year?
-Two-hundred-and-fifty million years.
-Yes.
ALL: Yay!
-You got it.
Okay, this one is for a Cadbury Creme Egg.
Ah! It's not even Easter time. This is crazy.
Which Archimedean solid
has 20 regular triangular faces...
...30 square faces, 12 pentagonal faces...
...GD vertices, and 120 edges.
ALL [IN UNISON]:
The rhombicosidodecahedron.
-Yes.
ALL: Yay!
-We are so smart.
-Why didn't girls like us in high school?
-We're awkward, weird, couldn't play sports.
-Right again.
[ALL CHEER]
[English - us - an]