Would you like to hear some songs
I've rewritten...
...to get children interested
in the hard sciences?
-Sure.
-Really?
Yeah, well, I like music. I like science.
I like making fun of Sheldon. Hit it.
[SINGING]
There was a scientist who had a theory
And James Clerk Maxwell was his name-o
J-A-M-E-S
C-L-E-R-K
Space M-A-X-W-E-L-L
And James Clerk Maxwell was his name-o
There was a scientist who had a theory
A-M-E-S
Okay, okay. We get it.
Perhaps you'd prefer this one.
[SINGING]
The itsy bitsy spider is not an insect at all
Because it has eight legs
And two body pans
-That's pretty cool, Sheldon.
-Thank you.
Do either of you know Beyoncé?
I'd love her to get behind it.
-Hey.
You know the new Discovery class missions
NASA's been working on?
-Yeah.
-They're looking to include a message...
...from Earth in case one of them
is encountered by alien life.
When I encountered alien life, I discovered
that the key thing was not to sit in its spot.
You can't breathe our air
without an inhaler...
...he's allergic to Earth nuts,
but I'm the alien.
Anyway, I'm among a handful of scientists
that have been asked...
...to submit a design proposal
for the message and its delivery system.
-Excellent.
-Congratulations.
And I was wondering if any of you guys
would like to help me do it.
Are you kidding? Yes.
-What did you have in mind?
-l'll tell you what you should do.
Avoid the presumption
of the Terran sensory input paradigm.
Absolutely. You need a device capable
of delivering info...
...across a wide range
of perceptual modalities.
Any intelligent organism
would at the very least...
...need the ability to locate
the position of objects in space.
So the ideal interstellar lingua franca
would be haptic.
How about a 3D tactile communicator
rigged for cross-sensory transposition?
Exactly what I expected. Two people forcing
their ideas on me, and only one gentleman...
...who bothered to ask me
what my thoughts were. You two are out.
Congratulations, Leonard.
You're on the team.
My mommy raised a gentleman.
-Hey, thanks for coming by.
-Yeah, I'm excited to help.
I would've included the others, but
you know exactly what would've happened.
They would've taken over the project
and bossed us around.
I get it. Just this morning, Sheldon wouldn't
let me put almond milk on my Grape-Nuts...
...because he said
it was a theoretical nut conflict.
You should've told him
to mind his own business.
That's better than what I did say, which was,
"Fine, I'll eat them with club soda."
What makes them think
they're always in charge of everything?
-They're alpha males.
-Huh.
-What does that make us?
-We could be betas, they're second in charge.
-Okay, sounds good.
-Or we could be omegas.
They get pushed around by the alphas
and the betas.
Okay, that sounds like us.
Whatever. There's no alphas here,
and this is your project.
You're in charge.
How do you wanna start?
I don't know. How do you wanna start?
I don't know.
Should we call Sheldon and Howard?
-No, we can do this by ourselves.
-Okay, great. How do you wanna start?
I don't know. How do you wanna start?
Sheldon. Sheldon. Sheldon.
I bet that started off as ajoke...
...but by the third one you realized there was
something strangely enjoyable about it.
Yeah, I kind of wanna do it again.
I don't recommend it.
You'll be doing it the rest of your life.
If you're looking for Leonard,
he's with Koothrappali.
-No, I actually came to talk to you.
-How nice.
Here are some topics that interest me:
quantum mechanics, trains, flags--
No, no, it's about my acting career.
Oh, I'm sorry, that's not on the list.
-Well--
-Oh, wait.
How about we split the difference...
...and discuss why Austria was
an archduchy and notjust a regular duchy?
Okay, here's the thing.
I like pharmaceutical sales, it's going great...
...butl have an audition for a movie,
and ifl get it, it could screw everything up.
Mm. I know exactly what you should do.
Unfortunately, I cannot tell you.
Well, why?
I'm attempting to turn over a new leaf.
Earlier today, it was pointed out to me
that I tend to force my ideas on people.
You're really not gonna tell me?
No, that train has left the station.
Now, we can play this one of two ways.
You can say, "Trains? Tell me more."
Or you can just look at me like that
and I'll start.
What's going on in here?
lam making molecular cocktails.
This sphere is actually a cosmopolitan. Heh.
Oh, how do you drink it?
Just put it in your mouth
and pop it like a zit.
I think I'll have a beer.
-First, take a picture with me.
-Why?
Well, Raj and I always talked about learning
how to make cocktails like this together.
So I taught myself...
...and I'm putting this on lnstagram
so he can see it and feel like a turd.
Say, "Cheese."
Is this about the probe
he's working on without you?
You betcha. The very one.
Howard, you're a grown man. You guys
don't have to do everything together.
I know--
That's why I'm spending tonight with you.
Trying to hurt Raj's feelings.
With my honeybunch.
-You're being childish.
-No. He is.
So I have a dominant personality.
We all know that.
I'm sorry, what do we know?
In social groupings,
ljust naturally wind up in charge.
Don't take this wrong, but how many
of these little booze balls have you had?
-You don't think I'm a leader?
-I was kidding. Of course, you are.
Right. I couldn't change if I wanted to.
You'd better not change
because I love who you are.
Will you need help cleaning all this up when
you're done, or can you do it all by yourself?
All by myself.
There's my big boss man.
So often, on the front of the locomotive...
...is a large iron wedge
for clearing objects off the tracks.
While commonly known as a cow catcher,
I prefer the more accurate "cow exploder."
Okay, Sheldon, let me ask you a question.
If I was at a train station...
...and one train could take me
to my currentjob...
...and the other could take me
to an audition for a movie...
...which train should I get on?
Are you using trains
to trick me into giving you advice?
All right, then.
You should take a third train
where you audition for the movie...
...but hold off on making a career decision
until you have more information.
You're right. I'm worried about something
that hasn't even happened yet.
Huh. You are awise man.
Well, Penny, who's smarter, the wise man
or the person who comes to him for advice?
Oh, I guess you're right.
Maybe it is the person who asks.
No, it's the wise man.
That's why he's called the wise man.
Know howl know that?
I'm the wise man.
I'm sorry. What was I thinking?
Just out of curiosity, why didn't you
ask Leonard for advice about this?
Because I already know what he'll say,
"wah, wah, wah, you shouldn't do it."
It's just like he's here.
So we know that previous attempts
to send a message into space...
...like the Golden Record on Voyager,
were heavily criticized.
Aliens could only play the Golden Record
if they knew how to build a record player.
To be fair, I watched E.T. build a telephone
out of a Speak & Spell and an umbrella.
-Dude was like a little brown MacGyver.
-That would be helpful if E.T. were real.
Well, my feelings were real
when he was about to die.
My God, when he's on the table
and they used the paddles on him.
And he's all white.
And they zip him up in that bag.
And Gertie can't stop crying.
And the flower dies.
-Okay, let's talk about something else.
-All right.
So it sounds like we need a way
to communicate that's simple.
And doesn't require outside machinery
to be built to access it.
It's also a problem because we don't know
if the aliens who find this can see.
They might communicate
in a totally different way than us.
Like when my dog is mad at me,
she tells me by peeing in my slippers.
That's actually a valid example.
Animals do deliver messages through scent.
Bees talk to each other by dancing,
whales have songs--
Penny has about 20 different ways of rolling
her eyes that each mean something different.
So what it sounds like is what we want
is a device that can deliver a message...
...through not only sight
but other senses as well.
The most basic sense...
...that any space-faring civilization
would have to possess is touch.
Ooh! Ooh, ooh.
We could make a video-playing device...
...that simultaneously translates
the information into a tactile medium.
All we have to do
is rig a 3D communication system.
-We can totally do that.
-I know.
-This is great.
-Know what else it is?
-What?
-Exactly what Sheldon and Howard said.
Well, thank you for peeing in my slippers.
[SINGING] It's the eye of the tiger
It's the ear of the bat
It's the whiskers of the catï¬sh
And the walrus
Hang on.
Not that your song isn't terrible, it is.
But how do you mention bats
and leave out sonar?
You didn't let me finish.
[SINGING]
And also regarding the bat
It has sonar
-Hey.
-Hello.
Look...
...I know you guys are upset.
But we've talked about it...
...and we think it'd be beneficial
for you to be part of the project.
Well, well, well, did you hear that, Sheldon?
I'm sorry. I was trying think of what rhymes
with "nose of the aardvark."
We want you back on the project with us.
Well, well, well, did you hear that, Howard?
Look, we admit it, the idea that you guys
came up with was really good.
And I'd love your help.
I suppose it couldn't have been easy
for you to say.
It wasn't.
So are you in?
-Certainly.
-Sure.
Great. Now that we're all on the same page,
let's get together tonight and work on it.
Get together tonight?
Leonard, stop trying to control everything...
...and give poor Raj a chance to come up
with what we should do. Go ahead.
-I think we should do it right now.
-Tonight works better for me.
Okay.
P E N N Y :
Okay, it's just an audition.
Why am I nervous?
Maybe it's a good thing.
It just means I want it.
And I can have it.
This feels right. Why did I ever give this up?
Yeah, I'm starting to remember.
So I'd like to try a technique
where no one gets steamrolled.
When you talk,
instead of bringing up a new idea...
...respect what was just said
by building on it.
Uh, building on that,
we should order dinner.
How is that building on what he just said?
Building on what Sheldon said,
I could go for Chinese.
Hang on. Building on what Leonard said,
no one built on what I said.
Building on building on that, there's a new
build-your-own pizza place on Colorado.
-Building on that, I'm lactose intolerant.
-No, I saw the menu, they have soy cheese.
You didn't say "building on," you're out.
-lt's not Simon Says.
-You're missing the point.
You're out and you're out, I win.
Who wants pizza?
Penny?
-Oh, hey.
-Hey. I haven't seen you audition in a while.
Yeah, I got ajob
as a pharmaceutical sales rep.
-You quit acting?
-Kind of.
But now I get to act like inflamed heart
is only "a mild side effect."
I heard you can make good money
doing that.
Yeah, it's going okay,
but I do miss this sometimes.
Really?
Because I gotta tell you,
lam so sick of the humiliation...
-...and being treated like a piece of meat.
-Chelsea?
Wish me luck.
They're gonna love you.
I heard she's pushing 40
and everything's fake.
Yeah, I started that rumor.
Since we agree on the delivery system for
the message, maybe we should talk about...
...what the message could be.
Well, I think we should show
what Earthlings look like.
The plaque they sent on the Pioneer probe
had a drawing of a naked man and woman.
Yeah, I never cared for that.
It's advertising to predator races
just how soft and squishy we are.
Squeeze yourself.
Oh, don't be offended.
You know of the four of us,
you have the most veal-like consistency.
Maybe we can appear non-aggressive,
but also protect ourselves if necessary.
Like smiling and waving with one hand...
...but the other hand
holding the severed head of a tiger.
You wanna send a passive-aggressive
message into space? That's ridiculous.
Oh, you mean passive-aggressive
like posting pictures...
...of you and your wife eating cosmopolitan
balls that you know belong in my mouth?
Maybe Howard meant passive-aggressive
like asking our group's help...
...and then only choosing Leonard.
Look, I'm sorry I hurt your feelings...
...but you two have strong personalities
and always end up taking over.
It's not always.
What about when we went to Comic-Con
dressed like Jabba the Hutt?
You got to be Jabba's head
and I got to be his fat slug butt.
We looked great.
You let a guy sit on me.
He was dressed as Princess Leia.
It made a nice picture.
I'm just saying,
sometimes Raj and lfeel pushed aside.
Yeah, like when you took Sheldon to Texas
and showed him all around NASA.
You didn't even think
to ask me and Leonard.
You know what? You're right.
lshould've asked you.
And if he does ask you, go, it's amazing.
If we're talking about being left out, you
guys went to Skywalker Ranch without us.
Oh, I recommend that too.
That was a magical experience.
Wait. Sheldon spent a whole day with
James Earl Jones and never told any of us.
I sure did. Oh, my goodness.
From Jabba's head
to ice cream with Darth Vader.
I'm having a heck of a ride.
Clearly, good things happen
when I'm in charge.
Now, why don't you boys step aside?
Let me knock this project out.
Sheldon, you're not in charge.
Raj is in charge.
Leonard, who's really in charge?
The person in charge
or those who put him in charge?
He's right.
If you think about it, we're all in charge.
No, the guy in charge is in cha--
Why's everyone so bad at these?
I mean, the whole experience reminded me
about how much I hated that world.
You know, the anxiety, the depression,
the negativity.
I don't wanna feel those things.
I wanna sell drugs to people
who feel those things.
I can't believe you got up and walked out
of an audition for a big movie.
I did. I mean, I walked in, read for the part,
then stunk up the place.
But then I walked right out.
I'm glad you have a new appreciation
for yourjob.
I do. And I don't think I've ever thanked you
properly for helping me get it.
"Properly," "at all,"
it's just words I've never heard.
Well, thank you. You're
a good friend and you changed my life.
You're welcome. Hey,
now that you're making some real money...
...maybe you could take your friend out
for a nice thank-you dinner.
-Sure.
-You have to invite your other friend...
...because she overheard you talking
and it would be awkward to exclude her.
-Okay.
-How about now?
All right.
Don't forget your wallet.
Greetings from planet Earth.
Just turn left at Alpha Centauri,
you can't miss it.
[IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[English - us - an]