Gentlemen.
LEONARD: Hey.
HOWARD: Hello.
If any of you are looking for something
to do on Valentine's Day,
Amy and I'll be streaming our first ever
live episode of Fun with Flags.
You're welcome to join us
as we celebrate the timeless love affair
between wind and flapping fabric.
Penny and l have dinner reservations
that night, but any other time, no.
Sorry, Bernie and l are breaking in
the new hot tub, if you know what I mean.
Not a clue. Raj?
I'm spending Valentine's Day with Emily.
You don't sound very excited about it.
lam. lam. I guess I'm still wondering
if Emily and l are right for each other.
Does this have to do with that girl
you had coffee with?
You mean the strong, sexy angel
I can't stop thinking about? Who can say?
You've been talking about
breaking up with Emily forever,
why don't you just do it already?
Just get it over with.
Well, you say it like it's easy.
Have any one of you
ever broken up with anyone?
-No.
-Not really.
You know, once I ordered
an Uber by accident.
ljust got in and went somewhere.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
So, you're really gonna break up with her?
Yeah, I think so. Do you have any advice?
Well, l have broken up with
my fair share of guys.
I mean, how many times
did I break up with Leonard?
I stopped counting at four.
Great. My advice to you is do it at her
place so you can leave when you need to.
Tell the truth, make it quick,
and be prepared for tears.
Oh, I'm gonna do a pre-cry before I go
in there, really dry myself out.
-She meant Emily.
-No, I really didn't.
-You're seriously breaking up with me?
-Yeah.
And you thought right before
Valentine's Day was a good time to do it?
You're right, let's talk again
in a few days.
Hey, Claire. Hi, it's Rajesh.
l was wondering if
you're free for Valentine's Day?
Sorry, ljust got back with my boyfriend.
But ljust broke up with my girlfriend.
Right before Valentine's Day?
(SCOFFS) What an ass.
Please take me back!
Our love was meant to be--
(SOBBING) I'm gonna be all alone
on Valentine's Day!
Hmm, you were right, tears.
Okay. And we are live in 22 minutes.
l'm nervous. I hope people will be around
to watch even though it's Valentine's Day.
People who are fans of an Internet show
about flags? Trust me, they're around.
Oh, and speaking of Valentine's Day,
I haven't forgotten about you tonight.
What do you mean?
Well, you've become such an integral part
of my life as well as this show,
I felt it only right to include
your name in the title.
(CHUCKLES)
That is so sweet.
So, from now on, this program
will officially be known as
Dr. Sheldon Cooper and
Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler present...
(SHELDON READING)
Catchy.
I'm gonna check the temp on the tub.
Don't make it too hot.
Sorry, but too hot is
the only temperature I come in.
Look at that. You shaved it all.
You're welcome.
Um, question. This is my first hot tub,
is it supposed to come with
a rat flopping around in it?
Ew, really? Get it out!
H ow?
lwish we had a skimmer.
Well, you turn off the jets,
I'll get a strainer from the kitchen.
I don't know how to turn off the jets!
Good, I don't know where
you keep the strainer!
Excuse me.
Bad news, the maitre d' said
it's gonna be at least an hour.
An hour? What?
That's crazy, we have a reservation.
-I know.
-So, what did you say?
Thanks, sorry to bother you.
But I said it like a badass.
All right, well, can't you like
slip him some money or somethin'?
Really? I've never done that before.
Does it work?
Do people like money?
Is that what you're asking?
A lot of attitude from the woman
who thought MC-squared was a rapper.
Now is that a smart thing
to say on a holiday
that's basically national sex night?
I'm sorry. You're pretty. I'm stupid.
Hello. Just checking again for Hofstadter.
Still gonna be an hour?
-l'm afraid so.
-Okay, thanks.
H ey,
I think you may have dropped this?
Oh.
Anybody lose a 20?
ldid.
Oh, I took care of it.
Okay, we are live in five, four, three--
Oh, wait, oh, shoot, I already pushed
the button, never mind, we're live.
Hello, and welcome to a special
live edition of Dr. Sheldon Cooper...
And Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler present...
-Dr. Sheldon Cooper's Fun with Flags!
Consider tonight's episode a
Valentine's Day gift for you, our viewers.
It's also my gift to you.
That was clear, right?
'Cause you're not getting anything else.
Since we're live, you'll finally
be able to reach out to us
with your flag thoughts
and flag questions.
Allow us to answer a few quick ones
that we get all the time.
Yes, I really am a doctor.
Yes, she really is my girlfriend.
And no, ljust blink a lot,
it's not Morse code for "rescue me."
(COMPUTER CALL RINGING)
Oh, uh, uh...
Here's our first call.
Hello and welcome to Fun with Flags,
what's your question?
RAJ: What is wrong with me,
why am I so self-destructive?
-Rajesh?
-Yes!
Whenever things are going well,
| always find a way to ruin it.
You two look happy. How do you do it?
I think it starts with
good communication--
You know what?
That's not a flag question, next caller.
I hope you don't think I'm just saying
this because it's Valentine's Day,
but I love you so much.
I'm gonna put this down your robe.
It's not moving
but I think it's still alive.
Well, should we put it back
in there a few minutes?
No!
And it's not a rat, it's a rabbit.
-We need to save it.
-Well, how do we do that?
I don't know, look it up on your phone.
I'm gonna wrap it in a towel.
"Taking care of injured rabbit." Okay.
"Make sure it's comfortable and warm."
He was just in a hot tub,
I'm gonna say check.
Anything else?
"To make sure it's not dehydrated,
feed him an electrolyte solution.
"If it's not responding, use a warm cloth
to wash its face and genitals."
Yeah.
This is ridiculous. You know what,
I'm gonna talk to the maitre d'.
-What're you gonna say?
-I don't know. I'm gonna flirt with him.
I don't know if I'm comfortable with that.
I'm still sleeping with you tonight.
See if you can get a table by the window.
-Hi, there. What's your name?
-Glenn.
Oh, boy, it is crazy
in here tonight, huh, Glenn?
Well, you know, Valentine's Day.
Yes, ugh, I bet your girlfriend is
super bummed you had to work tonight.
Anyway, look, we have been
waiting awhile, and ljust feel--
With all due respect, ma'am,
there's nothing I can do.
(CHUCKLES) You don't have to
call me ma'am.
-Okay.
-I mean, we're basically the same age.
(LAUGHS) Okay.
How old are you?
I'm 21, how old are you?
Just shut up, Glenn.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
-What, why?
-Because I'm young, let's go!
Rajesh, it's perfectly normal to have
doubts after breaking up with someone.
RAJ: You really think so?
You know what's not normal?
Blubbering about emotions
during a flag show.
Unless that emotion is excitement over
New Zealand changing their flag.
And good luck you crazy Kiwis,
we're rooting for you.
Yourfriend is hurting.
No, Sheldon's right. Emily did say
| always talk about my feelings too much.
Why, I suppose that could be
a legitimate concern in a relationship.
Perhaps even a red flag,
and speaking of red flags,
check out this sexy number
from the former Soviet Union.
Hubba, hubba.
-(COMPUTER CALL RINGING)
-Oh, uh...
We have another caller.
Hi, you're on Fun with Flags.
BARRY: Hello, I wanna talk about
how Ioner I am, too.
Kripke, is that you?
Yeah, I'm just sittin' here
all by myself wondering if I'll ever
find someone to share my life with.
Preferably Asian, 18 to 24, no fatties.
Please, all comments and questions
should be flag related.
BARRY: All right.
Is my poIe flag related?
I don't see why not.
He's eating, that's a good sign.
You're gonna have to wait one hour
until you can go swimming again.
-He's pretty cute.
-He is.
Should we name him?
It is Valentine's Day.
How about Valentino?
Nice. A classic rabbit name.
Peter Rabbit, Roger Rabbit,
Valentino Wolowitz Rabbit.
Look at all that chest hair and overbite,
of course you're a Wolowitz.
Son of a bitch, he bit me!
-Are you okay?
-No. I'm not okay.
Wild rabbits can have rabies.
Oh. Well, why'd you put your finger
near its mouth?
Poorjudgment, obviously!
He's so little, I'm sure it's fine.
How can it be fine? ljust got attacked
by a clearly anti-Semitic wild animal.
It's not what we planned,
but this isn't so bad, right?
(MUFFLED) It is freakin' amazing.
Well, I'm glad you're feeling better.
lwasjust hungry and cranky.
And I've never been called ma'am before.
-Is that a big deal?
-Kind of.
When's the first time
someone's called you sir?
Sixth grade. But I wore a sport coat
and carried a brief case so...
Can you believe when I met you l was 22?
I mean, it's crazy.
Where did all that time go?
Hmm, you watched The Bachelora lot.
Yeah, go ahead and makejokes.
But your 30s are almost over.
No, they're not.
You're closer to 40 than you are to 30.
(LAUGHS) You married an old man.
Tell you what,
let's do something fun tonight.
It won't make us any younger.
Well, maybe not,
but someday we actually will be old
and we'll look back on this night and
remember what a good time we had.
Okay, like what?
I know, food fight!
I'll keep thinking.
Look, I know you both
feel bad about being alone,
but sometimes the best thing you can do
is take a little time for yourself,
especially when you
just got out of a relationship.
And speaking of ending relationships,
when British Honduras became Belize,
they designed a new flag
with a tree on it.
And lwould like
to hang myself from that tree.
But Amy, when you and Sheldon split up
didn't you start dating
someone right away?
Well, I wouldn't say right away.
And actually, it was three different men.
BARRY: Three different men?
Damn, girl, way to give the milk away!
Aw, looks like we just lost Kripke.
BARRY: No, actually, I'm still here.
-N ow?
- Yep.
N ow?
Aw, looks like we just lost Kripke.
Before Emily, l was alone for so long.
I don't know if I can do that again.
Well, you know, here is something
that might cheer you up.
The flag of the Isle of Man is nothing but
three legs sharing
a weird pair of underpants.
So, you think you got problems...
l have an idea.
Maybe someone in our audience
would be interested in meeting Rajesh.
Ladies, I can attest that he is a kind,
handsome, intelligent--
RAJ: Rich parents,
don't forget rich parents!
-Spoiled astrophysicist, who not only--
-(COMPUTER CALL RINGING)
Oh, well, that was quick.
Hi, you're on Fun with Flags.
BARRY: Hey, I think Igot cut off.
Hello, Kripke.
BARRY: I have a flag question.
How many men did you have sex with?
Let's see, what's young and fun?
Uh, we could go dancing.
Are you actually gonna dance?
-Well, of course.
-Yeah, no one wants to see that.
Hey, how about skinny-dipping
at the beach?
No, I don't need any fish
nibbling my business.
Oh, there's a screening of Moulin Rouge.
I heard the crowd sings along and stuff.
That sounds fun. When's it start?
Midnight.
Midnight, really?
You know what? Let's do it.
Okay, great!
Oh, wait, uh, it's sold out.
-Oh, thank God!
-Yes!
It says rabies in rabbits
is highly unlikely.
Terrific!
It's not terrific.
Lots of highly unlikely things happen.
You saw what's under this robe
and you still married me.
If you're really worried, we'll take him
to a vet and have him tested.
Good, thank you. Okay, there is a test.
All they have to do is cut off his head
and check his brain.
Oh, cut off his head?
That's where his little nose is.
He's not showing any symptoms.
Okay, I guess, I'll just go to
the emergency room to be safe.
Howie, this is just your hypochondria.
When I sat on the mute button
and thought I'd gone deaf,
that was my hypochondria.
We'll find another time
to tell him I'm pregnant.
RAJ: I mean, this is the ï¬rst time
I've ever broken up with someone.
ljust... I didn't realize it was
gonna hur't just this much.
It really can.
All right.
Nothing about this is fun.
And no one wants to talk about flags.
But I haven't spoken in over 10 minutes.
So, enjoy your new show, lnternet.
(SHELDON READING)
RAJ: I'm sorry for bothering you.
I'll hang up now.
Hold on, Rajesh.
You know, you're not being
very sympathetic.
You know firsthand that breakups are hard.
Fine. If you insist on making me
a part of this, yes,
I acknowledge how painful they can be.
However, pain has an evolutionary purpose.
It provides information
from the environment
that a behavior isn't good for us.
BARRY: Like when I fell in love with
that stripper and bought her a Prius.
I'm just gonna push all the buttons.
Raj, now, I'm sorry you're suffering.
When Amy and l were broken up,
I also suffered.
And this may sound surprising,
but I'm grateful
for having gone through it.
Really?
Yes.
I believe our relationship now
is stronger than ever.
So do I.
When we were apart,
I learned how important you are to me.
And I realized that when two people
are in love, sometimes they--
Happy Valentine's Day!
(HORN BLOWING)
We are young and fun!
(HORN CONTINUES BLOWING)
I stand corrected.
Congratulations on a successful live show.
And a lovely Valentine's Day.
Cleaning up is not young and fun.
It can be. Confetti fight!
Maybe you should take a break. I got this.
Did you know the singular
of confetti is confetto?
Interesting, and when
would you use the singular?
I'm glad you asked.
Amy, you have a confetto in your nose.
No, no, no, other side. There you go.
English - SDH