-You're wrong.
-No, I'm not.
-Yes, you are.
Settle this. Those little animated pictures on
the Internet. Are they called gifs or "jifs"?
Well, the 6 stands for "graphic,"
so that's a hard 6, so I'd say gif.
-The guy who invented it says it's "jif."
-Do you mean the guy or the "juy"?
Well, I'll give you three guesses
why I'm so irritated.
Something happened different
from the way you wanted it.
I guess news travels fast.
It's true. A select group of scientists
was invited to a weekend symposium...
...at a former home of Richard Feynman,
and lwasn't included.
Oh. Sheldon, I'm sure it's not because
they don't think you're an elite scientist.
Yeah, I bet you anything
it's just because you're a pain in the ass.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
You can spend the rest of the day
being bitter--
Ag reed.
l was gonna say "or," but why bother?
-Hey, Raj.
-Hey. I got you a little gift.
Wow, that's a lot of Girl Scout cookies.
You know me. I'm from India.
I can't resist children begging.
-How's it going with the title to the house?
-Great. It's done.
The lawyer tracked down my father,
got him to sign it over.
I didn't have to meet him, didn't have
to talk to him. I don't even know where he is.
-Wow. So you're not curious at all?
-Nope.
Huh. What if he's in prison?
What if he's a spy?
What if he's in a Beatles cover band?
I'm just saying,
if he's got your nose and haircut...
...he'd make a killer Ringo.
-Thanks for agreeing to do this.
-Cool. I've never been on a podcast before.
Well, you picked a good one to start.
Wil's had lots of great guests.
Jonathan Frakes, Brent Spiner,
Michael Dorn, Gates McFadden.
-Those are Star Trek people.
-Yes.
I only figured that out
because I'd never heard of any of them. Heh.
l deserved that.
I invited you on my show and I drove here.
Sorry.
Okay, so this is basically
just like a little talk show.
We're gonna take some calls, talk about
what it was like on the set of Serial Ape-is! 2.
-It should be really fun.
-This is exciting.
Yeah. So how many people listen?
Most people download it later,
but usually a few thousand listen live.
What? A few thousand people listen
to you talk about nerd stuff?
Again, right in the ears,
straight to the feelings.
Can you please pass the salt?
Sure. Not like I was invited
to Richard Feynman's house...
...and have anything better to do.
-Is this how the rest of the night's gonna be?
-I don't know the future.
Do you think there's a chance
that an asteroid could hit the Earth...
...destroying Feynman's house
and everyone in it?
No, Sheldon.
Well, then, buckle up.
You're in for a cranky night.
According to the codicil
of the relationship agreement...
...which you insisted on, we're not allowed
to pout or be moody on date night.
You know I just put that in
because of uterus stuff.
Well, it applies to you too.
l was afraid you might bring this up...
...so I have a work-around.
There you go.
As far as you're concerned, I'm smiling.
Though I admit I'm smiling a little
at the moment...
...because this loophole is so brilliant.
So, Bernadette, have you thought about
how you're going to redecorate this place?
You know, I'm thinking,
ripping up the carpets...
...maybe lose the wallpaper,
all new light fixtures.
You know, if you knocked out this wall,
it would give you an open floor plan.
And then--
It's a little scary but could be fun.
--indoor fire pit.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hey, I grew up in this house, okay?
No one's knocking anything down.
Okay, okay.
When he's at Comic-Con,
I'm bringing in awrecking ball.
-Can I help you?
-Hi, are you Howard Wolowitz?
Yes.
Um, this is a little weird.
A lawyer was trying to contact my father...
...because his name was still on the title
for this house.
Well-- Who's your father?
Sam Wolowitz.
Oh.
-Sam Wolowitz is my father.
-I know.
Well, wait. So if we have the same father....
I mean, are you saying
you're my half-brother?
lthink so.
Bernadette, weird things are happening
out here.
I think I started to suspect
it was a bad movie...
...when I looked at the script
and saw the title...
...Serial Ape-is! 2: Monkey See, Monkey Kill.
Spoiler alert: After the monkey sees, it kills.
Psst.
I've just been handed a note.
I'm going to read it.
"Wil, do you want more Diet Coke?
Also, we have juice."
I didn't wanna interrupt.
That voice you just heard belongs
to Leonard, Penny's fiancé.
-Will you grab headphones and join us?
-Really?
WIL: Yeah.
-That'd be great.
All right, so while Leonard gets set up,
let's take a call.
Hello, caller. You are on with Penny and Wil
from Serial Ape-is! 2.
WOMAN : I don't have a question.
I just wanna say I'm a big fan of the movie.
I've seen it like 10 times.
Okay, well, I'll apologize for the first time,
but the other nine are on you.
Thanks, caller. You know the movie
actually has a little bit of a cult following?
-Really?
-I was at a science-fiction convention...
...and I saw a woman dressed
as your half-ape character.
Oh, if she was with an Indian guy
dressed like a banana...
...that was just my friends Howard and Raj.
It's time for a very special guest caller.
A friend of mine you probably know
as the director of such movies as Clerks...
...or from podcasts and books where he
reminds you he directed Clerks.
Hello, Kevin Smith.
KEVIN SMITH [OVER PHONE]:
Hey, man, yo. Is everything okay, Wil?
Because it's been like two minutes and
you haven't even brought up Stand by Me.
-Hey, Kevin, it's exciting to talk to you.
-Yeah, it really is.
Oh, you guys are very sweet.
So, Penny, listen. I saw your movie.
Oh, wow, I wish it was better.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Have you seen some of Kevin's films?
You're cruising for a beating, Wheaton.
Anyway, man, I dug the ape movie, Penny.
Andl thought you were really great in it.
-Aw.
-You know, I'm in the movie too.
Yeah, whatever. Penny....
Penny, how come you're not in more stuﬁ?
I'd cast you in a minute.
-Seriously?
-Oh, yeah, man.
I'm actually in preproduction
on a movie right now...
...way diﬁ'erent than anything
I've ever done before. It's called Clerks 3.
-You should come over and read for a part.
-Oh, my-- I would love that.
-You have a newjob.
-Well, maybe I could do both.
I don't think you can do both.
I don't think I asked you.
Yeah, you tell him, Penny.
Stay out of it, Kevin Smith.
Do you think there comes a time when
it stops feeling bad to be left out of things?
Probably not.
It's an evolutionary advantage
to be included in group activities.
You know what?
I used to be a fan of evolution...
...but I've since evolved,
and now I think it's dumb.
Being left out is a terrible feeling.
No one understands that better than I do.
Hey, look at that.
Even in your example,
you're all by yourself.
When there was a lice epidemic
at my school, everybody got it except me.
I tried to fool everyone by sprinkling sugar
in my hair, but I just got attacked by bees.
I can just picture them all right now
at Feynman's house.
Probably discussing Schrodinger...
...and at the same time,
not discussing Schrodinger.
See? They're missing out
on hilariousjokes like that.
And at the same time, not.
Reminds me of when my stupid brother and
sister would build forts in the living room...
...and wouldn't let me in.
I hated that so much.
You know, there's nothing I can do
about getting you invited to the symposium.
But if you wanted...
...we could build a fort.
Isn't that a little juvenile?
More juvenile than this?
I'll get the blankets,
you Google how to have childlike fun.
You know, I'm being a bad host.
Let me get some more coffee.
-Oh, let me do it, Howard.
-No, I got it.
So, Josh, what do you do?
I'm studying oceanography
down in San Diego.
Oh, how nice.
I love Finding Nemo.
Enough chitchat. How do we know
you are who you say you are?
-Why would I lie?
-Okay, you got me there.
-You here looking for money?
-No.
Kidney? Cornea? Piece of his liver?
You're in a Beatles cover band...
...and you need Howard
to replace your dad as Ringo.
-Why don't you help with the coffee?
-Okay, but something smells fishy.
And notjust because
you work around sea animals.
That actually sounds interesting,
and I'd like to learn more about it.
-Hey, you okay?
-Not really.
This guy shows up out of the blue,
and now I have a brother?
My father has another family?
I get it. What do you wanna do?
I don't know, I....
I'd just like him to go away.
I can't deal with this.
All right, I got your back.
Thank you. Come on.
I'd like to point out,
this wall just provided a lot of privacy.
I can't believe my brother's an astronaut.
That's amazing. What was it like?
-Listen, dude, it's time for you to hit the--
-Hey. The man asked a good question.
So for those of you just tuning in...
...we are listening to a really fun fight
between my co-star--
We're not fighting.
We're just having a conversation.
All right. We're listening
to a really fun conversation...
...between my co-star from Serial Ape-ist 2
and her fiancé...
...who doesn't believe
women should have dreams.
Give me back thatjuice.
-What is the harm ifl audition?
-Well, what if you get it?
I don't know, I make a movie,
we could become rich and famous...
...win an Oscar, Golden Globe,
and live an incredibly wonderful life.
From a Kevin Smith movie?
KEVIN SMITH [OVER PHONE]:
Oh, I'm hanging up now.
Don't listen to him. You're awesome. You're
one of the greatest directors of our time.
I don't have a part for you, Wheaton.
And that was Kevin Smith.
-Thanks a lot.
-l'm just trying to protect you.
How many times did you get your heart
broken trying to make it as an actress?
Instead of protecting me, try being excited
when something good happens.
I'm always excited for you.
I'm excited that you found this newjob
where you're making decent money.
-Decent? I make twice what you make.
-Wait, twice?
Yeah.
Like, times two? Twice?
For you at home, Leonard just found out his
fiancée makes more money than he does.
Let's listen.
I went to school for half my life.
I have a doctorate.
I'm still paying off college loans.
Well, how much do you owe?
Maybe I can help you out.
Wil, l'm-- Can we just turn off the podcast
for a little bit?
For those of you at home,
lam shaking my head no.
How's it going, Sheldon?
Wonderful.
ljust finished hanging the lights.
-Can I come in?
-Yes. Oh, but enter through the side.
Batman is a load-bearing blanket.
-Amazing.
-I know.
This isn't the printout. This is my real face.
What are we doing? This is a fort.
Let's sit on the floor.
Roughing it? Okay.
Everything looks so big from down here.
This must be how Leonard feels.
I'm surprised you could hear me
with this Thin Mint in your ear! Ha, ha!
-Yeah, pretty cool, huh?
-Yeah.
Anyway, I should probably get going.
Howie, have you noticed how often
people say that when you start to do magic?
Sorry. I have a long drive.
Well, I hope I get to see you again.
I hope so too. I've always dreamed
of having a brother to play catch with.
Aw. Keep dreaming.
Hey, I threw the first pitch
at an Angels game.
-Wow.
-He did it with a robot.
You had sex with a robot?
-That's not what she meant.
-But technically, yes.
Hang on. If you're making all this money,
where is it?
-In a safe place.
-What does that mean? Under your bed?
No. It means a diversified portfolio
of stocks and bonds.
I'm not overly conservative. I'm young. So
my guy said I can afford to take some risks.
-Wait a minute. You have a guy?
-Don't you have a guy?
Why would I have a guy?
I don't have any money.
Oh, sweetie,
you should really get some money.
For those of you listening at home,
how great is this?
Wil, I'm begging you,
just please turn that off.
Sure.
And we're back.
Why are you making
such a big deal out of this?
So our roles changed a bit
over the last couple years.
This is the way life is.
And I'm sure in time they'll change again.
Great. You're not only
more successful than me...
...now you're more mature.
Okay, look. Would it make you feel better
ifl did something dumb...
...like sneak out of work one day
to go audition for a Kevin Smith movie?
That would be great. Thank you.
I'm just gonnajump in here real quick.
Leonard, a moment ago you were dead set...
...against Penny resuming her acting career,
but now you're all for it.
Is it fair to say
that she played you like a violin?
Yes, it is, Wil.
So I have to ask.
Was the robot sexy?
It was actuallyjust a mechanical hand.
Because that's all you need, right?
You are my brother.
So the final four forts in the first annual
Best Fort Ever Contest or fort-off...
...are Fort Knox, Fort Ticonderoga,
Fort Sumter...
...and Fort Cozy McBlanket.
I'd say Knox over Ticonderoga,
because it's got the gold...
-Mm-hm.
-...and McBlanket over Sumter...
...because it has a higher thread count.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Oh.
Ten o'clock.
-Date night's over.
-No. We haven't picked a winner.
We both know this one's gonna win.
Well, of course we do.
Fort Knox doesn't have
a secret physics lending library.
-Come on. I'll help you take this down.
-Wait. What if, just this once...
...we suspend the date-night parameters
and you stay later?
Well, as long as we're suspending
the parameters...
...I could stay really late,
and we could have our first sleepover.
-That's a big step.
-lt's a big fort.
Very well.
I will agree to a family-friendly,
G-rated boy-girl sleepover.
PG. Some scenes may be too intense
for younger viewers.
G-rated with a warning
for families with babies and toddlers.
You got yourself a sleepover.
Do you need to borrow a toothbrush
or pajamas?
Would it alarm you to know
that I hid those things here two years ago...
...just in case this ever came up?
It would, but you know how much
I admire preparedness.
How did you know
we'd be in the living room?
Who says this is the only one I hid?
Hello? What is this?
We built a fort.
Are those my sheets?
Yes, they are.
Okay, well, you kids have fun.
I'm gonna go to sleep.
Leonard, don't you wanna see
the inside of the fort?
-No, I'm good.
-Oh, come on.
I really wanna tell someone
they can't come in.
Okay, fine.
Sheldon, may I please visit your fort?
I wanna say no, but it's too glorious.
Get in here.
LEONARD: Thank you.
AMY: Have a seat on the floor.
SHELDON:
Not there. That's my spot.
[English - us - an]