-Hey.
-Hi, how was the screening?
Oh, Sheldon invoked Rosa Parks
to make somebody, who cut the line,
feel bad,
but only the white people felt bad.
I should have never
bought him that coloring book
that explains Black History Month.
How'd it go with my mother?
You know, it started a little rocky,
but I think we got to a good place.
Wow. Well done. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, and when I dropped her off
at the hotel,
she even gave me a hug.
Did she think you were choking?
I'm sorry, that's great.
Thank you for spending time with her.
No problem.
So, listen, I don't know
if you have any plans next weekend,
but I kind of promised your mom
we'd have another wedding ceremony
so she could attend this time.
Wait, we're gonna get married again?
Yeah, kind of, but now
we can invite our friends and family.
Seems like a lot of trouble for a hug.
Come on, it'll be fun. And you know,
your mom was genuinely hurt
we didn't invite her to the first one.
Well, in our defense,
it was kind of a spur-of-the-moment thing.
And also, we don't like her.
Leonard, come on, she's your mom.
If we can do something to make her happy,
why wouldn't we?
ljust said why. We don't like her.
Okay, look, forget about her,
let's do it for us.
We can keep it small and informal,
and this time we can invite our families.
Is your brother out of prison?
Thanks to overcrowding, yeah.
I'd love it if my dad could come.
Oh! You have to invite him.
I haven't seen him since the divorce.
Oh, he is like a different man.
He stopped twitching,
and I think he grew an inch and a half.
Well, then it's settled.
Yay!
God, it's so funny, I never thought
my second marriage would be to you.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Okay, so, it's not a legal ceremony,
it's just a chance for us
to redo our vows
so everyone can be part of it.
So, there's no maid of honor?
-No.
-Hmm.
But if I were to, say,
wear a purple satin dress
with a sweetheart neckline
and stand near you,
you wouldn't be able to stop me, right?
-I don't see howl could.
-(LAUGHS)
Then I graciously accept. (CHUCKLES)
Who's going to officiate?
l was kind of hoping you would.
Wait, now I'm just
some lousy maid of honor? What?
Hey, good news. ljust got off the phone
with my mother.
She is coming to the wedding.
Okay, you're inviting people
to ourwedding?
Yes, I'm inviting people to ourwedding.
Yeah, I've already asked Stephen Hawking
and Robert Downey, Jr.,
and now, don't get your hopes up,
'cause he's pretty busy, but Erno Rubik.
Who's Erno Rubik?
Seriously?
He invented the Rubik's Cube.
Okay, fine, but why would you invite him
to our wedding?
Because despite his fame and fortune,
he strikes me as a lonely man.
Well, it's very sweet of you
to go to all this trouble
for Leonard's mother.
You know, I'm also doing it for Leonard.
I think
this could really help their relationship.
How dare you invite your father
without consulting me?
I'm sorry,
but I don't think I need your permission
to have my father at my wedding.
You do understand our marriage ended
because he had an affair.
I know, and there's no excuse for that.
He claimed l was cold, emasculating,
and hadn't shown him
any physical affection for years.
l was wrong,
there's three excuses for that.
Oh, my God, it's working.
-You sure?
-Look.
The system is maintaining
its own stability.
The quantum vortex apparatus
is now controlling the orientation.
You're right. You realize what this means?
Yeah.
I do.
lt's proof of concept.
We've got a workable guidance system.
Congratulations. (CHUCKLES)
-Thanks.
-(BOTH LAUGH)
(BEEPS)
Hey, ljust got an email
from the US Air Force.
Open it.
"We request a meeting
at your earliest convenience
"regarding your quantum guidance system,
provisional patent 62/295118."
That's weird.
Is there a window around here
we don't know about?
No, I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
Yeah, of course, what else could it be?
Boy, do I love America!
Thank you for picking me up.
Oh, you're welcome.
l was speaking to your young lady.
My pleasure, Mrs. Cooper.
Oh, please, call me Mary.
Okay, Mary.
You know, that doesn't work for me,
let's stay with "Mrs. Cooper."
Sheldon, don't be silly.
What? That's what I called you
until I got to know you better.
It was so nice of Leonard and Penny
to invite me.
-Well, actually--
-It sure was!
I've always had a special place
in my heart for Leonard,
taking care of my baby all these years.
Excuse me, I take care of him.
Sure you do.
So, who else is coming to this shindig?
Oh, well, the usual gang.
Penny's family's coming tomorrow.
Yeah, Leonard's mother's already here.
Oh, Beverly, how nice.
You've met her, right?
Yes, l have.
Mother, she's an atheist, not a vampire.
Either way,
let's stop and get some garlic.
So, Mary, how have you been?
Thank you so much for asking.
I've been well, and you?
-Very good.
-Good.
I don't know what we were worried about,
they're getting along great.
Sheldon tells me your husband's coming.
My ex-husband.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
-Don't be.
-All right.
Ooh. Chilly.
I think I can see my breath.
We can hear you.
-Sorry.
I can't believe I was so nai've.
The military is just gonna take over
the whole project.
And you know what happens if we object.
We disappear.
(HOWARD CHUCKLES)
Like, off the map!
Like every American Idol winner
since season four.
Come on, Howard, you're overreacting.
(YELLS) Am I?
(WHISPERS) Am I?
I mean, what do you wanna bet
some black-ops guy
is reprinting my high school yearbook,
and I'm no longer in it.
That chess club picture is nowjust
David Zimmerman and Elaine Cho.
Okay, look, I'm on the Air Force website,
and the department that emailed you
is in charge of acquisitions.
So, maybe they just wanna give you
a lot of money for your invention.
Oh, please, that's not how it works.
You saw E. T., Avatar, Jurassic World.
The militaryjust shows up and takes over.
You do realize
those weren't documentaries, right?
(LAUGHS)
I'm sorry, you find this funny?
No, lwasjust thinking
about Jurassic World.
Boy, that was terrible.
Oh, we have to use the stairs.
When are they gonna fix your elevator?
I don't... Any day now.
Well, the stairs are fine.
ALFRED: Besides,
your mother's up there.
Maybe I'll have a heart attack
and not have to see her.
Hey, I know things are a little rough
with you and Mom,
but I'm really glad you're here.
Me, too.
I should never have had that angioplasty,
because I feel fine.
Penny's really looking forward
to seeing you.
Ah, she's a sweetie.
You got a good one there, Leonard.
Thanks, Dad.
How the hell did you do that?
(CRUNCHES)
Isn't this nice?
Hey, we're here.
-Alfred, thank you for coming!
-Oh!
-Well, happy to be here.
-Thanks.
-And congratulations.
-Thank you.
Dad, you remember Sheldon.
-Dr. Hofstadter.
-Dr. Cooper.
This is Sheldon's mother, Mary.
-How do you do?
-Nice to meet you.
And his girlfriend, Amy.
-A pleasure.
-Hi.
And of course, Mom.
Hello, my hateful shrew.
Hello to you, you wrinkled old bastard.
All right, now I'm starting to sense
a little tension.
All right, you two, don't start.
Penny and l
are throwing this second wedding
for your benefit.
Can you please not ruin it?
Of course. I'm sorry.
Look at that, you can apologize.
-Mom!
-l'm sorry.
You know, the Bible says forgiveness--
-Mom!
-l'm sorry.
Who's hungry? We have a reservation
at the best restaurant in town.
That only got
three and a half stars on Yelp.
-Sheldon.
-l'm not sorry, that's true.
I don't know what to do.
It's the Air Force.
I mean, should I respond to their email?
lgnore it?
You can't ignore it.
It's not that postcard that says
it's time to go back to the dentist.
Guys, come on,
we're meeting everyone for dinner.
One sec. I'm just afraid ifl respond,
then they'll know I got it.
Dude, the minute you opened that email,
they knew you got it.
I mean, they're probably looking at you
through the camera right now.
Damn.
I love America.
Are you done with this nonsense?
It's not nonsense.
This is how the US military works.
If it's even the US military.
It could be foreign military
pretending to be American.
You're right. We turn our guidance system
over to them,
next thing we know,
they're using it against us.
I also love the enemies of America.
Penny, I hope the example
of my failed marriage to Leonard's father
doesn't discourage you from the commitment
you've made to one another.
No, of course not.
Although, Alfred and I had a lot more
going for us than you two.
Mom, please save something for the toast.
So, Alfred,
what is it that you do for a living?
Oh, I'm an anthropologist.
I study ancient peoples and cultures.
My goodness!
So, all the way back to the Flood.
(LAUGHS)
Don't laugh, she wasn'tjoking.
Play with your phone.
Well, on that note,
there are many cultures
that have an apocalyptic flood
as part of their mythology.
I don't have a mythology,
l have the unerring word of God.
-But that's very interesting.
-Oh!
I didn't mean to disparage your faith.
Actually, I admire it.
-Really?
-Yes.
I'm an agnostic, myself,
but I have prayed many times to God
to turn my wife into a pillar of salt.
Well, he came close. He turned her
into a giant block of ice.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Howard, there must be someone
at the university you can go to for help.
Are you kidding?
They're probably the ones who leaked it
to the military in the first place.
What about the guy on the Channel 4 news?
You know? "Four on your side."
Maybe he can be on your side.
I'm being harassed by the government.
I'm not trying to get to
the bottom of a dog-walking scam.
Ugh. Stop.
You know what's really happening?
All the movies you've watched,
the TV shows, the comic books,
they've completely twisted your thinking.
No one's after you,
no one's listening to you,
no one cares about you.
I'd like to think
the "Four on your side" guy
cares about me.
You know, Beverly, I know you and Alfred
have your differences.
But if you think about it,
if you hadn't married him,
-there'd be no Leonard.
-(CHUCKLES)
So, that's good, right?
Yeah.
(SIGHING)
Is that Howard in front of us?
Oh, maybe. Hey, get closer.
God, I think someone's following us.
You're being ridiculous.
I'm not being ridiculous. He's right
on my tail. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Turn left here
and see if he turns with us.
Oh! Why is he turning here?
The restaurant's the other way.
I don't know. He uses that traffic app,
maybe there's an accident.
Oh! So follow him.
Oh, no!
I told you.
lt's probablyjust a coincidence.
Speed up a little,
see if he stays with you.
Well, go faster, you're losing him.
What is his hurry?
You know what? Flash your lights,
let him know it's you.
He's flashing his lights.
What's that mean?
I think he wants us to pull over.
Do not pull over!
I'm not raising this baby alone!
Hang on!
So, after your husband passed,
you never remarried?
No. Just focused on work and the church.
Ah! And what do you do?
| work at the church.
Well, they're lucky to have you.
Well, thank you.
You're welcome.
Do you realize what's happening here?
Yeah, I do.
They're filling up on bread
and ruining their meal.
-Hey.
-Hey, what took you guys so long?
We were following Howard,
but for some reason
he turned off his headlights
and went up a one-way street.
So, what did we miss?
Oh, just Mary and |
getting to know each other a little.
Leonard, your father's just charming.
He's also broke. Did he mention that?
Okay, Mom, you sit over there.
You know, I'm gonna call Bernadette
and see what's keeping them.
Well, if I'd known you were broke,
I wouldn't have made a big deal
about the bread.
Hey, Penny.
What are you talking about?
Oh, that was you?
(CHUCKLES)
Long story.
Why don't you go ahead and eat?
We're gonna be a while.
I'm telling ya, I'm not on drugs.
The government's out to get me!
Now, one of the more exciting things
we found recently
is that Neanderthals and Homo Sapiens
frequently mated with each other.
Well, that certainly explains
my marriage to Sheldon's father.
(LAUGHING)
That's funny because my father
was not a very clever man.
I'd be lost without you.
(CLINKING)
I would like to propose a toast
to my wife and bride-to-be.
-Now, see, that's funny because--
-Back to your phone.
Penny,
I've always known I loved you.
But this last year has shown me
that I also love being married to you.
Thank you for saying yes.
Thanks for asking until I did.
-Hear, hear.
-Cheers.
I would also like to make a toast.
Aww.
Leonard, I am so happy
that you have found a woman
who loves and cares for you.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Why don't you take a pill?
Like you did before sex?
What I really needed was a blindfold.
All right, everyone, calm down.
Let's all remember
what it says in the Bible,
"He who is slow to anger
is better than the mighty."
Oh, dear woman,
can you please read another book?
When God writes one, lwill.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Um...
If we wanna order the soufflé,
we might wanna get on that.
Leonard, if you don't mind,
I think I'm a little tired.
I'm gonna call it a night.
-Sure, Dad.
-l'm a little tuckered out myself.
I will see you all in the morning.
-Would you like to share a cab?
-That would be fine.
-Where you staying?
-l'm at the Westin.
Well, so am I.
Could I interest you in a nightcap?
I think that you could.
What is happening there?
I think it's pretty obvious.
They don't want dessert
'cause they filled up on bread.
She's still not answering.
My father's not texting me back.
'Cause they both turned their phones off.
I don't like this at all.
I don't like it, either.
Really?
(LAUGHS) Because I love it.
(LAUGHING)
English - SDH