I have a question about Batman.
Batman is a man who dresses up like a bat.
Yeah.
Man-Bat is a part-man, part-bat hybrid.
Now, if Man-Bat dressed up as a man
to fight crime,
would he be Man-Batman?
No, he'd be Bat-Man-Bat.
But wouldn't Man-Batman just be a Batman
that was bitten by a radioactive man?
But Batman is a man.
You're talking about a man
who would have the powers of a man.
That's just Man-Man.
lsn't Man-Man just Man?
But what if Man-Man dressed as a bat?
Well, that's just Batman.
No, if a man dresses as a bat,
that's Batman,
but if Man-Man dresses as a bat,
that's Bat-Man-Man.
(PHONE CHIMES)
So, does that answer your question?
Oh, I haven't asked it yet.
Oh, that's Claire, gotta run.
Thought you were back with Emily?
Uh, actually, I'm seeing both of them.
You mean like through their window
from behind a bush?
No, I'm actually dating two women.
Later.
(SCOFFS) Really?
The guy who for years
couldn't even talk to women
is suddenly going out with two of them?
-How is that possible?
-HOWARD: Iknow.
Scientists have tried to reproduce it
with computational models,
but in each case, the world blows up.
Seriously, that guy's dating two women?
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
What? Why did you get a party sub?
People are coming over. It looked fun.
Oh, we're only watching Game of Thrones.
No, a party sub implies it's a party.
Your attendance implies it's not.
I like a party as much as the next man.
As long as the next man
doesn't like a party.
Oh, by the way, don't forget, tomorrow is
our quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
Sheldon, we don't need a meeting
every three months.
Well, it sounds like the kind of thing
one would bring up
at a quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
Lucky for you it's tomorrow.
Well, you know what? I'm not going.
Well, you have to go.
lt's Penny's first time leading
the Pledge of Allegiance.
This meeting is a waste of time.
Whether we make the switch from
Post Raisin Bran to Kellogg's Raisin Bran
should not require
parliamentary procedure.
You realize one of them
has sugar on the raisins.
You're the only one who eats them!
And yet you get to weigh in!
Democracy! It's pretty cool, isn't it?
I'm not going. You can't make me.
Well, we'll just see about that.
What is the problem?
He says he's not coming to
the Roommate Agreement meeting tomorrow.
What?
Why the hell did I memorize the Pledge?
You have fun. lwill not be attending.
Well, fine we don't have to have
a Roommate Agreement meeting
-if you don't want to.
-Thank you.
Of course, this will require a vote.
Unfortunately, my official gavel
is in my bedroom.
-But luckily, I have my travel gavel.
-(GAVEL CLICKS)
You're being ridiculous.
There's a motion on the floor,
"l'm ridiculous."
Do we have a second?
Mmm? Mmm?
There is no second. The motion is denied.
Next time, make sure
you have the votes first.
-That was embarrassing.
-(BANGS GAVEL)
Can you please talk to him?
Oh, why are you fighting him on this?
Because I am tired of him
always getting his way.
We don't need a stupid meeting,
we don't even need a Roommate Agreement,
and I hope that sandwich
does cause a party!
Well, I will still come to your meeting.
You... Well, I should hope so.
Tomorrow's picture day.
Why are you taking his side?
Because it's important to him.
And when we signed the Roommate Agreement,
we made a deal.
Yeah, you keep talking like that,
you're gonna make color guard.
(GUN FIRING IN VIDEO GAME)
-Man, I'm worn out.
-(|ND|ST|NCT YELLING ON TV)
I know.
Imagine if we were actually moving.
No, it's just, ever since I started dating
Claire and Emily at the same time,
it's exhausting.
You're exhausted?
Try folding every five pages
in a pregnancy book,
so your wife thinks you read it.
But, dude, you're so lucky.
Getting to stay at home at night
with the woman you love.
-I guess I am lucky.
-You are.
Because dating two women...
I mean, I can't even remember
the last time I slept in my own apartment
lwake up and I'm like, "Am I at Claire's?
Am I at Emily's?
"Is there a third girl
I've forgotten about?
Like, "Where am I?"
-Hey, Raj.
-Hey, how's the mommy-to-be?
Good. A little tired.
| feel you.
I've been dating multiple women.
You sure you don't wanna come watch
Game of Thrones with us?
You guys have fun.
I'm just gonna snuggle up in bed
with a book.
Oh, that sounds great. A bed to yourself.
Can't even remember what that's like.
Are you up-to-date on Game of Thrones?
Mmm. lthink so.
Dragons, snow zombies,
and all the hot guys are dead.
Oh, I don't know.
Theon Greyjoy looks pretty good for a guy
who has genitals cut off.
Uh-oh, somebody's still pouting.
Leave me alone.
If it's because you lost a stick,
I know where it went.
Not funny.
You know you're gonna make up with him.
Can we just skip to that part?
Ch, of course,
because I'm the only adult around here.
Really? "The only adult"?
Yeah, that's right.
Tonight, I'll be watching a show
rated M.A.,
and that stands for
"mature audiences," buster.
Yeah, you would think the "only adult"
wouldn't let something silly
ruin our entire night.
And I'd think you'd understand
why I'm annoyed.
You... All of this could be avoided
if you'd just come to the meeting.
I don't want to.
Oh, it's just a meeting.
One simple meeting.
Stop saying "meeting"!
(SINGING GIBBERISH)
I brought my famous spinach dip.
No, Amy, just one second.
I'm not sure if I'm hoping
for a boy or a girl.
I mean, If it's a boy, I'm gonna have
to teach him to play catch, (CHUCKLES)
which means I'm gonna have to google
how to play catch.
(CHUCKLES)
And if it's a girl... (CHUCKLES)
I mean, they're so innocent,
and you know how guys are.
-Totally. Guys are the worst.
-(S|GHS)
Look at me.
I let Emily make me a frittata,
and I kept the leftovers
in Claire's fridge that night.
I'm such a dog.
(SIGHS)
There you go again.
I'm sorry.
Havel been complaining about it too much?
No, actually what you're doing
is pretending to complain,
but really trying to brag.
How could you say that?
(IMITATING RAJ)
"Oh, lwish I could enjoy a cup of tea
"without a naked girl
bouncing up and down on me."
I never said that.
"Don't you hate it when you can't remember
"whose bra it is
you found wedged in your couch?"
Okay, that I said.
But that's a real problem!
You give a girl another woman's bra,
and you will not
be having sex with her that night.
Maybe the other girl, but not her.
What's going on with him?
Oh, he's all bent out of shape about
having a Roommate Agreement meeting.
Apparently, perfect attendance
isn't cool anymore.
Don't worry, he'll come around.
Oh, I get why he's annoyed.
Oh, then you don't understand
what's happening.
See, Leonard refused to participate
in a mandatory quarterly
Roommate Agreement meeting.
This is what a generation raised
on Bart Simpson looks like.
You love The Simpsons.
I love Lisa Simpson.
Well, I know how he feels.
I never enjoyed
our Relationship Agreement meetings.
(GASPS) Wait. You were pretending?
Sorry.
No.
I don't believe you. No, I could tell.
"on, Sheldon,
"I never thought re-filing a matter
in a standing subcommittee
"could be so fascinating."
Hmm. What do you think?
You don't know?
Hey, did I say something to upset you?
No, I'm fine.
Really?
Because usually we walk side by side,
and | just went up two flights of stairs
staring at your bottom.
Just drop it.
Okay, I think | see what's happening here.
-You're jealous of me.
-Oh...
Please. What could you possibly have
that I would be jealous of?
It's not what I have,
it's how many people I'm having it with.
(DOOR OPENS)
Come on, Sheldon.
We'll watch Game of Thrones over here.
-Gladly.
-Good, go.
You know, it'll be nice to watch
an episode without someone saying,
"| read the books,
don't get too fond of this character."
It's not always because they die.
In one case,
it's because they've become involved
with underground tree people
from the dawn of time.
Yeah, but I won't say who it is.
lt's Bran.
What is going on?
Leonard's being ajerk,
so we're gonna watch over here.
Do you guys want to watch with us?
As long as I don't have to watch with him.
Fine.
I don't want to watch with you, either.
I'll go over here.
Why do you get to pick?
Okay, then you go there!
Don't tell me where to go!
Howard, just come in here.
Yeah, come on, Raj.
-Wait, did Amy make a spinach dip?
-She did.
And I'm gonna eat it all!
(DOOR CLOSES)
So what the hell happened?
Oh, ljust ran out of patience
with Sheldon's nonsense.
Tell me about it.
I've had it with Raj, too.
You know, like women,
men have a monthly hormone cycle.
Dips in testosterone
can cause irritability.
Interesting.
Well, maybe my male cycle
synced up with Raj's actual period.
lf Sheldon's testosterone dipped,
he'd become a butterfly.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Oh...
Maybe someone's here to apologize.
Hey, Leonard.
Stuart.
Uh...
This not a dress up party?
No.
Was it ever a dress up party?
Howard, didn't you tell me
it was a dress up party?
Yep. (CHUCKLES)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
l was told this is where to go
if I'm mad at Howard?
May I take your cloak?
Thanks.
This thing kept getting caught
in the chain of my bike.
Well, I'll catch you up.
Uh, Penny is angry at Leonard.
Leonard's angry at me and Penny.
l'm angry at Leonard and Amy.
Raj is angry at Howard.
And I'm angry at George RR. Martin
'cause there are no new books for me
to spoil it for Leonard.
So, what happened with you and Howard?
He says I was talking too much
about dating Claire and Emily,
and l accused him of being jealous.
I'm jealous.
Closest I've come to dating two women
was that time | dated one woman.
I don't know how you put up with it.
He's impossible.
I mean, holding a meeting to decide
what breakfast cereal we should buy.
Yeah. Cap'n Crunch with Crunch Berries.
Move on.
AnyWaY. Amy.
thank you for sticking up for me.
Oh, I honestly couldn't care less.
Sorry?
Well, | just took your side
'cause sometimes I get annoyed
at how close Sheldon and Penny are.
They argue all the time.
They aren't that close.
Who's always comforting him
when he's upset?
Penny, but--
Who's the only one who can make him
take his medicine when he's sick?
I try to hide it in his peanut butter,
but he spits it out.
Okay, and did you know she has him
add things to the Roommate Agreement,
so she can get her way,
and not fight with you about it?
Son of a bitch.
(LAUGHING)
Why is that funny?
I don't know. I like the pain of others.
Oh, well, then, you'll enjoy this.
Bernadette does the same thing
with you and Koothrappali.
No, she doesn't.
She defends him all the time.
She does not.
Who told you to stop making
all those Gandhi jokes about him?
Well, she did, and Human Resources.
Who do you think told Koothrappali
to go to Human Resources?
Son of a bitch.
(LAUGHING)
You're right. It feels good.
All right, it's almost game time.
Get it? Game of Thrones, game time?
Two women, huh?
(GAME OF THRONES THEME PLAYING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Oh, perhaps it's Amy coming to her senses.
What's up?
You know, you don't need to use Sheldon
to get your way with me
in a dumb Roommate Agreement.
-Where did you get that from?
-From Amy.
Oh, Amy, why did you tell him that?
Because you were defending Sheldon
like you always do.
-I don't always defend Sheldon.
-Oh, yes, you do.
You know you have a weird brother-sister,
Elliott-E.T. relationship with him.
What about your
weird relationship with him?
That's different.
I'm like the little girl in Poltergeist
and he's the creepy thing in the TV.
HOWARD: Um, guys,
were there any nuts in that food?
I don't think so, why?
Well, just a feeling. (CHUCKLES)
Oh...
It just said "ltalian sub."
I had no idea mortadella
has pistachios in it.
Interesting fact.
In Italian, the "morta" in "mortadella",
means death.
Sheldon.
I didn't say "fun fact".
I'm not a monster.
He's gonna be okay.
-(ALL SIGH)
-Now it's a fun fact.
Boy, stuff like this
really puts things in perspective.
Why are you dressed like that?
Oh, uh...
Howard thought it'd be funny
to tell me it was a costume party.
That wasn't nice.
No, but he almost died. So we're cool.
You know, if you think about it,
tonight was kind of like
a real-life Game of Thrones.
H ow?
Well, Howard eating that pistachio,
was like when King Joffrey got poisoned.
Okay, well, that was murder.
This was an accident.
Okay.
But you using Sheldon
to do your dirty work,
is like when Cersei
used the Kingsguard to do her bidding.
Cersei uses her body to manipulate men.
Pennyjust takes me to the Lego store.
Okay. Oh, how about this.
Stuart's dressed like a brother of the
Night's Watch, and they don't have sex.
-There you go.
-That's true.
-Makes sense.
-Fair enough.
-Hey.
-You all right?
-l'm fine.
Just a little embarrassed I had to be
carried down the stairs like a baby.
Thanks.
Let's get out of here.
That was scary.
Well, the important thing is,
I said that big sandwich
would ruin everything,
and l was right.
RAJ: Hey, Jon Snow!
How come your horse has a basket on it?
How come your head has your face on it?
They don't wear bicycle helmets
in Game of Thrones.
You're thematically inaccurate,
but I applaud your commitment to safety.
Don't you guys have anything better to do?
Better than watching a guy in a fur cloak
ride a girl's bike?
-Nope.
-(ALL CHUCKLE)
That's it!
You just lost bathroom privileges
at the comic book store.
Horse has a basket on its stupid...
(SCREAMS)
-(B|KE CLATTERS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(KNOCK|NG ON DOOR)
-SHELDON: Leonard.
Leonard.
What?
I never got to ask my question
about Batman.
What is it?
If Batman were bitten by a radioactive
Man-Bat,
and then fought crime
disguised as Man-Bat,
would he be Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Man
or, simply, Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Batman?
Is he still wearing the Batman suit
under the Man-Bat suit?
I'll be back.
English - SDH