NARRATOR:
Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
RAJESH:
Can I have your attention, please?
We're all here tonight because
we have no one to be with.
We gotta stop defining our self-worth...
...by whether or not we're in a relationship.
We are a community...
...and as long as we have each other,
we're never truly alone.
That was cool. What you said.
Thank you.
Uh, would you like to, uh,
get a cup of coffee?
Okay.
Later, losers!
So then I went to Cambridge,
which was wonderful...
...not only because it's a good school,
but because it totally looks like Hogwarts.
That's where I fell in love with astronomy,
and now I'm an astrophysicist at Caltech.
So I guess you could say, uh,
Raj is my name, and stars are my game.
And rhyming is also my game.
So, uh, two games.
Uh, anyway, that's enough about me,
I want to hear everything about you.
l have to go to the bathroom.
I go to the bathroom too.
Sometimes more frequently
than I care to admit.
I've had it checked out, it's nothing.
This is going great.
Mm. Can I have a refill on my chai tea?
Ah, yes, I have a good feeling about this.
I should have bought condoms.
Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun With Flags.
My apologies
that this episode is coming late.
I did shoot one last week
in honor of Black History Month...
...but I was informed by my roommate
that my spot-on portrayal...
...of George Washington Carver
could be considered "wildly racist."
My heart goes out to the members
of the African-American community...
...who, like me,
have been kept down by the man.
Now, Fun With Flags
is not just for the flag aficionado...
...it's also for the flag novice.
So to help me with that, please welcome
my friend, neighbor and flag virgin...
...not a real virgin.
She's had coitus many times.
Sometimes within earshot
of this flag enthusiast.
Once while he was trying to watch
The Incredibles.
Penny.
Hello.
So, Penny, I understand...
-...you'd like to learn more about flags.
-I can't tell you how many times...
...l've been at a party, everyone's talking
about flags and ljust couldn'tjoin in.
Well, you came to the right place.
I'm sorry, can we just pause for a minute?
What's wrong?
I think it'd look more natural
if you talked to me instead of the camera.
You know, like a real conversation?
It's something we work on
in acting class.
Interesting.
A few people in the Comments section
have said that my delivery is robotic.
Perhaps that isn't the compliment
it sounds like.
Let's try it again. Maybe this time
you could work on body language a bit.
When you're hunched like that,
you're shutting the audience out.
But when you're relaxed and open,
you're inviting them in.
Right.
And which one do I want?
Let's try open.
If our friend the flag has taught me anything,
it's to go where the wind takes you.
As long as you remain
firmly attached to a rigid pole.
And action.
[PENNY CHUCKLES]
So, Penny, what sort of flag questions
keep you awake at night?
Um, well, I'm from Nebraska.
So, what can you tell me
about the state flag?
Gosh, Penny...
...what did you have for breakfast,
a big glass of good question juice?
The Nebraska state flag
is simply the state seal on a field of blue.
Spread your legs, invite them in.
I'm telling you, something's wrong.
I can always feel it when Raj is in trouble.
Jeez, how close were you
before we got married?
Don't look under that rock.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
-Raj, you okay?
-You in there?
RAJ ESH:
Go away.
-Come on, buddy, open up.
-We're worried about you.
RAJESH: Oh, just because I stop
going to work and answering my phone...
...you think something bad happened?
Maybe something good happened.
Did something good happen?
Of course not, nothing good ever happens!
Whoa.
-What?
-Just whoa.
Smells pretty ripe in here.
You kind of feel it in your eyes.
Raj, what's going on?
l was humiliated by yet another woman.
You didn't kill her and chop her up,
that's not what we're smelling, right?
No, I took her for coffee...
...and she snuck out the bathroom window
to get away from me.
Oh, you poor baby.
I went and looked.
It was a high and tiny window.
She must've been very motivated.
I'm sorry, that's awful.
-But come on, you gotta shake it off.
-You can't stay in your apartment...
-...for the rest of your life.
-Why not?
With online shopping and overnight
delivery, I can get anything I want.
Look, I just ordered a case
of Dinty Moore beef stew...
...and two live lobsters on Amazon.
-Lobsters overnight?
-You're kidding. Let me see.
Well, I'll be. Look, you can throw in
a couple steaks and have a surf and turf.
Surf and turf sounds good.
See if they have corn on the cob.
Guys, we're trying to get
him out of here, not you in.
You're wasting your time.
Just please, leave me alone.
-Now what?
-I don't know.
We could go to Red Lobster
and talk about it.
We're all thinking it. ljust had
the decency to wait for him to leave.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
-Hello, Sheldon.
-H el lo.
How's the final stage of your
nicotine addiction study going?
[MONKEY'S GIBBERING OVER MONITOR]
Fine.
Just hold on.
Mommy's on the phone!
Sorry, we've cut the monkeys down
to one cigarette a day...
...so things are a little intense.
Makes me miss my marijuana-abusing
ﬂatworms. Those guys were mellow.
Good news, uh, the latest episode
of Fun With Flags is online.
-Oh, that's right. How'd it go with Penny?
-Much better than I expected.
She even gave me some helpful tips
about acting and body language.
Watc h .
Welcome to my world.
Not welcome to my world.
Welcome.
Not welcome.
Subtle but powerful.
I know, I'm still learning to control it.
Did you tell Penny how helpful she was?
Why would I do that?
Because she's your friend
and she did a nice job.
I'm sure she'd like to hear it.
All right.
I didn't mean now. Hello?
[MONKEY'S GIBBERING OVER MONITOR]
Yeah, yeah, you want a cigarette.
Well, I'd like a normal boyfriend. Deal with it.
Oh. Hey, what's up?
Um....
You need me to shut the door
so you can do your knocking thing?
No. I didn't start yet. It's fine.
Okay. So, what do you need?
Well, I was thinking about
you helping me out last night.
Penny.
And I just wanted to tell you, Penny...
...that the answer to the question,
"Who did a greatjob?" is you.
Penny.
-Really?
-Yes.
You were very natural
in front of the camera...
...and I found your suggestions
extremely helpful.
Oh, sweetie, you just made my day.
Okay.
My acting class is putting on a play Friday.
I can put you and Amy on the guest list.
Oh, that sounds terrible.
Why would I want to do that?
That's right,
they're no good without the lighter.
So much for your advice
on complimenting Penny.
Why, what happened?
She tried to rope us into going to her
acting class to see a play.
Don't worry, luckily I had the good sense
to drown that kitten in the river.
Sheldon, that's very rude.
She helped you with your show.
The right thing to do is reciprocate
by going to see her play.
Oh, so many crazy rules.
[MONKEY'S GIBBERING OVER MONITOR]
That better be Tootsie Rolls
you're throwing at me!
Penny.
Oh, yeah, much better.
What?
Amy pointed out to me that
since you did something nice for me...
...l'm obligated to do something
nice for you.
So, yes, I'll go to your dopey play.
-Hey, I don't want you to go anymore.
-Why not?
Go because you want to,
not because you have to.
Oh, dear Lord, more rules.
Where does it stop?
Can I want to go
because I have to want to go?
-Okay, do whatever you want.
-Yeah, but, no, wait.
Do whatever I want
or whatever I have to want?
Oh, for God's sake, just come to the play.
All right.
I don't want to
but at least that makes sense.
You know, I haven't seen Raj
in several days.
Is he no longer a part of our social group?
And if so, should we be
interviewing for a replacement?
Perhaps this time we go Latin.
He's just decided
he's never leaving his apartment again.
Oh. Brilliant.
I've been itching to pull that trigger.
He's upset because
he can't get anywhere with women.
Would it help ifl gave him some pointers?
I'm just funning you. Ha, ha.
Hi. I don't know if you remember me
but I was here the other night at your party.
Oh, yeah, you left with Raj.
LUCY: Yeah.
-You're the one?
Let me tell you something.
That guy you blew off
happens to be my best friend.
Okay? He was devastated.
Sorry.
Can you just give him this?
Okay.
But I gotta warn you,
Raj is a proud, passionate man.
lfyou go running out on him again...
...you're only gonna get like three or four
more chances before you are history.
Come on, she came back.
This is good news. You should celebrate.
I don't want to celebrate.
Not even a little?
We could have a pants party.
Go put some on.
Why would I want her number?
I want nothing to do with this woman.
-Come on, Raj.
-You don't get it.
I want nothing to do with any woman.
My heart is stone.
From now on, I am a monk.
l renounce all worldly pleasures.
Except for lobster.
And garlic butter.
Boy, I wanna tell you it's her loss,
but you are not making it easy.
You're a good friend for trying to help,
but I've made my choice.
All right, well...
...l'll see you around.
See you.
No, wait.
Take her number.
I don't want the temptation.
Okay.
I must be strong so I don't stray from
my true purpose: the study of the universe.
All right.
Thanks for ruining lobster for me.
RAJESH:
Wait! Give me the number!
Give me the number! Give me the number!
So, Amy, what's going on
with your addiction study?
Sadly I'm no longer associated
with that project.
-Why? What happened?
-Typical bureaucratic nonsense.
You can get animals addicted to a harmful
substance, you can dissect their brains...
...but you throw their own feces back at them
and suddenly you're unprofessional.
I'm sorry.
That I asked.
All right, let's get this stupid play over with.
Uh, hang on. Empty your pockets.
-Why?
-You know why. The Nintendo DS.
[e ROANS]
And the PSP.
Now the Game Boy.
Oh, for Pete's sake.
-Can we go now?
-Is that all of it?
Just set it down.
Just so you know,
this is not a stupid play.
A Streetcar Named Desire
is an American classic.
It's about streetcars?
Great. Then I won't need this.
Just a sec.
Oh, who says "just a sec"?
I hate myself.
Hello.
-Hi.
-Uh, would you like to come in?
Uh, no, I can't stay.
Oh.
I just wanted to say...
...l'm sorry for running out
of the coffee shop. That wasn't cool.
So yeah.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Can you at least tell me what went wrong?
It's okay, I can take anything.
Unless it's something I did, or said, or am,
because those are like my buttons.
No, it's not any of that.
It's just, I kind of have a hard time
around people I don't know.
Really? Then what were you doing
at the comic book store that night?
I've been trying to force myself
into situations I'm not comfortable with.
I saw the flyer in the store window
and I made myself go in.
I don't even like comic books.
-Yeah, me neither.
-What were you doing there?
I lied. I love them.
I only said that so you'd go out with me.
You don't want to do that.
I'm kind of broken.
That's great. I'm broken too.
-No, you're not.
-I totally am.
If it wasn't for this beer, I couldn't even
talk to you right now. I'm a wreck.
There are many things
seriously wrong with me.
And not quirks either...
...like, diagnosable psychological problems.
Maybe brain damage.
Well, how do I know
you're notjust saying that?
Go out with me on one date
and I promise you you'll see.
Okay.
Text me.
Bye.
You won't regret it.
I'm the most pathetic guy you've ever met.
And that, boys and girls, is how it's done.
You love her very much, don't you?
Yes.
PENNY:
I think you have great capacity for devotion.
You will be lonely
when she passes on, won't you?
I understand what that is.
MAN: To be lonely?
-She's pretty good, huh?
She is.
But when do they get to the part
about streetcars?
When I was a very young girl.
When I was 16 years old,
I made the discovery:
Love.
All at once and much, much too completely.
It was like you turned
a blinding light on something...
...that had always been half a shadow.
That's how it struck the world for me.
But I was unlucky.
Deluded.
-She's remarkable.
-She really is.
Our Penny's a star.
How can she remember all those lines...
...but as a waitress, she can't remember
no tomato on my hamburger?
[English - us - an]