PENNY: Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
I guess I'm still wondering
if Emily and I are right for each other.
Does this have to do with that girl
you had coffee with?
You mean the strong, sexy angel
I can't stop thinking about? Who can say?
I need to come up with a big idea
to make some money.
-There's no reason you can't.
-That's easy for you to say.
You and Sheldon already came up
with your supen‘luid helium model.
That's just research,
we're never gonna make any money from it.
Forget helium. The real supen‘luid
is the fruit punch in this mug.
Reminds me of my daddy's
secret don't-tell-mamajuice.
Maybe that's an idea.
Guidance systems for drunk people.
They have that, it's called Uber.
Hey, in your super-cooled
helium experiments,
did you create quantum vortices?
-Yeah, Why?
-Well, if you made a guidance system,
couldn't you use those vortices
as a gyroscope?
Never thought about that.
And since it's in a quantum state,
it would maintain an infinite persistence.
Groundbreaking revelations,
tropical drinks, tell me
this isn't like the best episode
of Sex and the City.
Okay, I gotta ask.
Why are you wearing a bow tie?
Well, I've never applied
for a patent before.
I wanted to make a good impression.
Is the impression
that your first name is Pee-wee?
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, well, you're an engineer.
End ofjoke, burn.
Come on in, fellas.
See, he's not wearing a tie.
Well, he's a patent attorney,
maybe his tie is pending.
So, I've reviewed your paperwork.
It seems like we've got everything we need
to file a patent
for your infinite persistence gyroscope.
-That's great!
-Exce||ent.
So what happens next?
Well, the legal team needs to review
existing patents to avoid overlap.
Oh, I don't think there will be.
Yes, we did our own search, so...
That's nice, but I think ours
might be a bit more thorough.
(CHUCKLES) Get a load of this guy.
Can you imagine
if we make money with this?
Well, if we do, I am splurging
on the best sinus irrigator money can buy.
That old sad story, guy gets
a little money,
-goes straight up his nose.
-(CHUCKLES)
Just need you to review
and sign this document
acknowledging that you understand
the university will own 75% of the patent.
Seventy-five percent?
That's outrageous.
I mean, this is our idea
based on our research.
How can you possiblyjustify
owning a majority share?
It's university policy.
I know when I'm beat.
Hold on, hold on.
So the three of us do all the work
and only end up with 25%?
Dr. Hofstadter, this university's been
paying your salaries for over ten years.
Do you think we do that
out of the goodness of our hearts?
Well, until you just said
that mean thing, kind of.
And as far as Mr. Wolowitz is concerned,
I'm afraid as a federal employee
on loan from NASA,
your name can be on the patent, but...
You're not entitled to an ownership share.
Wait, so this can turn out to be
a financial success and | get nothing?
Well, sometimes they give you a plaque.
Well, that's not fair.
We should all get plaques.
Sorry, but we can't sign this.
Come on, let's go.
Thank you for your time.
A couple of questions about the plaque--
(THEME SONG PLAYS)
So, have you been having
any morning sickness?
A little, and it doesn't help that I have
this heightened sense of smell.
What, is that a pregnancy thing?
Yeah. The other day | sniffed out
where Howie hid the Girl Scout Cookies.
No more Tagalongs, my ass.
But now you'll be able to make
your own milk to eat the cookies with.
Hey, guys. Hey, Penny,
I really appreciate you helping me
with this. I don't know what to do.
-Sure, let me see it.
-See what?
I hadn't spoken to Emily
since I broke up with her,
and she left this
on my doorstep with a note.
"Raj, I got you this before we split up
but couldn't return it
"and thought you'd like to have it.
Happy belated Valentine's Day, Emily."
That's nice.
"Nice," or is she trying
to manipulate him?
I know. I mean, do | open it?
Do | return it?
Why wouldn't you open it?
Well, she was pretty mad,
for all I know it's a voodoo doll of me
with afork stuck in myjunk.
You don't think she'd actually send you
something gross or dangerous, do you?
I know one way to find out. Sniff this.
She's pregnant, she's not a bloodhound.
Although I am getting
a little machine oil, I think it's metal.
Come on, just open it.
You know, on Game of Thrones
Balon Greyjoy received
his son's genitals in a box.
Oh, never hurts to have a spare.
(BLOWS)
-BERNADETTE: What is that?
-Wow!
It's an antique sextant.
Sailors used these
to find their positions by the stars.
What a nice gift for an astrophysicist.
I know, she's so thoughtful.
See, she's trying to get you back.
Now that is exactly
what I would've gotten you
if I had any idea
what it is or what you do.
You know, I...
I have too much self-esteem
to let this girl guilt me
into getting back together with her.
You don't need to be pregnant
to smell that load of crap.
(SIGHS)
Well...
What if we go around the university
and just get the patent ourselves?
We can't. It says on their website
as long as we work there,
they have a controlling ownership
of anything we come up with.
Great. So they own my idea for a T-shirt
that says "Dumb as a Bag of Geologists."
Well, our choices are
we do this with the university
or we don't do it at all.
Either way, I get nothing.
Or if we end up making money from this,
Sheldon and I could
split our shares with you.
To be clear,
Leonard's referring to the gyroscope,
not the T-shirt and mugs.
Oh!
Now they own the mugs.
I guess that is a way around this.
You guys would be cool doing it like that?
Of course,
we would split any profits three ways.
-l'm fine with that.
-Okay, great.
It sounds like a contract
might be in order.
Sure, we could write something up.
But which one of us
should be the party who--
You can do it, Sheldon.
So stipulated!
Once I found a stash of contracts
under his bed, it was weird.
I wonder how much she spent on this.
Ooh! Let's find out.
It doesn't matter,
it's the thought that counts.
Yeah, yeah, and beauty's on the inside,
size doesn't matter. How much she spend?
Seriously, guys, I don't wanna know.
Oh, my.
Well, come on, you can't say,
"Oh, my" and then not tell me!
These things go for $500 and up.
Damn. All I got for Valentine's Day
was a postcard saying
my Vermont Teddy Bear was back-ordered.
Okay, so she drops off a $500 gift
and she's not trying
to get back together with you?
Maybe you're right.
Or she's telling the truth
and just being nice.
Maybe you're right.
Wow, I am easy to manipulate.
Guys, it's Emily. What should I do?
Okay. Answer it.
Just be strong, and if she starts to cry,
don't make any promises,
and most importantly,
put it on speaker so we can hear.
-He||o.
-EM|LY: Hey, it's Emily.
Is this a good time?
Yeah, yeah, sure. What's up?
Was it okay I left that gift?
I'm really hoping we can be friends.
Maybe, maybe.
Um, you think you'd wanna
grab a cup of coffee?
Hello?
I'm sorry, I seem to be taking
an annoying amount of time
deciding how I feel about this!
I just... I miss hanging outwith you.
It's not like I lost a friend,
it's like I lost my best friend.
(SOBBING) Is there any chance
you'd wanna come over?
I'm sorry.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Okay.
I'm just, I'm having a really hard time,
but that's not your problem, that's mine.
I won't bother you again,
but please know that you'll
always have a place in my heart.
(GAGGING)
Bye, Raj. You're a good guy.
Goodbye, Emily.
(EXHALES)
That was rough, you guys.
I know, but you did it.
I'm so proud of you.
(SIGHS) Well, anyway,
I'll leave you to your girls' night.
Are you sure you
don't wanna stay here with us?
No, I kind of
feel like being alone right now.
Well, if you change your mind,
we'll be here.
Thank you.
Say hi to Emily for us.
Will do.
Yeah, this contract looks good to me.
I'll say it looks good.
It's in my proprietary font, Shelvetica.
I wanna say something obnoxious,
but it is easy on the eyes.
I'm a little tired, Howie,
you ready to go?
Yeah, one sec.
ljust need to sign this contract.
What is it?
Well, we ran into a problem
about my share of the patent,
so we're forming a partnership
to split anything we make equally.
Sheldon, did you draft the contract?
You bet I did.
You're gonna make out so hard tonight.
So, you're just gonna sign this
without having a lawyer look at it?
Excuse me, I've been drafting contracts
since kindergarten.
Didn't need a lawyer to get me
out of finger painting,
don't need one now.
I know, but--
Bernie, the guys were nice enough to find
a way to keep me from being cut out.
Well, I should hope so.
The whole thing was your idea.
Well, to be fair,
Howard's idea was based on Sheldon's math.
Guys, everyone is involved in this, okay?
Howard's invention, Sheldon's math,
my original theory that space time
was like a super-cooled liquid,
which I'm sure Penny would've mentioned
if she wasn't working on
that hangnail right now.
What?
-Honey, this is fine.
-Okay.
You wanna sign a contract
that Sheldon whipped up, go ahead.
Can I talk to you in the hall?
-Sure.
-Excuse us.
Hey, Leonard.
What?
If she doesn't think
that we should apply for this patent,
she's being patently absurd.
Good one.
Okay, you got it.
See, I was afraid it was a thinker.
What are you doing?
| just wanna make sure
you've thought this through.
What's to think about?
We have an invention
and wanna move forward.
Howie, you're about to form
a legal partnership with Sheldon Cooper.
All right, if you're gonna
calmly make excellent points
then I don't know if I wanna talk to you.
Okay, I get it.
And it's sweet that you're worried
about me, but I can take care of myself.
I'm not worried about you,
I'm worried about me.
I don't wanna go through this pregnancy
listening to you complain about Sheldon
driving you crazy
more than you already do.
Here we go with the ironclad logic again.
You've tried to work with him before,
it hasn't gone well.
Why is this time gonna be any different?
Is the fetus helping you?
'Cause that's cheating.
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
-He||o.
-Hey, Raj. It's Claire, how are you?
Hi, I'm good. Really good.
Well, I don't know why I said
"really good," I'm just regular good.
| reallyjust wanted to sound confident.
And that "really" was a real really,
not a fake "really"
like the first "really."
Really?
I don't know,
I lost track and I missed my exit.
So, uh, so what's up?
Well, last time we talked I had just
gotten back together with my boyfriend
and I wanted to let you know
that things didn't work out.
Really?
I'm sorry, I swear I know other words.
So if you were still interested--
Yes! Indeed. Absolutely. Indubitably.
I'm not even sure what the last one means,
but it's another word and I know it.
So, when do you wanna meet up?
Um, I'm almost off work,
what are you doing now?
Right now? Well...
Well, actually, to be completely honest,
I'm stopping by to see my ex-girlfriend
because she's having a tough time,
but it's not like
we're getting back together or anything.
Let me guess,
the worst part about breaking up
is that she doesn't have
her best friend to talk to anymore?
That's exactly what she said!
How do you know that?
I'm a girl,
that's like page one out of the playbook.
Any chance
you could send me a PDF of that playbook?
Been out there awhile.
Hope everything's okay.
I wonder what they're talking about.
If you guys would shut up,
I could tell you.
Oh, be cool, be cool, be cool.
-Hey.
-He||o.
Hey. You guys all right?
Yeah. But, um, we were talking and...
I'm a little concerned about
the three of us forming a partnership.
Are you suggesting
a limited liability corporation?
'Cause I did not L-L-see that coming.
Sheldon, my concern is not with the money
or anything, it's with how you treat me.
Well, I believe
I'm treating you generously.
That's why I've stipulated
in the contract that your contributions
to our invention
are as valuable as my own.
Are you saying that his contributions
aren't as valuable as yours?
No, I'm not saying that,
because I kept saying that this morning
and Leonard said stop saying that.
See, this is what happens
every time we work together.
You know, hang on. What if Sheldon
had no choice but to be respectful?
What? Is there a switch on the back
of his neck we don't know about?
No. What I'm saying is,
you could add a clause to the contract
that he can't make fun of Howard.
How would you enforce it?
Oh, please, any contract I sign
is enforced by my own personal code
of ethics.
-And his obsessive-compulsive disorder.
-Yeah, that, too.
And scoot over,
part of your shadow is on my spot. Move.
Howard, what do you think?
I'm on board.
Good. I'll add it right now.
Oh, baby, it's addendum time!
(LINE RINGING)
-EM|LY: Hello?
-Hey, Emily, listen.
I've been thinking and I'm not sure
it's a good idea that I come over.
Oh.
(CRYING) Okay, I understand.
No, no. Please don't cry.
Okay, I'll stop!
-He||o?
-Hey, so listen, Claire, change of plans.
Fine, do what you want,
but she's playing you.
I don't think so,
she sounded pretty upset.
You mean like, "I wasjust really
looking forward to seeing you."
"I'm having such a rough day."
Emily, listen.
I'm sorry, but I can't come by.
Why not?
I think we both know if I come over
we're gonna get back together and--
I told you I needed afriend.
What do you think is happening here?
Can you right back.
The revisions I made start on page four.
That is a lot of "whereupons."
You should see
the Valentine's Day card he gave me.
"Article three.
As it pertains to this project,
"Dr. Sheldon Cooper
promises to abstain from all insulting
"or disrespectful language
directed toward Howard Wolowitz,
"including but not limited to
mockery of engineering, his height,
"his hair, his wardrobe
"and his insane belief
that the Ghost Rider movie
"was, quote, 'Not that bad."'
Hang on, maybe there should be
a no insult clause about me, too?
-Do you still like cilantro?
-Yeah.
You're tying my hands here.
All right, let's sign this.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are these changes on page six?
Sheldon, what did you do?
lshould've known.
"Twenty-five percent of profits
due to Sheldon Cooper
"will be allocated to a scholarship fund
"for the first born child
of Howard and Bernadette Wolowitz."
Sheldon, that's so nice.
That beats the onesie
I was gonna get them from babyGap.
That's very generous, Sheldon.
Oh, I've always valued education
over money.
And the very fact that you needed
a written guarantee of respect
made me realize how dismissive
I've been of your contributions.
I appreciate that.
And ljust hope that this scholarship
can rescue your child
from the subpar education
and menial life of an engineer.
-She|don.
-What? I didn't sign it yet.
I hear what you're saying,
but I've known Emily a long time
and think she deserves
the benefit of the doubt.
All right, it's your life,
but you know how this is gonna end.
As a matter of fact, I do.
I'm gonna comfort her
because I'm a caring and decent friend
who's happy to be there
when she needs someone to talk to.
Good talk.
English - SDH