PRESENTER:
All right! Let's bring out our panelists.
Please welcome our science
consultant, Dr. David Saltzberg...
All the writers ofThe Big Bang Theory,
including executive producers
Chuck Lorre, Steven Molaro and Bill Prady.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
And please welcome
our special guest moderator,
you know him best
as Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali,
please welcome Kunal Nayyar!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Hi!
Surprise!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
How is everyone doing in San Diego?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Welcome to Comic-Con.
-(PANEL|STS LAUGHING)
-Although, yeah, no.
-Yeah, welcome to Comic-Con.
-(PANEL|STS LAUGHING)
Um...
We are so excited to be here.
Uh, we love our fans,
our show would be nothing without you.
So, thank you so much.
Thank you so, so much for being here.
This means the world to us, thank you.
-(AUD|ENCE CHEERING)
-(PANELISTS APPLAUDING)
Um...
So we're gonna have a lot of fun today.
I thought we'd start by me asking
them some embarrassing questions.
And then we'll open up some
to the audience
and we'll see what happens, all right?
-(AUD|ENCE CHEERING)
-Um...
All right, so...
Let me take my jacket off.
-(PANELISTS LAUGHING)
-(AUD|ENCE CHEERING)
That's all that's coming off. Relax.
(CHUCKLING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
David Saltzberg,
who is our science consultant rock star,
who makes sure that everything is correct
and still gets a thousand
hateful e-mails a day for...
-(ALL LAUGHING)
-Um...
You were really nervous about the topic
of Leonard and Sheldon's paper, correct?
DAVID SALTZBERG: That's right.
KUNAL NAYYAR: Can you tell us why?
The writers asked me to come up with a
discovery for Sheldon and Leonard
and it would have to be
a signiﬁcant discovery.
So I, I thought about it quite a bit
and we came up
with something related to
superﬂuid vacuum theory
and the space-time of the universe
and I added a little bit,
which I thought was kind of cool,
about surface tension,
which had not really been used before.
So I thought this was really, pretty good.
And I, and I submitted it.
And I get the scripts, you know,
each time a few more pages,
and the next time I got the script,
[saw that one of the people in the show
who will be reading the script
was Professor Stephen Hawking.
At which point,
I had a little bit of a panic attack.
(ALL LAUGHING)
My fear was that
he would look at the script
and say, "I'm sorry,
I actually can't agree to be in the show, "
which luckily didn't happen.
On the upside,
I was hoping he would think
it's a brilliant idea and write a paper.
Um, I'm still waiting for that.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Funny, quick story about Stephen Hawking.
When Stephen Hawking
came on set for the ﬁrst time,
uh, he came to watch a run-through
and Simon Helberg, Wolowitz,
had to do the voice
in the scene in front of Stephen Hawking.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
And all of us are doing the scene,
but we're secretly looking at Stephen
Hawking from the corner of our eye
to see how he would respond
and he was, uh,
-he was smiling, he was loving it!
-He loved it.
CHUCK LORRE: Should I tell the time...
I directed the ﬁrst scene
with Stephen Hawking and Sheldon
and there was no
weirder moment in your life
when you look
at Professor Hawking and say, "Action. "
(ALL LAUGHING)
Again, Stephen Hawking
has a good sense of humor.
NAYYAR: Yeah, you're lucky
he has a good sense of humor.
Last season, we heard Amy's fan ﬁction
and I just want to know
what inspired that.
We had become aware
that there was quite a bit
of Big Bang Theory
fan ﬁction out there in the world.
And one day
in the writers' room, we looked it up
and started reading it...
So, I mean, is there gonna be any
Koothrappali fan ﬁction
or anything like that?
Wouldn't that be amazing?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
I think that might be a better
question for the woman who plays Amy.
Ah! You wanna ask her?
Hey, Mayim, you wanna come out
and answer that question for us?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(AUDIENCE CONTINUES CHEERING)
NAYYAR:
Mayim Bialik, ladies and gentlemen!
Surprise!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING)
STEVE MOLARO:
And, um, since you were asking about
fan ﬁction for you, the writers and
I took the liberty the other day
of writing some
Koothrappali-Amy fan ﬁction.
And I happen to have it here,
if you wouldn't mind giving this a read.
Yeah, are we standing together
and doing this?
-We'|| stand together.
-(LAUGH|NG)
-Can you hear like this?
-Yes.
-Can you hear?
-AUD|ENCE: Yeah!
(CLEARS THROAT)
So say your lines into the mike
-'cause it's a big, it's a big audience.
-I will. Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Let me just warm up for one second.
(ALL LAUGHING)
"Amy looked at Koothrappali
"peering at the stars
through his telescope.
"She had always thought of him
as a friend,
"but now something was different.
(ALL LAUGHING)
"She'd spent her life studying the brain,
"but she had a feeling tonight
"this swami of love...
(ALL LAUGHING)
"...was going to teach her
about another organ.
(ALL LAUGHING)
"He looked up from his telescope,
"met her longing gaze and said..."
"'Have you ever read Fifty Shades of Grey?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
"'I'm about to introduce you
to ﬁfty shades of brown. "
-(AUD|ENCE CHEERING)
-(ALL LAUGHING)
"Am y replied,
"'That doesn't make sense.
"'Grey was the main
character's last name. '
(ALL LAUGHING)
"Koothrappali pulled her close
and said..."
"'That kind of semantic nitpicking
"'is going to get you a spanking.'"
(ALL LAUGHING)
Oh, my!
"'Then Ishould point out
that semantic is the wrong word,
"'you sexy beast from the third world. '
(ALL LAUGHING)
"He whispered into her ear..."
"'Forget about Shamy.
"'Tonight you and I will be a sweaty
tangled mass of Koothrapamy.'"
(ALL LAUGHING)
"In that moment, Amy wondered
what she had seen in Koothrappali.
(ALL LAUGHING)
"She knew who she needed to be with,
"the sexiest people of all...
"Television sitcom writers."
(ALL CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING)
LORRE: That was great.
Oh, man!
We got to take a question
from the audience,
-I'm sweaty.
-(ALL LAUGHING)
I don't know, I don't know if we want to
answer your question directly
right, right now,
but I can tell you that the answer
will be
in the premiere episode of Season 9.
BIALIK: It will?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Well, a partial answer.
You know, from the actor's point of view,
in all honesty,
we don't get the scripts
until the night before.
So we tape on a Tuesday night
in front of a live audience
and Tuesday night we get the script
that we're gonna start on Wednesday.
And it's really exciting,
and to be completely honest,
almost nine years in, every Tuesday
night still feels like Christmas.
Because you open the script
and, in the ﬁrst few seasons,
it was like, "Okay,
how many scenes am I in?" You know?
And now it's really become,
like, "What's happening in the story?"
And that's a testament
to how these characters have grown
and how incredible these writers are.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING)
DAVID GOETSCH: Sometimes lunch is late.
It's terrible.
MOLARO: I think one
of the biggest challenges for us
is that any of those episodes
where there are big, heavy, uh, moments,
like, when Sheldon told Amy
"I love you" for the ﬁrst time
or these kinds of things.
So, we, you know,
we care about these characters deeply
and it's very important to us
that we get those kind of moments right.
And I think that's when the stress levels
probably raises up to the highest,
when we're in the middle
of those kind of scenes.
But there's also the challenge
I think in writing comedy,
which is you want characters
to do bold, funny things,
but you have to show that
the bold funny things are reasonable.
You have to show that it's the reasonable
next step in the progression
and sometimes that can be difﬁcult.
And ifyou don't do it right,
then the characters just seem crazy.
NAYYAR:
I have a question for you guys, then.
When you're pitching jokes in the room,
do you pitch them as the characters?
-MAN: You're asking if we do your accent?
-Yeah.
MARIA FERRARI: Only for you.
-Really?
-No, really. Really, only for you.
I know Bill does
'cause Bill has a good Indian accent.
So you pitch the jokes in the accent?
PRADY: (IN INDIAN ACCENT) Of course.
That's how you would know
how they would sound.
Thank you, Arnold Schwarzenegger.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Kevin Smith
was on the show this past season
and, uh, he was supposed
to be coming to the
run-through, the rehearsal for that week,
and that morning my assistant said
you know, "Kevin wants to know if it's
okay if he could bring his friend, "
and Isaid, "Who is his friend?"
and she says,
"I don't know. Some guy named Jay. "
And I ran down the hall
saying, "Oh, my God!
Silent Bob is bringing Jay today!"
So, you either
knew what that meant
and you lost your mind
or you didn't care,
-but I know you were very excited...
-I lost my mind.
I remember
when, uh, Billy Bob was on
and we were all, you know,
we were in the scene with him
the ﬁrst day of rehearsal
and we're, like, nervously doing the scene
and he's also nervously doing the scene
and then he stops
in the middle of the scene
and he looks at us
and he says, "I can't believe I'm here. "
Because his mother loves the show so much
and got him hooked on the show
that he was watching it.
And he was doing a scene
with me and Simon and it's like...
And he couldn't believe that it was real
and we couldn't believe that he was real.
(ALL LAUGHING)
That was, that was fun.
That was a fun moment for us. Um...
PRADY: Billy Bob Thornton was one of the
nicest people that we ever met
and he came and he worked very hard.
And then after the show
when we tape on Tuesday nights
there's pizza and beer backstage
and people sort of hang out,
and if people have brought friends,
then they meet people and stuff like that.
And Billy Bob stayed until...
He kind of closed the place.
They're, sor'ta, you know,
turning the lights on
and playing Closing Time...
FERRARI: We also had Nathan Fillion on.
PRADY: Oh, yeah!
He 's dreamy.
I had met Nathan Fillion
previously at a Golden Globes par'ty
and it was, like, pretty deep into the
party and I was feeling super brave.
(LAUGHING) [was like,
(IN RASPY VOICE) "Hey, Nathan Fillion,
Firefly was a good show.
(ALL LAUGHING)
"And someday
I'm gonna make a million dollars
"and buy it and make
both our dreams come true. "
And he was really nice,
but then he came on the show
and so I kind of walked up and I was like,
"Hello, Nathan Fillion,
it's nice to meet you for the ﬁrst time!"
(ALL LAUGHING)
And it's great, 'cause it turns out
celebrities, if you meet them,
they don't remember.
So it, like, doesn't matter.
NAYYAR: Or so they say.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Um, so we did the episode where, um,
we had to shoot an alternate—
A different ending to
the Skywalker Ranch episode
when, um, Jim and Johnny
end up at Skywalker Ranch
and we shot the ending
and then a week later
we had to shoot a different ending.
Do you want to talk about that?
That was an interesting story.
You wanna discuss the ending
that didn't air?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, Imean, I'm just reading it
from the pages that you guys gave me.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Sorry.
If you don't see me
next season, you'll know why.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Um...
The ﬁrst ending that got shot,
um, we found out at the end
that Sheldon had stolen a Iightsaber
-from Skywalker Ranch.
-From Skywalker Ranch.
And I just... I was deeply troubled.
I just... No. The character couldn't...
Couldn't commit what was,
essentially, a felony.
He had stolen something
that has real value.
So we came back a week later and...
I don't even remember
what the other ending was,
but, but no,
Sheldon was never going to become a felon.
(LAUGHING)
As long as I'm engaged in this show,
I just... That character can't
possibly commit a crime like that.
So that was, I think,
how the second ending came about.
What was
the second ending, now? Do you remember?
STEVE HOLLAND: His sense of smell
was still burned off from being tased
and Leonard, I think,
was having him sniff magic markers
to see if it was coming back.
MOLARO: So I have a ques...
So, uh, when Sheldon stole
the print of, uh, Indiana Jones
from the movie theater and then
ran down the street, is that not a crime?
We have to go rewrite that one again too.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Mayim, I have to ask you a personal
question that's on everyone's mind.
How is it to kiss Jim Parsons...
(LAUGHING)
On The Big Bang Theory?
Um... (CHUCKLING)
(STUTTERING)
It's, Imean, Idon't, it's...
(ALL LAUGHING)
It feels weird to qualify it,
like, it's great, you know, I think, um...
-You know, whenever...
-MAN: Details, Mayim,
I think, is what they want.
I think, whenever...
NAWAR: We're not looking
for a philosophical answer here.
Well, you're gonna get one. Whenever...
You know, whenever
Sheldon and Amy
have intimacy, it's usually very speciﬁc
and it's very, um...
It's very, um,
it's very gently placed and, you know,
that scene that was
in the reel of us opening a scene kissing,
even Jim and I felt so strange about that
because our kisses have never been, you
know, kind of, like, makeout-y,
you know, and even that, um, we both know
how to kiss differently
than our characters do,
but, you know,
I remember Mark Cendrowski, our director,
you know, he... We tried it
a lot of different ways, you know.
-At one point I was...
-(ALL LAUGHING)
NAWAR: You're welcome, audience.
MOLARO: Oh, my!
No, at one point,
I had my hand on his shoulder,
and then Mark wanted, like,
a little bit of movement,
but not, you know, very elegant movement.
So I think for me and Jim,
kind of everything we do that's intimate,
you know, including that,
it's very crafted.
You know, we're never
cavalier about that.
NAWAR: Tongue or no tongue?
(ALL LAUGHING)
NAWAR: It's funny,
for two characters who haven't kissed,
he sure spanked you a lot.
Is that on your little piece of paper?
No, no, no. That was all in here.
It's really fun
being an actor on this show too,
watching the other actors in scenes
because we're also
such big fans of each other.
And on a personal note,
watching... You know, Mayim and Jim
are also wonderful, wonderful,
close friends off stage,
but watching their scenes
together is electric.
So even in rehearsals,
we'll just sit and watch their scenes
and it's really, truly...
We become fans, you know,
to watch the scenes
between them. It's really fun.
-Thank you.
-PRADY: But, Mayim, you and Jim
have a very particular...
I'm not making a joke,
you have a very particular
process that is interesting to watch.
Could you talk about how you and Jim,
sort of, work through and
decide how to play a scene?
Um, yeah, Imean, what's interesting is,
you know, Jim is
a classically trained actor
and I'm an untrained actor,
but what's kind of neat is that
we have a very similar way
that we go about
approaching scenes
and approaching our work
and we work well together
which, I think, you know,
is very important,
especially for, you know,
as Steve indicated,
things that are heavy and delicate,
especially for a character like Sheldon's
and then, you know, Amy
as his kind of counterpart.
Jim and I are very, very careful
about how we do things,
we talk a lot about it.
You know, some actors don't talk a lot
and that's ﬁne and that's their
process, but Jim and I do talk a lot.
Um, we wonder sometimes
why the writers make decisions,
we have conversations of, "Gosh, did
you think we were ready for this?
"I didn't expect this. "
And even with, "I love you"
Jim and I were both very,
we were very surprised
that we were there, you know.
Even the ring,
we have those conversations,
and, to me, I think
that adds to the complexity
of the interactions as characters
because when
[have to tell him [need time off,
you know, that had
all of those conversations
that Jim and I had had behind it.
"Is this right, is it not right?"
Um, so I think it's really,
it's part of what makes our
communication as actors well is that
as people we're interested
in the same things about those characters.
We talked about them
as being brilliant minds
without the paranoid schizophrenia.
One of the things
that I remember very much,
being around people like this
and being a person like this,
is the celebration of difference.
And the acknowledgment
of difference and the celebration of it.
And, um, we talked about that,
that these characters
celebrate who they are.
You know, I get asked this kind of thing,
a lot and I feel like,
um, much as there is this sort of notion
of, like, geek chic and, you know,
that, maybe, our show
has had some part in showing that.
I think what our show demonstrates
is that all kinds of people can have full
lives and relationships and friends
and we don't need to
pathologize everyone,
that's not what we do,
but I think what our show
also shows is that
it still can be lonely to be different
and some of my most favorite moments
are when [see the writers
have Sheldon have that experience.
So, you know, when people ask me, like,
"Oh, you guys make, you know, nerds cool. "
It's still really hard to be different
and especially for young people,
if you have interests
that are not aligned with popular culture,
it's still lonely
and I love when Sheldon expresses that,
that he does not understand
some interactions and it's painful to him.
And I think that's kind of, you know,
the beauty of what our writers do.
They show all sides of that.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
PRADY: Let's let Mayim take this...
Mayim's not taking this one!
(LAUGHING)
Why, why would E. T. and Jesus ﬁght?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Wouldn't they be on the same page?
Superman
is vulnerable to magic.
Wouldn't godly powers
be technically under magic?
(ALL LAUGHING)
We'll get back to you.
And when Thor...
Historically, when Thor fought Jesus...
(ALL LAUGHING)
He, he lost.
He lost. Northern Europe
converted to Christianity.
(ALL LAUGHING)
-(|ND|ST|NCT TALKING)
-PRADY: Give that to Saladin.
Saladin is our engineer.
"Why are engineers
bad ?" is your question.
He hates what he doesn't understand.
-(ALL LAUGHING)
-(AUD|ENCE APPLAUDING)
PRADY: I thought that's
because Sheldon likes science.
(LAUGHTER)
Whoa! It's on.
I have a question...
We did something very cool,
it's not even a question, I just think
it'd be fun to bring up
that we did something very cool with UCLA.
Chuck, if you
wanna talk about that for a few minutes?
That would be nice.
Oh, yeah. We started this scholarship,
for kids going into STEM
educational paths
-at UCLA.
-You wanna explain what STEM is?
STEM is science, technology,
engineering and math
and this started a couple
of years ago, actually,
when we noticed that
there was a trend in
United States and in England
where kids were pursuing
the hard sciences
and one of the reasons
they were doing that
was they were watching the show.
And that was stunning.
When this started
at my kitchen table 10 years ago,
we never imagined
that people might make life choices
based on what we were doing.
And, uh, so it seemed
like a natural progression
to "Let's... Maybe we can help. "
So, uh, I think we have a little over
$4 million in a fund and...
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
This fall at UCLA
there'll be 20 Big Bang Theory scholars
starting in UCLA.
And we get to hang out with them and
stuff and I think if we do it right,
it'll go on, it should go on
in perpetuity.
-So we gotta keep doing this.
-Yeah.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING)
(CLEARS THROAT) I think that
Amy had really longed for all this.
She didn't have friends. She didn't have
a Penny, she didn't have Bernadette.
And after a lifetime of loneliness
and craving that, she had access
to somebody who could put her
on the fast-track
and with that came
these desires for a boyfriend
and all those other things
came along with it.
And, you know,
like all the characters on the show,
they have grown, as have
Sheldon and Amy and their relationship.
-So...
-Yeah, I think, Sheldon really needed...
He really needed a reason and a, you
know, a speciﬁc person or event
that might lead to some, you know,
catalytic reaction in his existence.
But yeah, I think that's exactly it.
Amy absolutely was wanting a life
with something more than herself.
And it all came quickly, as it were,
and it's taken much longer for Sheldon.
We honestly didn't know
what we were doing at all.
We truly had no idea what we were doing
and I think it's pretty much well known
that the ﬁrst try
was an absolute, colossal miss on our part
and we got lucky
and we got a chance to do it again.
I think most of you in the room
know what Chuck is referring to,
that there was a ﬁrst
Big Bang Theory pilot that never aired,
that never made it onto the network
and then they got
another opportunity to do it.
PRADY: In your opinion, Kunal,
what was the biggest problem
with the ﬁrst version of the pilot?
Oh, me and Simon and Kaley weren't in it.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I think he's right.
This is a wonderful invention
by a man named Sam Kass,
who is a computer programmer
and he had put it online.
In the ﬁrst episode where it was used,
the reference to Sam was cut and we made
sure when we referenced it again
that the characters said,
-"All hail, Sam Kass..."
- Yes.
...to acknowledge this wonderful gift of a
thing that we found on the Internet
-and Jim learned it...
-Yeah.
NAWAR: I was in that scene with Jim.
I was in that scene with Jim.
Probably did not more than four takes?
Probably, I mean,
Jim's a genius. He really is a genius.
PRADY: Jim is really good
at memorizing things like that
in some kind of strange,
supernatural, superpower way.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
MAN: You see why we wouldn't have said,
like, "Soft Tur'tle" for example, right?
PRADY: Is there an animal
you think would have been better?
MAN: Soft Porcupine was tossed around.
Soft Porcupine wouldn't have worked.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Do you guys wanna sing Soft Kitty?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
I don't know the words,
so please, take it away.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(ALL SINGING) Soft kitty, warm kitty
Little ball of fur
Happy kitty, sleepy kitty
Purr, purr, purr
We love you guys so much!
We love you so much! Thank you!
Thank you so much for being here.
Have a wonderful weekend.
Be safe. Love you.