NARRATOR:
Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
We were worried about you.
Don't be melodramatic.
I'm just getting on a train
and leaving forever.
A few things don't go your way...
...and your best decision is to
ride the rails like a hobo?
Leonard, I am overwhelmed.
Everything is changing
and it's simply too much.
I need to get away and think.
-Sheldon.
-Yes?
I'm gonna miss you.
Of course you are.
-You just made that easier.
PENNY: Mm-hm.
Excuse me.
Is it at all possible
that you're knitting a pair of pants?
Oh, no. You're understandably terrified.
You know, allow me to explain.
Forty-five days ago...
...um, I embarked on
a railroad journey of healing...
...because my university
was making me do string theory...
...my favorite comic book store
burned down...
...and when my roommate got engaged,
my girlfriend wanted to move in with me.
Which was no doubt a ployjust to see my...
...well, excuse my language,
but my bathing suit parts.
Sir, may I use your phone?
I don't think so.
I understand that I'm half-naked...
...but there is a reasonable explanation.
While I slept in my sleeper car...
...all my possessions were stolen.
Now, typically, I wear pajamas...
...butl recently adopted a hobo lifestyle...
...and pajamas are
the sleep-pants of the man.
I'll have you know
Mahatma Gandhi wore no pants...
...and a nation rallied behind him!
My good man, now, before you walk away,
I know that I may appear deranged...
...but I am, in fact,
a world-renowned physicist.
Ask me the difference between
a boson and fermion. Go ahead, ask.
Bosons have integer spin.
Fermions have half-integer spin.
My legs are getting cold.
Why won't anybody help me?
-Morning.
-Hi. Want to do yoga with me?
Uh, let me just have some coffee first...
...and then I'll have the strength
to tell you how much I won't be doing that.
[PHONE RINGING]
-Hello?
-Hello, Leonard.
Hey, buddy. Good to hear your voice.
I'm in Kingman, Arizona...
...and, uh, I need you to come pick me up.
I'd love to, I'm just about to
do yoga with Penny.
Leonard, I'm at the police station.
I was robbed.
They took my phone,
my wallet, my iPad, everything.
-Oh, my God. Are you okay?
-No, I'm not okay.
I'm wearing borrowed pants...
...I don't have ID...
...and one of the officers here
won't stop calling me Chicken Legs.
Okay, I'll come get you.
-What's the address?
-Hey, what's going on?
-He got all of his stuff stolen.
SHELDON: 2530 E. Andy Devine Ave.
-Okay.
SHELDON: Hurry.
Sheldon, hang tight.
Hey, do you want me to bring anything?
Yes, please. A pair of pants.
And my toothbrush.
And my mail. And a really good
comeback for Chicken Legs...
...because, "I know you are, but what am I?"
was met with stony silence.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
-Is he okay?
-Yeah, he's fine. He's just a little rattled.
-Feel like driving to Arizona?
-I can't. I have thatjob interview.
-Right.
-Besides, I don't need six hours of:
"Your hair is different.
Why did you change?
I'm holding my breath
until your hair grows back."
All right, fine.
Can you think of a reason
I shouldn't invite Amy to come with me?
-No.
-Come on, you didn't even try.
-Thanks for the lift.
-What's wrong with your car?
I'm having my windows untinted.
Why?
I got a hot girlfriend now.
I want the haters to know.
What are you talking about?
No one's paying attention to you.
Wow.
How's that Haterade taste, bro?
Hey, this isn't the way to work.
I just want to pop in
and make sure Ma's okay.
-I thought Stuart was looking after her.
-He was.
But now that her cast is off, he moved out.
And, honestly, I'm kind of glad.
It was getting a little weird.
-How so?
-I don't know.
They're chummy.
Like us?
No, not like us. Creepy chummy.
Like you and your dog.
She feeds him out of her own mouth?
I mean, he calls her Debbie,
she calls him Stewie...
...and they're all giggly around each other.
And believe me, when food goes
in that mouth, it does not come out.
So are you worried because
he's replacing you as a son...
...or are you worried because
he's becoming her lover?
First of all, no one can replace me as a son.
I'm her little matzo ball.
And secondly, my mother is well past
having any kind of sex life.
Okay, okay.
-Although, many older women lead vibrant--
-I said, well past it!
Excuse me, Officer Hernandez.
Any leads on the person
who stole my belongings?
-Not yet.
-Perhaps I can help.
Sherlock Holmes always says,
"When you eliminate the impossible...
...whatever remains, however improbable,
must be the truth."
Now, have you tried doing that?
Nope.
Well, maybe you should.
There's lots of books
called Sherlock Holmes...
...and there's no books
called Ofﬁcer Hernandez.
Thanks again for coming.
Six hours was gonna be
a long drive by myself.
My pleasure.
I'm not angry that
my boyfriend was in trouble...
...and called you instead of me. I love that.
Yeah, time's gonna fly by.
I haven't been on ajob interview in years.
-l'm really nervous.
-Don't be.
You are built for pharmaceutical sales.
You're cute, you're flirty and....
Started that like there were
gonna be three things.
I don't have any experience in sales...
...unless you count
the bikini carwash I did in school...
...but you already made me
take that off my résumé.
This job is a lot like being a waitress.
Except, instead of pushing fish tacos
because they'll go bad...
...you're pushing our antidepressants...
...before the FDA finds out
they may cause rectal bleeding.
They do?
Maybe.
Like our lawyers say, "The world is full
of things that can cause a rectum to bleed."
I talked you up to Dan.
He'll be interviewing you.
Ugh, I really appreciate this.
ljust hope I'm not in over my head.
-You'll be fine. Just be yourself.
-I wish I felt more confident.
I wouldn't put you up for this
if you couldn't handle it.
-Thank you, but maybe I should cancel.
-lt's too late to cancel, you're going.
But I don't know anything
about pharmaceuticals.
Oh, I understand. You wanna
do something you're already good at.
I know, why don't I get you ajob...
...at the sitting around all day
wearing yoga pants factory?
They're comfortable.
Ma, I hope you're decent. Raj is here.
You just started seeing naked women again...
...and I don't want you to be confused
about where the boobs should be.
Oh. Hey, guys.
What are you doing here?
Uh, what are you doing here?
I thought you moved out.
Oh, yeah. I was going to.
And then Debbie and I got to talking
over dinner the other night.
I didn't have any place to go,
she likes having me around...
...so we both said, "Why leave?"
At the same time. Ha-ha-ha.
Yeah, it was precious.
It's not that precious, heh.
I'd like to back you up,
but it sounds like it was pretty precious.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Stewie, I can't find my glasses.
Be right there, Deb-Deb.
Oh, they're probably on her head.
[CHUCKLES]
Or in her neck. Listen.
You staying here seems like
something she would've talked to me about.
Well, maybe if you called your mother
more often, you'd know.
[SCOFFS]
Wouldn't kill you to pick up the phone.
[CHEWING LOUDLY]
Any word on my stolen items?
We're doing everything we can.
You know, Sherlock Holmes liked to
use cocaine to sharpen his focus.
But I'm sure those
Cool Ranch Doritos are doing the trick.
Sheldon.
Leonard. Oh, I'm so happy to see you.
-Are you okay?
-Oh, I'm fine. Why did you come?
What do you mean, why did I come?
You're my boyfriend.
I haven't seen you in over a month.
ljust drove six hours to help you out.
Don't you have anything to say besides,
"Why did you come?"
I do, but I feel uncomfortable saying it
out loud in front of these police officers.
Fine. Whisper it.
[WHISPERS]
Shotgun.
So, Sheldon, tell us about your trip.
Where'd you go?
Where didn't I go?
I went to New York, Chicago, Atlanta...
...Denver, Seattle.
How were they?
Oh, I have no idea.
I never left the train station.
Hang on. You traveled across the entire
country and never left a train station?
Why would I?
That's where all the cool trains are.
I'm sorry. So you never went outside?
Or had a single piece of fruit.
So why do you think you'd make
a good pharmaceuticals sales rep?
Well, I'm a people person.
People like me.
Some of my favorite people are people.
I feel like I'm saying "people" a lot.
People, people, people-- Okay, I'm done.
You sure?
People. Yes.
Good. Ahem. So how do you feel
your previous job experience...
...has prepared you for a career like this?
Uh, well, as a waitress,
sales was a big part of myjob.
Believe me, I convinced a lot of
very large customers...
...who should not be eating cheesecake
to have more cheesecake.
I mean, one of those chubsters
even had an insulin pump.
l have an insulin pump.
People.
It's weird, right?
A grown man in his 305
living with my mother?
That is weird. I thought he was, like, 45.
-Come on, you don't think it's a little odd?
-I don't know.
She's lonely, he needs a place to stay.
I doubt there's any funny business going on.
And even if there was, who cares?
They're both adults.
Who cares? You wouldn't care
if I slept with your mom?
You know what? You're my best friend
and she's in a bad marriage.
I give you my blessing.
This is stupid. I'm just gonna
call my mother and be honest with her.
Because that's what little matzo balls do.
[LINE RINGS]
STUART: This is Debbie.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: And this is Stuart.
[BOTH LAUGHING
ON ANSWERING MACHINE]
BOTH :
Just kidding!
STUART:
Leave a message!
[MACHINE BEEPS]
[WHISPERS]
This is the part where you talk.
All right, let's say a physician was
prescribing one of our competitor's drugs.
How would you convince them
to switch to ours?
Um....
Any chance his car needs to be
washed by a girl in a bikini?
Okay, I'm really sorry for wasting your time.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks for stopping by.
Okay, than ks.
Um, I'm sorry--
Listen, could you do me a favor...
...and not tell Bernadette
how badly I blew this interview?
She'll get upset and honestly,
I'm a little terrified of her.
-Wait, you're scared of Bernadette?
-Yeah, kind of.
I thought it was just me!
No, no. Everyone thinks she's so nice
with her squeaky little voice.
I know. But she's kind of a bully.
Well, she is.
I didn't even want to meet you,
but I was too scared to say no to her.
Me too.
One time, I had-- Whoa, ha, ha.
I had to tell her
we were cutting research funding...
-...for one of the drugs she was developing.
-What happened?
I couldn't do it. She's still working on it.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oh, we're not gonna
tell her about this, right?
-Oh, my God, no.
-No.
At the hot dog stand
in the Denver train station?
Heinz ketchup.
The hot dog stand
in the Salt Lake City train station?
Heinz ketchup.
The hot dog stand in
the Indianapolis train station...?
I don't care.
Wrong. Hunt's.
Hey, Amy. What do you say? You ready
to move on to the mustard round?
Have you not noticed
that I've been sitting back here...
...quietly stewing for the past two hours?
I just thought you were bad at the game.
I'm mad at you.
How could you go away
without even saying goodbye...
...and then call Leonard for help
instead of me?
Amy, may I please have a moment
of privacy to speak with my roommate?
We're in a moving car.
What do you expect me to do,
stick my fingers in my ears?
l was thinking put your head out
the window like a dog, but that'll work.
Please. This'll be quick.
Leonard, as soon as we get home...
...I want to have coitus with Amy.
Okay, she can't hear.
The reason I called you is because...
...I didn't want Amy to know
I couldn't make it on my own.
What's the big deal?
Of course it's no big deal to you.
You idolize me and nothing could ever
knock me off that pedestal you put me on.
It's true. You are a god to me.
-Can I stop now?
-Just tell her.
I called Leonard because I failed...
...and I didn't want you to think less of me.
You were worried about that?
Yes.
Sheldon.
It's okay with me that you're not perfect.
Can I have one more moment
with Leonard?
Sure.
Amyjust hurt my feelings.
I want to break up with her.
I never thought I'd say this,
but I'm kind of excited to see Sheldon.
but Penny got ajob today.
-She did?
-Well, the only reason she got it...
...is because the guy
who interviewed her loves me.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[CLEARS THROAT]
What do you want?
I, uh, kind of got the feeling...
...you might not be okay
with me staying at your mom's.
You're right, I'm not. I think it's weird--
-Howie.
-It is. He's a grown man.
He's just gonna live there rent-free?
How is that gonna motivate him
to get off his butt and get ajob?
I mean, do you even have a plan?
Hey, you're not my father, okay?
And besides,
your mother and l were talking--
-"Your mother and I"? You're not my father.
-I didn't say I was your father.
-Calm down.
You're not his father, he's not your father.
Nobody is anybody's father.
I'm sorry you don't like
my life choices, but it's my life.
Well, it's my house, it's my rules.
Oh, ho! Okay, Dad.
lfl mow the lawn, can I have my allowance?
Don't take that sarcastic tone with him.
-I don't have to listen to you.
-Don't talk like that.
That is my mother--
Wife. My wife. I said my wife.
You know what?
This isn't getting us anywhere.
When you're ready to apologize,
you know where to find me.
Yeah, in my house!
STUART:
That's right, sucker!
lwish I'd never gone on that trip.
I feel no better now than when I left.
-But you still accomplished something.
-Yeah.
If you had told anyone you were going
on a train by yourself across the country...
...do you know what they would've said?
-That I couldn't do it?
LEONARD: Exactly.
Right after they said, "Yeah!"
But you did do it.
So what if it didn't all go your way?
That's what makes it an adventure.
That's a good point.
You know, I'm a lot like Gandalf the Grey.
He fought the Balrog and emerged stronger
than ever as Gandalf the White.
l was robbed of my phone and pants
and I, too, came back stronger.
And whiter too, because I wasn't in
direct sunlight for six weeks.
See? This trip was good for you.
Indeed.
l was the world's smartest caterpillar.
And then after pupating
in our nation's railway system...
...l have burst forth
as the world's smartest butterfly.
A butterfly could've gotten
himself home from Arizona.
Yeah, I feel renewed.
I'm ready to deal with
any changes that come my way.
-Hey. Look who's back.
-Hey.
Your hair is different. You changed
your hair. I can't take this. I'm out.
-Like to see pictures from my trip?
-I thought your phone got stolen.
It did, but luckily, all my photos
got backed up to the cloud.
And you thought they all had a silver lining.
Here, day one.
This was the seat I was going to sit in...
...but didn't because there were
cracker crumbs on it.
And as it was first-class, I suspect Ritz.
This is the train bathroom.
This is the lmodium I took so I would
never have to use the train bathroom.
I can't believe you traveled the country
and never left the train station.
I know. You know, I almost died
in afire in Des Moines, but I stayed put.
FYI, that's when the lmodium gave out.
[English - us - an]