-This is an easy one, you love this guy.
-Me.
Come on.
He's an underappreciated genius...
Still think it's me.
It's not you. Now think.
There's a car named after him.
Of course there is.
The Mini Cooper, because it's me.
How about this?
He's a poor man's Sheldon Cooper.
Oh, Tesla.
-Hi.
-Hey, how'd it go?
Not fun. The doctor shoved
a camera up into my sinuses.
Yeah, I watched. It was like
the scary boat tunnel in Willy Wonka.
-They figure out what's wrong?
-lt's a deviated septum.
The surgery is simple.
He's gonna do it next week.
Why would you have surgery?
Because I can't breathe.
And I snore, I get sinus infections....
Back off, he's all mine.
You don't have a life-threatening condition.
Why would you take the risk of surgery?
Sheldon, it's a routine procedure.
I've heard you complain about his snoring.
Yes, for the first five or six years,
but I've gotten used to it.
It helps me sleep.
He's like my mucus-powered
white-noise machine.
Sheldon, I'm gonna get the surgery.
It's no big deal, end of story.
-Very well, I'm done talking about it.
-Thank you.
-I believe it was your turn in the game.
-Okay.
Let's see. Oh, this person
is most famous...
...for never having gotten his nose
mutilated with elective surgery...
...and never living his life
in the shadows...
...as a hideous disfigured freak.
I think you could give a better clue.
I don't. I'm not even sure
if that's a person or a typo.
[SNORING]
Okay, why?
I'm listening to you snore.
I'm wondering how
I'll ever sleep without it.
If it helps you sleep,
then why are you sitting here...
...staring at me
like the albino boogeyman?
Really, Leonard, insults?
After I spent two hours in your closet
waiting for you to fall asleep?
-What's your problem?
-If the surgery is successful...
...the snoring is gone.
And if you die during surgery...
Sounds like either way
I finally get some rest.
l have to be honest with you, Leonard.
I'm truly worried.
Okay, I told you,
there's nothing to worry about.
I've been doing some research,
and I've learned that 1 in 700,000 people...
...die from general anesthesia.
Buddy, do you realize that also means
699,999 people don't die?
I suppose that's true.
You're such a glass half-full kind of guy.
I'm going to miss that.
Oh, so my parents' 40th anniversary
is coming up...
...and I can't think of a thing to get.
Damn. Can you imagine being married
to someone for 40 years?
Not anymore.
Anyway, any ideas on a gift?
What are some of the things they like?
They liked going to
the Mumbai Symphony...
...but last year, my mom thought
they were phoning it in.
Then my dad said, based on their love life,
she should know about phoning it in.
-He said that?
-They weren't speaking...
...so he had a servant say it to her.
Oh, maybe I could make a gift for them.
I know how much you guys love
the coasters I made for you.
They're yours in the divorce.
Hey, what are you working on?
Remember when I said
if you went through with surgery...
...there was a1 in 700,000
chance of dying?
[SIGHS]
-Yeah.
-Well, I've been crunching the numbers...
...and so far, I've gotten
your probability of death...
...all the way to a sphincter-tightening
1 in 300.
Great timing.
My "check sphincter" light just went on.
Leonard, what if you have
an allergic reaction...
-...to the surgeon's latex gloves?
-l'm not allergic to latex.
Then why don't you wear the gloves
I bought to do the dishes?
For the same reason
I don't wear the apron or the hairnet.
Fine. What about epilepsy?
I don't have epilepsy either.
No, you don't,
but the surgeon might. Hm?
And your carotid artery
is just one shaky scalpel away...
...from becoming the dancing fountain
at Disneyland.
Sheldon, do you realize
that driving is riskier than surgery?
I do. I have the drive
to the hospital right here.
That is, if you make it to the car
without falling down the stairs.
And don't expect me to carry you,
I do that enough in life.
Buddy, I get that you're worried about me,
and I appreciate that...
...but I'm not going to die.
You don't know that.
I do know that it won't be
from an asteroid strike.
You know who else said that?
Every cocky 1'. Rex currently swimming
around in the gas tank of your car.
If there was an asteroid strike,
wouldn't you die too?
I don't know. I'm smart and scrappy.
I think I'd find a way.
Tell you what, the surgery's not for a week.
I'll think about it.
Thank you.
And while you're thinking about it...
...if you have the surgery in Nicaragua
during monsoon season...
...I can guarantee your death.
Yes. Okay.
I understand.
Of course, yes. I'll call you tomorrow.
Bye.
So I found this fencing school
in Burbank...
...that has a Jedi class.
If you're cool being the only adults there,
they said they are.
Dude, my parents just split up.
-What?
-Uh, that was my dad on the phone.
He moved out.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
If you're not up to it,
we don't have to go out.
-We can just hang here.
-No, it's fine.
It's not that big a deal.
As long as they're happy, I'm happy.
And when I get to see them
for the holidays...
...I get to celebrate Diwali twice,
one at each house.
That's double the Diwali.
-You sure you're okay?
-l'm okay.
-You don't look okay.
-How can I be okay?
I come from a broken home.
Doctor said I should be
out of surgery by 10.
Okay. And Sheldon really believes
we're at a public swimming pool?
He was so busy figuring out
how many parts per million of urine...
...we'd be floating around in,
he didn't even question it.
Eighteen parts per million.
And he's still doing it.
Don't worry about it.
I'm happy to take you to work.
Well, thank you.
And Leonard never lets me
have French toast sticks in the car.
I can't have syrupy fingers...
...but he can do the backstroke
in a toilet bowl.
It's nice they're getting exercise.
Although, now that I think about it...
...Leonard would never go swimming
in public without his swim shirt.
-l'm sure he brought it.
-No, but last year at Magic Mountain...
...he got such a bad sunburn,
we had to cut him out of it.
He probably got a new one.
Finish your breakfast.
There's an entire section of my dashboard
that doesn't have any syrup on it.
You're acting odd. Why?
I'm odd all the time, everyone knows that.
Just last night I tried to see how many
fava beans I could fit in my mouth.
-Tell me the truth.
-Twenty-eight.
-Come on.
-Fifty-six.
Amy. What's going on?
All right.
Don't get upset...
...but an earlier appointment
opened up for Leonard...
...and he's getting the surgery right now.
Take me to Leonard.
-Just go to work. He'll be fine.
-Amy, he's my best friend.
And if you don't take me,
I'm going there anyway.
Fine.
-lt's sweet that you care about him so much.
-I do.
I couldn't forgive myself
if something happened to him...
...and I wasn't at his bedside to say,
"I told you so."
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA]
-Hello.
-We had a really nice swim.
Oh, stop it.
I assume this medical center's
treated the bums on your bottom...
...from the recent pants fire.
-Because I'm a liar, liar?
-That's for the fire marshal to determine.
-You had to tell him?
-He wore me down.
And I was distracted.
He has on extra baby powder today.
-Is he okay?
-He's still in surgery.
[SHELDON SIGHS]
-Very well.
-He's gonna be all right.
That is sticky.
Let's talk about something
other than the surgery.
That's a good idea.
Penny, did you and Leonard...
...ever discuss funeral arrangements?
I think she meant something
a little happier.
I suppose we can try
to make it a celebration...
...but he died so young.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
-Knock, knock.
-Hi.
-Hey, what brings you guys by?
-Oh, muffin much.
Told you, not funny.
Well, he's just not laughing
because he's feeling blueberry.
Tough crowd.
-l'm sorry. This is very sweet, thanks.
-So how you doing?
Better. I guess the news just hit me
a lot harder than I expected.
Well, of course. I would be devastated
if my parents split up.
Why? Your father barely speaks
to your mother. Heh.
Well, at least he stuck around.
Not like your dad, who just took off.
As you can see,
we're here to cheer you up.
Sorry, Raj. Do you have any sense
of what happened with your folks?
I think over time,
they started to resent each other.
Instead of talking about things,
they kept it bottled up...
...and the hate just grew.
It's a shame they spent
all that time unhappy...
...but sometimes,
there's muffin you can do about it.
You get it, right?
Well, it's nice you got him that.
Oh, this isn't for Leonard. No.
Amy bought it for me.
He stubbed his toe on the revolving door
on the way in.
You know those confounded things
make me dizzy.
Who told you to keep going around?
There was a large plant in the lobby.
It kept looking like the outside.
When Leonard comes out,
he's not gonna feel great...
...so please don't give him a hard time.
Penny has a good point.
This is like the man in the supermarket
with the goiter on his neck.
Whatever you're thinking,
just keep it to yourself.
It was like a grapefruit.
And I'm sure he knew that...
...before you held a grapefruit
up next to it.
Well, I'm not making any promises.
Not only did Leonard take
what I feel is an unnecessary risk...
-...he deceived me.
-The reason he deceived you...
-...is you were a pain in the ass.
-The reason I was being a pain in the B...
...is because I was worried
and no one else was.
-Really? You won't even say A?
-You bet your sweet B I won't.
Obviously I care about Leonard. I'm
gonna spend the rest of my life with him.
And I'm not?
[RUMBLING]
-lt's an earthquake. I knew it.
-Sheldon, it was just a little tremor.
A little tremor that turns
routine sinus surgery...
...into a frontal lobotomy.
Oh, I don't care for this at all.
I need to see he's okay.
-Sheldon, you can't go back there.
SHELDON: Try and stop me.
[THUDS]
AMY: Are you okay?
SHELDON: Why didn't you stop me?
Can I tell you something?
This whole thing with Raj's parents...
...just got me a little worried about us.
What are you talking about? We're fine.
And Raj's parents probably split up
because of Raj.
What?
They always say the children
aren't to blame, but....
Heh, come on.
I'm notjoking, Howie.
You heard what he said about his parents.
It was the little things
they kept bottled up.
I don't want that to happen to us.
How can I convince you it won't?
Well, is there anything about me
you're keeping inside?
Heh. I'm not answering that. It's a trap.
So there are things you don't like.
And here I am in the trap.
You just keep talking,
I'm gonna chew my leg off.
Just tell me one thing that bothers you
and I promise I won't get mad.
Okay. The truth is...
...sometimes you're too beautiful.
Howie, be serious.
Okay, okay.
I really don't like how your wings
poke me when we sleep...
...because you're an angel.
Okay, fine. Maybe it was a bad idea.
I just don't think the secret to a happy
marriage is to criticize each other.
Although, there are ways
to improve our communication.
One thing I learned
when l was in couples therapy was--
-Who were you in couples therapy with?
-Not important.
-Was it your mom?
It was your mom.
Anyway, the therapist
had us tell each other...
...what we loved about one another.
Oh, that's so sweet. I wanna do that.
Okay.
Okay. Um, I love that you make me laugh.
Thank you.
And I love that you're strong
and independent.
And yet, I still love
when you hold a door for me.
I love that I'm kind of a slob
around here...
...and, heh-heh, you're okay with that.
Uh-huh.
And I love that I work and do
all the cleaning and you're okay with that.
See, I am. Isn't this great?
Come on, smile.
This is gonna be my Christmas card.
[IN NASALLY VOICE]
You know, this is all your fault.
How is it my fault?
I told you not to get the surgery.
Okay, first of all, the surgery
was a success.
Secondly, I didn't want you there.
Wow. I don't know which hurts worse,
my nose or my heart.
I'm done speaking to you.
Don't be like that.
You two need to talk this out.
Yeah, because you sound really funny.
[PENNY LAUGHING]
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about the surgery...
...but you were worried about nothing.
Oh, you're hardly out of the woods.
You still run the risk of infection,
a blood clot...
...the possibility that an inattentive surgeon
let a barn spider lay eggs in your nose.
The minute you sneeze web,
I'm moving out.
I never thought I'd say these words,
but come on, nose spider!
You were so panicked
Leonard was gonna die...
-...you'll never leave him.
-Sheldon will move out eventually.
Yeah, once he figures out
how to work a door.
l was not panicked.
And I am not overly attached to Leonard.
You were so worried that you smashed
your face trying to check on me.
You love me.
Tell me those aren't the words
of a man with a spider eating his brain.
Amy, you're a neuroscientist.
Crack his skull open,
spray some Raid in there.
I love that you take pride in your looks.
Even when l have to pee...
...and you're in there
spending an hour on your hair.
I love that you're too good to pee
in the kitchen sink.
I love that you have
the confidence to speak...
...even without giving it
an ounce of thought.
I love how your hair
is always on the soap.
It's like washing myself with a hamster.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey, guys. Sorry I am so late.
l was on the phone with my mother.
-How is she?
-Pretty good.
She bought the book Eat, Pray, Love...
...and used it to set
my father's Mercedes on fire.
So, what's up with you guys?
We're just saying all the things
we love about each other.
Oh, like you and I did at couples therapy.
-What'd you get?
-Oh, I ordered it before your surgery.
It's the um I was going to put you in.
Okay, that's morbid. Send it back.
I can't send it back. I had it engraved.
"Here lie the ashes of Leonard Hofstadter.
He thought he was right,
but his roommate knew better."
[LEONARD CHUCKLES]
That's funny.
Boy, I'm gonna miss these painkillers.
Hey, why did you get two?
-"l'm with stupid."
-Oh, that one's mine.
[English - us - an]