PENNY: Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
Well, there's no point dwelling on it.
As the Vulcans say...
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
-Do you know what that means?
-No.
You telling the truth?
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Well, this is ridiculous.
Being upset about Amy all the time
isn't accomplishing anything.
If I wanna resolve this situation,
then I need to take action.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to find her
and ask her to marry me.
And if she says yes, we can put this
behind us and resume our relationship.
If she says no, well, then she can just...
(SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
He didn't mean that.
(INAUDIBLE)
I think it's so adorable
you're making Sheldon breakfast.
Well, he's having a rough time.
Amy broke his heart,
the DVR cut off the last minute
of Doctor Who.
That crow followed him home.
Aren't you worried you're making
French toast on oatmeal day?
Oh? Well, what's this? A pot of oatmeal?
Or thanks to you, what I will
now call "gloatmeal"? (CHUCKLES)
Oh, I don't want credit for that.
Dr. and Mrs. Hofstadter,
lovely to see you this fine morning.
-You're in a good mood.
-I am indeed.
I have decided, instead of
wallowing in sadness about Amy,
it is time that I find myself
a new female companion.
-Ah, good for you.
-What brought this on?
I realized something.
When Amy was in my life,
I was hyper-focused on my work
and ignored her.
And you don't want to make the same
mistake with the next woman?
No, I need a new woman
in my life to ignore,
so I can hyper-focus on my work again.
Hey, I made French toast sticks.
-On oatmeal day?
-Ah, I also made oatmeal.
Oh, that's a lot of carbohydrates
for a man on the prowl.
You know what? You eat it, you're married.
It doesn't matter what you look like.
Don't take advice from a man
who threw his shoe at a crow.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
-Thank you for coming by, gentlemen.
-No problem.
So, what's up?
It was the two of you
who found Amy Farrah Fowler for me.
Now that I'm looking
for my next girlfriend,
it seemed only logical
that I employ your services once again.
You sure you're up for that?
She did hurt you.
Oh, no, it's all right. |think of my time
with Amy as a stick of Fruit Stripe gum.
Sweet and enjoyable at first, but
ultimately a flavorless lump of sadness.
You're not wrong about Fruit Stripe.
I was always a Hubba Bubba man.
Hubba Bubba over Dubble Bubble?
You're crazy.
Hey, the jaw wants what it wants.
Gentlemen!
Oh, right. Uh, girlfriend.
(STAMMERS) What are you looking for?
All I'm looking for is an educated,
intelligent woman who shares my interests,
while retaining
her own unique point of view.
She should be kind, patient,
and most important,
unable to imagine life without me
by 10 o'clock tonight.
Isn't that a little unreasonable?
Ah, fine. She doesn't need her own
point of view. Now, chop chop.
Come on, Amy! Show us the dress!
AMY: Okay, but I'm really stepping outside
of my comfort zone here.
Uh...
I don't think any of your comfort zones
are showing.
It's your third date,
maybe you could go more sexy.
Well, some people think
the sexiest organ is the brain.
No one ever bought me drinks at a bar
because my brain just
popped out of my shirt.
Do you have any heels higher than this?
He's pretty tall.
Ooh, tall! Finally some details
about this mystery man.
Yeah, come on. Tell us more.
Well, I told you his name and that
he's tall. What more do you need?
-Did you kiss him yet?
-Just a little peck on the lips.
(BOTH SQUEAL)
Well, we're your best friends.
Give us one more detail
and we promise we'll leave you alone.
Fine. Um, he's British.
(BOTH SQUEAL)
(CHUCKLING)
All right, that is ajuicy one!
All right, where's
Tall British Dave taking you?
Tea and basketball?
-To that new Italian place on Walnut.
-Oh, nice.
-l'm gonna go look for other shoes.
-Oh, good luck.
I threw out all my ta|| ones
when I married Leonard.
Hey, you wanna swing by that place
tonight and get a look at this guy?
We don't even know what time
they're gonna be there.
I'll just call the restaurant, pretend
I'm Amy and check the reservation.
Damn, you're sneaky.
Yeah, but I'm little, so it's adorable.
I think the quickest way
to find you a new girlfriend
is just to get you on
every dating website out there.
Are you sure?
I've heard that on those sites,
often when you think
you're corresponding with someone,
it's actually a computer program
pretending to be a real person.
And you're afraid
it'll do a betterjob than you?
Excuse me, no one does a betterjob
pretending to be a person than I do.
Siri comes close, but I know more jokes.
Well, if you don't want to use
dating websites, what do you suggest?
Off the top of my head?
Prospective women
weed themselves out in a battle of wits
until only one champion remains,
she shows up at my door
flush with the thrill of victory,
and then sits quietly by my side
while I watch Daredevil.
You seriously think women
would fight for you?
People compete forjobs and trophies,
why not me?
He's right. He knows a lot ofjokes.
No, but it is basic human nature.
If we present him as a prize,
maybe they would.
Well, he's smart,
he's a respected scientist.
And I have the soulful eyes of a cow.
-(SCOFFS)
-I don't know if I'd say you... Oh.
I have an idea. What if we put
a post on Craigslist that says,
"World-class Caltech physicist
seeking girlfriend.
"If interested, solve the following
puzzles for a chance to meet him."
Oh, we'll make the puzzles
extremely challenging
to eliminate unworthy candidates.
Oh, we can set it up like a scavenger hunt
where the last puzzle gives the winner
Sheldon's contact information.
This is actually
an interesting social experiment.
I'm a little jealous of the people
who get to do it.
Me, too, and we've seen the prize!
I don't understand why we're leaving
so early for the movie?
Oh, I forgot to tell you,
we're gonna meet up with Bernadette
to spy on Amy and her date. (CHUCKLES)
What? I don't wanna do that.
And you think I wanna see a documentary
about aluminum can recycling?
This is the movie that Big Soda
doesn't want you to see.
Yeah, it's the movie
your wife doesn't want you to see.
So, you're actually okay with invading
your friend's privacy?
-You're not curious who she's outwith?
-Not really.
But you're curious about aluminum cans.
You're a weird little guy.
That's it. The Sheldon Cooper
Girlfriend Challenge is officially live.
(CHUCKLES)
-Congratu|ations.
-This is exciting.
Right now, somewhere,
a woman is dividing the atomic weight
of the best noble gas
by the number of colors
in the oldest national flag still in use--
Then using that number as
the average speed to calculate
-the travel time from Mordor to the Shire.
-(CHUCKLES)
And taking her first step towards
a lifetime of laughter,
love and best of all, rules.
I hope we didn't make
the puzzles too hard.
Well, if she can solve them,
it'll prove she's intelligent,
tenacious and so socially awkward,
she has nothing better to do
on a Saturday night.
(LAUGHING)
Golly, she sounds too good to be true.
This is fun.
I haven't dated much since my divorce.
Well, I'm having a good time, too.
If you don't mind me asking,
why did you and your wife split up?
Oh, you know how it is,
we wanted different things.
I wanted children, and she wanted
a pastry chef named "Jean-Philippe".
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
-lt's fine.
It's why! left England.
It reminded me too much of her.
Cold, gloomy, and easily accessed by
a Frenchman through a tunnel.
-Hey. So, where are they?
-Across the street, in the left window.
Oh, damn it,
we should have brought binoculars.
Right here.
You just happen to have those in the car?
Kind of. Before I met Howie, I liked to
keep close tabs on my boyfriends.
By stalking them?
No, stalkers are creepy.
I'm just a harmless little girl
with military grade spy equipment.
PENNY: Oh, there he is.
BERNADETTE: He's cute, right?
Yeah.
Can I see?
What? Now you're interested?
You didn't even want to come.
I know, but you guys make
being a crappy friend look fun.
Fine.
LEONARD: Yeah, okay, [see him.
It looks like they're having a nice time.
lwish I could hear what they're saying.
Yeah, I should have brought
my parabolic microphone.
-Your what?
-Nothing. Not important.
So, you've never been married?
No. To be completely honest, I've only
been in one long-term relationship.
-What happened with that?
-That's a good question.
After five years, it was just feeling like
more work than it should be.
That's too bad.
Was he a neurobiologist like you?
No, he's a theoretical physicist
at CalTech.
I love teaching math,
but that would be my dream job.
What's his focus?
Um, it used to be string theory,
now it's dark matter.
But let's not discuss Sheldon,
let's get back to you.
Wait, you're not talking about
Dr. Sheldon Cooper?
I'm trying not to.
Do you know him?
No, but I've followed his work for years.
He's a rock star.
You've got to tell me about him.
What's he like?
He really seems into her.
I took a video.
| forgot how much fun this is.
Okay, we saw them.
Can we go catch the movie?
(PENNY EXHALES)
-Why'd you bring him?
-I had to, we're married now.
Ah, I hear that.
I'm sorry,
just one more question about Sheldon.
Sure, why not?
It's more of a four-part question, really.
When he wrote his paper on supersingular
prime numbers, how long did it take?
Um, about an hour and a half.
Wow!
I mean... Wow!
And you were there to see it?
Yes. Yeah, we were on a date.
Very much like this one.
I doubt it was like this one.
I mean, he's a genius.
And I wasn't even smart enough
to figure out why
my wife always smelled of croissants.
What was the rest of your question?
-Do you think you can introduce me to him?
-Rea||y?
You want me to introduce you
to my ex-boyfriend?
You're right, it's weird.
No, wait. Do it.
No, I changed my mind, I'd be too nervous.
Oh! I don't know what to do!
Are we gonna be much longer?
I really have to go to the bathroom.
Right here!
37 minutes left until the deadline.
Someone will show.
And no matter what happens,
this was still a fun experiment.
Not as fun as the night
we blew up grapes in the microwave.
We really have led full lives.
Someone will show.
Maybe you don't want someone
exactly like you.
You know what they say, opposites attract.
By that logic, I should be with someone
short, dull, and needy.
Not to cast dispersions, but I can't shake
a stick around here without hitting that.
You know, I once drove 500 miles
to hear him speak at Stanford.
-l have a DVD of that lecture.
-Rea||y? Wasn't it great?
Not as a Valentine's present, no.
Well, the next time you watch it,
I'm the bloke who asked the question
that he said was stupid and obvious.
It was the nicest thing
he said to anyone there.
That's, um, terrific. Listen, um,
I'm kind of tired. Can we call it a night?
Oh, gosh. Sorry, ljust spent the whole
night talking about your ex-boyfriend.
-l'm such an idiot.
-No, you're not.
Well, maybe not an idiot.
But certainly not as smart as...
Someone we won't mention.
Thank you.
That you said you might introduce me to.
I'm free on Thursday.
-Hey, they're leaving.
-What? Here, gimme, gimme.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
They're coming right towards us.
-We gotta get out of here.
-Wait, what about Leonard?
-He and his tiny bladder can take the bus.
-(SEATBELT CLICKS)
(ENGINE STARTING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
Oh, no!
She just hit my car!
What are you guys doing here?
Hi, Ames! What're you doing here?
-What happened?
-OMG.
-Aren't you Leonard Hofstadter?
-Yeah?
I saw you speak at Stanford
with Sheldon Cooper.
Amy, can you believe it?
It's Dr. Leonard Hofstadter!
No, pinch me!
It's an absolute pleasure to meet you.
Can I shake your hand?
I don't know if you want to do that,
lwasjust... Okay, never mind.
-Amy, I'm never washing this hand again.
-You really should.
60 seconds, this is not looking good.
One minute is a long time.
Oh, I've been telling women that
for 20 years.
-45.
-45 seconds is plenty of time
for a woman to walk through that door
and fall in love with me.
And probably half that
if I break out the old cow eyes.
30 seconds.
Uh-oh.
-What if it's Jennifer Lawrence?
-What?
Oh, that last Hunger Games
was not my cup of tea.
You thought she was great in X-Men.
Fine, I won't shut my heart
to the love of Jennifer Lawrence.
Guys, 15 seconds.
Maybe she's waiting to show up
at the last possible moment.
Ugh. Sounds like a drama queen. Oh, no.
It is Jennifer Lawrence.
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's too bad.
Maybe we did make the test too difficult.
(SIGHS) I don't think it matters.
Look, Sheldon,
I believe when the time is right
for you to meet someone,
it'll just happen, okay?
Not because of a test or a website,
but because--
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
We are the dreamers of dreams!
It's an actual girl
and she's really pretty!
Answer it!
All right.
Can I help you?
Um, are you the physicist
that placed the ad on Craigslist?
-Yes.
-Hi, I'm Vanessa Bennett.
Sorry it took a while for me to get here.
I was stuck in this boring symposium
on atomic spectroscopy
when I came across your ad.
And it saved my night. (CHUCKLES)
The puzzles were really fun.
I've never had to translate Klingon
into ancient Sanskrit before.
Careful, it's addictive.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Or as they say in Sanskrit,
(SPEAKING SANSKRIT)
And just like that,
you're a Klingon-Sanskrit junkie.
Anyway, ljust knew
I had to meet the person responsible
for such a brilliant idea.
And I don't need to tell you there aren't
a lot of men who love physics,
archaic languages and flags of the world.
I am a bit of a unicorn.
Well, you certainly seem
like a special lady,
uh, but as you know,
you missed the deadline,
so thanks for playing.
What?
How could you send her away?
She was late.
And she found atomic spectroscopy boring.
I wouldn't coitus her with your genitals.
(HANDBRAKE CLICKS)
-Uh, thanks for driving me home.
-No problem.
-l'm really sorry about your car.
-Oh, it's all right.
If you're free next weekend,
I'd love to take you out again.
Um...
Listen, you're a really nice guy,
but I don't think this is working out.
Oh. Okay.
Um... I'm really sorry.
Oh...
At least the same woman
that rejected Sheldon Cooper rejected me.
There ya go. (CHUCKLES)
If I ever do meet him,
we'll have that in common.
Sure. (CHUCKLES)
And he's kissed you and I've kissed you,
so if you think about it--
Okay, get out.
English - SDH