Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
And welcome to:
"Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun With Flags...
...the Final Episode Flagtacular."
[SHELDON GASPS]
I knew it was coming, still scary.
Now, I'm sure you're thinking:
"The final episode? Who will stand
between us and flag ignorance?"
I know I was thinking that.
Is this a show on flags or mind reading?
But the truth is I can no longer balance
a full-time career...
...a popular Internet show,
and a girlfriend.
And he really does have one,
you jerks on the comment board.
So as they say,
all good things must come to an end.
After only 232 episodes.
Two hundred thirty-three if we include the
one somebody forgot to press record on.
-You said you weren't gonna bring that up.
-And you said you pressed record.
Anyway, please, sit back, relax
and join us as we take our final lap...
...as indicated by the waving
of this racing flag.
Of course, white flags
can also represent surrender...
...the Stewards of Gondor,
and the Japanese Minamoto clan.
But I'm sure you remember
that from episode 62:
"White Flags:
Who's Waving Them and Why."
-That was a good one.
-That was so good.
You know, I thought cleaning out
a dead professor's office...
...was just going to be boring,
but then I found his dentures...
...and realized it's also gross.
Doesn't Professor Abbott's family
want any of this stuff?
-I don't think he had a family.
-That's rough.
I know. You can spend
your whole life working...
...and, at the end, all that's left
are some papers in a box.
Makes you think.
Oh,well.
Hey, we're supposed to look through
this before we throw it away...
-...in case it's important.
-I did. It's all outdated or disproved.
I don't know,
this old pen kind of proves gravity.
When ltilt it,
her bathing suit falls right off.
My dad used to have a pen like that.
l dated it all through sixth grade.
It still feels weird
just throwing away his work like this.
Don't feel bad, some day someone
will be throwing out your work too.
That someone was Sheldon
and the day was yesterday.
Hey, look at this.
"Dear Roger, to be opened upon
your first great discovery. Love, Mom."
Wow, look at the date.
He saved this 50 years
and never got to open it.
That's intense.
Poor Roger Abbott.
Roger Abbott sounds just like
"Roger Rabbit."
[CHUCKLING]
Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott,
Roger Abbott.
Oh, my God, Leonard,
I know he's dead, but try it, it's fun.
Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott....
-Ah, Penny. My rookie of the year.
PENNY: Hi.
Dan. My boss who didn't want to hire me
and now he's a little hug machine.
Look at you. Brand-new
and already the third best sales rep.
-Come over to my table.
-l'll be right there.
Bernadette's just parking the car.
Oh, good. Heh. Bernadette.
Cute, sweet, vicious little Bernadette.
Come on. She's not that bad.
Oh, yeah? At the company picnic,
she yelled at me and my grandson...
...for losing the three-legged race.
He still calls her
"that mean kid with the big boobies."
I know she can be a little intense...
...but I swear,
she is so sweet once you get past--
-Hey, what are you talking about?
-How much we love working with you.
Isn't that right, Dan?
Over the years here at Fun With Flags...
...we've had an opportunity
to learn, laugh, wonder....
And, yes, even shed a tear or two.
Like when you do a two-hour Fourth of July
spectacular and it doesn't get recorded.
How many times
do I have to say I'm sorry?
How about 4000? One for every domino
I set up to make that American flag.
Please enjoy these highlights.
[IN AUSTRALIAN ACCENT]
Crikey. What flag do we have today?
Australia, mate.
And now it's time for the speed round
of "Flag or not a Flag."
Flag. Flag. Not aflag. Flag.
I'm crushing this.
Say, Betsy Ross,
what are you working on?
[IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
l have no idea...
...because the story of me sewing
the first American flag...
...is unsupported poppycock.
Then who did sew it?
Don't ask me.
I'm just a simple seamstress
whose descendants--
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Are out to make a quick buck.
Fancy a dip, my dear?
I do.
Wait. That purple flag indicates that marine
pests, such as jellyfish, are present.
Wow, that flag is a lifesaver.
No, this is.
Stop looking at my legs.
Not a flag. Flag. Flag. Not a flag. Flag.
[BUZZER]
Eh, crap.
When stuff like this gets me down,
you know whatl like to do?
Sing "Hakuna Matata"
like an 8-year-old girl?
Wrong, smarty-pants.
It's "Everything is Awesome"
from The Lego Movie.
Look at these notebooks.
They're full of pages and pages of data.
He clearly spent years on this.
It's just columns of random numbers.
Toss it.
But what if this was a potential
breakthrough for him?
What if this is the thing that would've
let him open that bottle of champagne?
Maybe he didn't know what to pair
champagne with.
Strawberries, caviar, oysters,
all good choices.
That look right there is why people eat
before they come to your parties.
This has to mean something.
There's no discernible pattern
that I can see...
...but it shouldn't be too hard
to run the numbers and check.
Maybe we can get some time
on the supercomputer.
Sure, we could try multiple regressions...
...with varying physical
and experimental constants.
We could run a pattern-matching algorithm
against unsolved physics problems.
Ooh, it might be a substitution cipher.
We could start with basic cryptanalysis.
Or we could go talk to this guy
he used to share an office with.
Oh, let's do that.
You don't know how
to do cryptanalysis, do you?
Yeah, I'm not even sure
if it's the right word.
So, Dan, you have a grandson.
How old is he?
-Seven.
BERNADETTE: Oh, yeah.
I remember him from the picnic.
He was the one crying like a wuss
the whole time.
I heard he was being picked on
by a mean kid, heh.
Just builds character.
Like my dad said, "Nobody likes a crybaby
except their mommies and Democrats."
I need another drink.
What's his problem?
I don't know, maybe he didn't like the fact
you called his grandson a wuss.
Well, I didn't think you were supposed
to say "sissy" anymore.
Okay, look, I know
what a good person you are...
...but sometimes people think
you might come off a little harsh.
What?
I'm like the sweetest person I know.
Look at me,
I should be in a tree baking cookies.
Yes, but once in a while,
people think you're a little mean.
Oh, yeah? You one of those people?
No, no, no. I think the cookie thing.
Action.
Welcome back.
Our guest today
is a returning fan favorite.
He puts the reading in your rainbow,
the Geordi in your La Forge...
...and the Kunta in your Kinte:
Mr. LeVar Burton.
Thank you, Sheldon.
Now, remember our deal.
You do this,
I delete your contact information.
-While...?
-While you watch me do it.
Great, happy to be back.
Wait. Since you're here, I'd like
to get your opinion on something.
In honor of Black History Month,
| portrayed George Washington Carver...
...in a loving tribute
that my roommate called "wildly racist."
What do you think?
SHELDON [ON TABLET]:
Hi, my name is George.
Oh, hell, no.
You heard him, Leonard.
No, it's not racist.
Are we sure this is the place?
The doorman said
this is the right building.
I think if you're pulling up your pants,
you're not a doorman.
SHARPE:
Who is it?
Uh, I'm looking for a Professor Sharpe.
SHARPE:
Hold on.
-Can I help you?
-Hi, we're from the university.
We're trying to get some information
about Professor Abbott.
We were cleaning out his office
and found these books full of numbers.
-Any chance you know what it is?
-He was always working on this.
l was thinking it might be
an interstellar coordinate system.
Maybe an updated version
of Hubble's law.
I keep seeing the number 90 repeating.
That could be the angle of perturbation
of a distant galaxy.
It's the number of calories in a yogurt.
That's his food diary.
-Really?
-Yeah. He wrote down everything he ate.
He was convinced that calorie restriction
was the key to living forever.
-Does it work?
-Seriously?
He could have been hit by a bus.
You don't know.
Sorry it's not more interesting.
On the bright side, you didn't have to listen
to his stomach growl for 35 years.
So was there anything Professor Abbott
worked on during his life...
...that came close to an accomplishment?
To be honest,
his research never amounted to anything.
You were his colleague.
How did yours turn out?
Great, this is the apartment you get
when you win a Nobel.
You could be very frugal. I'm getting
a little tired of everybody's sarcasm.
I'm not a bully.
I mean, maybe I come off a little strong...
...but that's because my dad raised me to be
tough and not to take crap from anybody.
That's fine. There's a difference
between being tough...
...and telling your friend
her new pants look like a saggy diaper.
I did say that, didn't I?
Yeah, you did. I felt so self-conscious
I had to return them.
Where? To Babies "R" Us?
You're doing it again.
Sorry. Can we just go?
I feel like everybody hates me.
Come on, they don't hate you,
they're just a little intimidated.
All you need to do is show everyone
how sweet you are.
-I think I'd rather go.
-No. You're not going anywhere.
All right? I'm here for you
and we're gonna fix this together.
-Thank you.
-Even though your dress is ugly.
Well, my little flag-keteers...
...it looks like the last episode
of Fun with Flags is at an end.
lfl could, I would run each and every
one of you viewers up a flagpole...
...and salute you.
And if you touched the ground, burn you.
I'd like to take a moment to personally
thank Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler...
...who you may or may not know
is the first woman to co-host...
...a flag or banner related
Internet info-tainment show.
Take that, glass ceiling.
And if I may get serious for a moment...
...hosting this show has been
one crazy ride.
With all its ups and downs,
I wouldn't give it up for the world.
Except for now, when I'm giving it up.
Before I sign off, I'd, uh....
I'd like to share with you all
one last use for a white flag:
It's good for times like this.
Good night.
Cut.
Sheldon.
-That was beautiful.
-If you didn't press record--
I pressed it!
Well, that's it.
That's the end of Roger Abbott.
And we still don't know who framed him.
I still keep thinking about how an entire life
can seemingly amount to nothing.
I guess the sad truth is not everyone
will accomplish something great.
Some of us mayjust have to find meaning
in the little moments that make up life.
That's a nice way of looking at it.
Yeah, for you, not for me.
I went to space, so I'm covered.
You know what? This bottle was meant
to celebrate an achievement.
Let's make a pact. When one of us
gets their first big breakthrough...
...we'll celebrate by opening this bottle of
champagne and toasting Professor Abbott.
-I love that.
-Me too.
And of course, rubbing our success
in Sheldon's face.
-That's the best part, really.
-Yeah.
Dan, could I talk to you for a minute?
Sure, go ahead.
I just want you to know I didn't mean
to be rude about your grandson.
-lt's okay.
-No, it's not.
Penny told me
that everyone's scared of me.
[LAUGHING]
What?
Why would she say that?
You know she drinks, right?
What?
No, she's right.
I just want you to know, from now on,
I'm gonna be much more sensitive.
I don't want anyone walking
on eggshells around me.
Well, okay. Then, uh, one thing
I've been meaning to tell you...
...is the company is gonna
stop paying for our coffee.
-No problem. When does that start?
-Five months ago.
-What? Who's been paying for my coffee?
-Yeah. All of us.
It comes from the swear jar
we put money in when you curse.
What else don't I know about?
-Uh, well, you know your private bathroom?
-Yeah.
-That's supposed to be for the whole floor.
-You're kidding.
No, no. It's okay, it really only affected
Wheelchair Kathy...
...and she's back in the hospital now,
so it all worked out.
I feel so bad.
Then maybe you shouldn't have named her
Wheelchair Kathy.
Oh, my God, I thought everybody liked me,
but I'm just a monster.
But a cute one, like that eyeball guy
in Monsters, Inc.
No, I'm the worst. I'm a terrible person.
Come on, don't cry. It's okay.
It's not okay.
How can I even work here anymore?
Because this company needs you.
It's fine, we don't mind
paying for the coffee.
I can't let you do that.
Maybe we could get you an
espresso machine for your office.
I guess that would be all right.
See? You don't have to be mean
to get what you want.
You're right. Now, where did we land
on my bathroom?
-Hey.
-Hello.
LEONARD:
How come you're up so late?
I posted the last episode
of Fun with Flags hours ago...
...and not a single person
cared enough to comment.
All that effort for nothing.
Hmm.
I know how you feel. I spent the day
throwing out a man's entire career...
...and all that's left is an old bottle
of champagne...
...and a naked lady pen Raj took
when he thought no one was looking.
It's not the same thing.
I don't think you know how I feel at all.
Sad?
Huh.
You do get me.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
Someone left a comment.
Yeah? What did they say?
"Too bad your show is done.
I kind of liked it."
Leonard, did you hear that?
The people are heartbroken.
I can't take this away from the world.
Fun with Flags is back.
-Congratulations.
-Let's celebrate.
[CHAMPAGNE BOTTLE POPS]
Sheldon, that wasn't for you.
Oh, I'm not going to drink it,
I just wanted to hear the pop.
You know, I knew it was coming,
still scary.
LeVar Burton.
[SIGHS]
What are you doing here?
You told me not to call and I didn't know
how else to give you the good news.
Fun with Flags is back
and you can be in the next episode.
Wil Wheaton said get a gate.
I don't know why I didn't get a gate.
At least listen to the premise.
Since you were born in Germany,
I thought we could talk about German flags.
How do you feel about dressing up
like a swastika?
[English - us - an]