-Helium.
-Yes.
-Tay|or Swift.
-Pi.
-Yes.
-Kardashian.
-More specific.
-Kh|oé? Ah!
-Yes!
See, I remember because
if it looks like Kim, it's Kim,
if it looks kind of like Kim,
it's Kourtney,
if it looks nothing like Kim, it's Khloé.
Oh, that's a Venn diagram,
and I remember
because I thought to myself,
"Venn is he gonna stop talking
about this diagram?"
What're you guys doing?
Well, we decided to use our breakfast time
to expand our respective knowledge bases.
Let me try.
Atom of hydrogen,
Adam of Maroon 5, mic drop.
I'm sorry, who is Mike Drop?
(LAUGHS)
Oh, hey, Penny, do you wanna go
to the airport with me later
to pick up my mother?
-Sure.
-LEONARD: Thanks.
No problem.
Hey, Penny, since you're already
gonna be at the airport, do I need to go?
Why don't you wanna
get your mother from the airport?
I can do without the 40-minute car ride
where she criticizes
every aspect of my life.
She can cover it in a car ride?
I can do 40 minutes on your posture alone.
You really want me
to pick up your mother all by myself?
ljust feel like it would be
a good chance for you to bond.
Or a way for you to avoid her?
I don't know what he's putting on those
cards, but you are smarter than ever.
Fine, if you really want me to,
I will pick your mom up.
Seriously?
Yeah, you know what,
she is my mother-in-law,
and I'd like for us to have
a good relationship.
That is very mature of you,
so I'm gonna go ahead and say, suckah!
-All right, back to learning.
-Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, easy, Bill Nye, the Science Guy.
Or as I know him.
Creepy old dude
from Dancing With The Stars.
(IMITATING BELL DINGING)
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Did you guys see
there's an Avengers screening?
Joss Whedon's gonna show
some deleted scenes
and do a question and answer session.
Well, l have a few questions for him
about the last Avengers movie,
and a whole lot of answers.
When's the screening?
lt's tonight,
but it's first come, first served,
so we should probably
get there early and wait in line.
Let's do it.
Penny's busy with my mother, so I'm in.
Bad news, Amy's making me
go shopping with her later,
so it looks like none of us can go.
You do realize we're allowed
to have fun without you?
In fact, that's usually the trick to it.
What time do we need to get there?
Uh, I'd say by 3:00.
You're really going without me?
It's not a big deal. Go shopping with Amy,
and we'll save a spot in line for you.
You don't have the authority
to save places in the line.
If I do that, I'll be cutting.
People do it all the time.
You know the golden rule
of line etiquette,
"No cuts, no buts, no coconuts."
If you really care that much,
there are apps now
that'll let you hire people to do stuff
like errands and wait in lines.
People are actually
waiting in lines as ajob?
Boy, it makes me feel better
about my life.
Some of these guys make over $20 an hour.
And now | feel worse again.
I'm not surprised Leonard chose
to avoid picking me up.
He's battled intimacy issues
his whole life.
Does he have difficulty
maintaining erections?
(CLEARING THROAT) Wow. Didn't even
make it out of the parking lot.
You know what, enough about Leonard,
let's talk about you.
What would you like to do
while you're here?
Dear, I'm a psychiatrist.
You don't have to avoid having
intimate conversations with me.
Well, I'd actually like
for us to be close,
but maybe we start with our favorite books
and work our way up
to my husband's sex organs.
Very well. What's the last book you read?
Uh, does Pottery Barn Spring count?
Penny, it's only natural to want
your mother-in-law to like you,
and I acknowledge
I can be an intimidating person.
So, what can I do
to make this process easier for you?
For starters, maybe you can
not psychoanalyze everything I say?
And how does it make you feel when
l psychoanalyze everything you say?
Uncomfortable.
That was ajoke, dear.
Oh, sorry.
(CHUCKLES) Didn't know you made those.
Hey, listen, what if we have
a little mother-in-law,
daughter-in-law dinner tonight?
So, just the two of us?
Or do | invite a few girlfriends?
'Cause hearing you say "the two of us"
just sent a chill right down my spine.
H ey.
What are you doing here?
You're not Sheldon.
I thought that might come up.
Sheldon hired me to go shopping with you.
Hold on, he paid you
to get out of spending time with me?
No, it's not like that.
There's a long line he'd rather stand in.
So, what're we doing, Old Navy,
Build-A-Bear, | get paid either way.
We're not going shopping together.
You sure? I'm happy to hold your bag,
and Sheldon gave me money
for Hot Dog on a Stick.
Can you understand
whyl might be annoyed right now?
(CHUCKLING) Look, lady, ljust work here.
We've waited in a lot of lines together,
haven't we?
Remember when we camped out
for the Doctor Who panel at Comic-Con?
Yeah, sleeping under the stars
with other fans who love the show
as much as we do.
Waking up wondering
which of those fans stole our wallets.
Stuart, what're you doing here?
Sheldon, you are the most inconsiderate
person I have ever met in my entire life!
Where do you get off
sending me to shop with your girlfriend?
I don't understand. You were happy
to do this when I hired you.
Why are you upset with me now?
I'm not upset with you,
but Amy's pretty bent out of shape,
so she hired me to let you have it.
Well, I suppose turnabout is fair play.
You're darn right it's fair play,
you selfish jerk!
You know, just when I think we're
making progress in our relationship,
we revert to our old patterns where
thoughts and feelings go unexpressed.
I mean, if he didn't wanna go shopping
with me, why didn't he just say so?
Maybe he couldn't get a word in edgewise.
Sorry, I've been going on and on.
No, it's all right, dear.
Sheldon has a brilliant
and complicated mind.
lt's understandable that being in
a relationship with him could be trying.
I called him "babe" once.
He asked me to get a drug test.
Well, I do admire your resolve.
You're an extraordinary woman.
Thank you.
You know what, she's my mother-in-law,
why can't I bond with her like that?
Amy's with Sheldon
who she loves like a son.
You're with her son, who she doesn't.
Do you realize it took me five years
to get a massage from him?
Well, that still could be
a big step for Sheldon.
Three minutes.
And he used a kitchen timer.
I felt like a soft-boiled egg.
You know, being in a relationship
with Leonard
also comes with its challenges.
Yes, well, what can you do?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Maybe it's Sheldon,
here to say he's sorry.
Sheldon says he's sorry.
Bernadette,
I'll give you $5 to slam the door.
I would've done it for $3.
Boy, all this standing's making me tired.
Good thing I brought
my collapsible stick chair.
The stick chair.
You look like an idiot on that thing.
Sticks and stones may break my bones,
but chairs on sticks are comfy.
H ey.
Hey, is everything smoothed out with Amy?
Uh, no, she's still pretty mad.
Did you make the apology
as sincere as I would have?
I said, "Sheldon says he's sorry."
Yeah, well,
that's laying it on a little thick.
Think it's time
you apologize to her yourself.
I suppose so, but if I get out of line,
l'll lose my spot.
I'm happy to hold your place
till you get back.
You would do that?
Consider it my way
of getting more of your money.
You're a good man.
So, Beverly, did you know
Penny is the number three sales rep
at our pharmaceutical company?
I didn't realize you two work together.
Well, we don't exactly, I'm
a microbiologist for the research team.
What are you currently developing?
BERNADETTE: Some exciting
new anti-anxiety drugs.
That's interesting. ljust attended
a lecture on pediatric anxiety.
Oh, was it Dr. Jenofski?
ljust saw his TED Talk.
BEVERLY: It was.
Well, let's get back to Penny.
Hey, weren't you telling me something
great about your company car?
Um... (CLEARING THROAT)
It has seat warmers.
(INTERMITTENT KNOCKING ON DOOR)
SHELDON: Amy, Amy, Amy.
Come in.
Hello, everyone.
Oh, Beverly, good to see you.
I'd love to chat, but there's a line
that could start moving any minute,
so let's do this.
Amy, a proper apology
requires three steps.
Step one, an admission of wrongdoing.
Amy, I was wrong.
Step two, a promise
never to repeat said action.
Amy, that action will never be repeated,
and that's a promise.
Step three,
an earnest request for forgiveness.
Amy, I hope you can forgive me,
and I hope you do it right now
'cause there's an Uber waiting downstairs,
and I don't wanna repeat this apology
nonsense with my driver, Ganesh.
Fine.
Oh, thanks, you're a peach.
And Beverly, we'll catch up soon.
Bernadette, it's a pleasure, as always.
Penny, you have spinach in your teeth.
How long have I had spinach in my teeth?
Since the airport, dear.
You look like you come with a kickstand.
You can't make me feel bad.
Maybe not. Leonard?
So, when the aliens brought you back,
theyjust left the probe in?
-l'm back.
-Hey, how'd it go?
It went well.
You know, I've learned that
if you never say you're sorry,
the times you do
really puts them on their heels.
Stuart, l relieve you of your line duties.
Anyone else need anything before I go?
I'll give you a dollar
if you make fun of Raj.
-That's mean.
-Five.
You look like Tigger
if Tigger looked like ajackass.
If you ever need a reference
or anything, just let me know.
Hey, guys.
Did you see that?
He just cut the line.
He's just joining his friends, it's fine.
No, it's not fine.
It is a breach of line etiquette.
We're near the front of the line.
We'll get in either way.
What if every person in front of us
lets someone cut?
We'd still get in.
What if each of those people
let someone cut?
Still get in.
Then each of those people let someone cut?
We'd still get in, but first l'd hit you
over the head with his stick chair.
-Excuse me.
-Oh, please don't.
I couldn't help but notice
that you cut the line.
Oh, uh, I'm with my friends. It's cool.
No, it's not cool.
If there were reserved seating,
we all had tickets, that'd be fine,
but this line is first-come, first-served.
Not "show up tardy
and nevertheless be first-served."
-Right here.
-No.
You need to go to the back of the line.
(SCOFFS) Who made you line monitor?
Mrs. Wunch in fourth grade.
And my slogan was, "A line
this straight is a line that's great."
Is this guy for real?
Boy, lwish I could say no.
That was very nice of Sheldon
to apologize.
Well, he's come a long way,
or a short way very slowly,
so it feels like a long way.
Your relationship with him is fascinating.
I'm preparing to write a book
on high-achieving couples,
and lwould love to interview
the both of you.
Oh, sure, I'll talk to Sheldon about it.
You know, Bernadette's husband's
a former astronaut.
Really?
Do you think he would be interested
in being interviewed as well?
Do I think he'd be interested?
Sometimes I hear him
pretending to be interviewed
when he's alone in the bathroom.
Wonderful, I'll give you
my contact information.
Um, you should
probably talk to Penny, too.
About what?
Okay, you know what, this is ridiculous.
I've been trying to make
a connection with you all day,
and clearly I'm getting nowhere.
Well, are you seeking a connection
orjust some form of validation?
What I was seeking was
some sort of friendship,
but at this point I'll take you
not insulting me to my face.
My intention was never to insult you.
You've been doing it all day.
Do you even know what an insult is?
Well, it's not a clinical term,
but one example would be
your marrying my son and not inviting me
or even telling me
the wedding was taking place.
Okay, good example.
What about Joss Whedon's work
makes you think he'd be okay
with rule-breakers and line-cutters?
The Avengers are rule-breakers, being
vengeful is in theirjob description.
They work for S.H.l.E. L. D.,
which is a sanctioned department
of the US government.
Now, do you work for a sanctioned
department of the US government?
As a matter of fact I do,
at a little place called the DMV.
He's got him there.
The "D" even stands for department.
Excuse me,
can I please see a show of hands?
Who here takes issue
with this person cutting the line?
Told you.
Well, what a sad state of affairs.
Now that you've all been
so ground down by life,
you don't even notice
when someone disrespects you.
I can't believe we're gonna get beat up,
and it's not because of your chair.
SHELDON: It's time for you to wake up.
You know, right now,
at the back of this line,
there's a movie fan like you
who's not going to get in
because this person simply doesn't care.
Yeah, well, 61 years ago,
there was another person
at the back of the line,
and her name was Rosa Parks.
Okay, you may have to pretend you're black
to get us out of here.
Let's all follow in that brave woman's
footsteps and stand up for ourselves.
Now, and I realize that
she stood up by remaining seated,
but now is not the time
to enjoy the irony of that.
Now, | ask you again,
who here takes issue with this person--
Why should we listen to you?
You cut the line yourself.
| most certainly did not.
I saw you.
If you're feeling dizzy,
it's because the tables have turned.
Excuse me, I paid someone
to wait in line for me,
and then when I arrived, he left.
So what you saw, my good woman,
was swapsies, not cutsies.
No, no, no, no, no, wait.
| ask you again, show of hands,
who here takes issue with--
Stop moving! He's gonna get in!
-Buddy, let it go.
-No, I can't, this isn't right.
-You did everything you could.
-No, I could've done more.
N ow, n ow.
You denigrated the memory
of a great civil rights pioneer.
That's all anyone could ask.
To be honest, I'm surprised
you cared about the wedding at all.
I'm still human, Penny.
Not getting invited to my own
son's wedding is difficult to ignore.
I know how you feel.
She didn't invite any of us.
It was spur of the moment.
Well, we did get to see
a live stream of it on the Internet.
I could've watched it on the Internet?
(WHISPERING) Thank you.
So, if we would've asked you
to come to Vegas to see us get married,
you would've come?
No, I would've said
you're making a huge mistake,
but an invitation would've been nice.
You really think we made a mistake?
At the time I did,
but I've never seen Leonard so happy,
so perhaps I was wrong.
Wow.
Okay, well, how about this?
Maybe while you're still in town, Leonard
and I can have another small ceremony,
you know, if you're interested.
I would find that perfectly acceptable.
(GASPS)
She would find it perfectly acceptable.
You guys saw it, we bonded.
Howie, you're doin' okay?
You've been in there a while.
HOWARD: I'm ﬁne, be right out.
Am I an American hero? (SCOFFS)
Oh...
That's a good question, Jim.
You know, don't you think
once an astronaut leaves the planet,
he's a hero
to all the nations of the Earth?
(TOILET FLUSHING)
Okie—dokie, I think I have time
for one more question.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH