(VOICE BREAKING) Iunderstand your e—mail.
(STAMMERS) Can you repeat that?
You're breaking up.
(VOICE BREAKING)
I didn't understand your e—mail.
Ah, yeah, well,
I had to get a little creative
because the "S," "R" and "M" keys
on my laptop stopped working.
"Deaw Aby,
"could you pleathe dwive be
to the twain thtow thubtibe tobowow?"
So, is that a yes?
Sheldon, why don't you get a new computer?
You know that one's out-of-date.
Oh. But I like this computer.
The video is failing
and the sound is cutting out.
(STAMMERS) I'm sorry, I didn't get that.
(VOICE BREAKING) The Video is failing
and...is cutting...
I'm sorry one more time,
the sound is cutting out.
What? I can't read that,
the video is failing.
Get a...computer.
What?
Get...new...
-(GROANS LIGHTLY)
-(PHONE RINGING)
-Hello?
-AMY: Get a new computer!
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
This is cool.
When was the last time
you and I built something together?
Scientifically? Little over a year ago.
LEGOs? Last week in my room.
If there was a Nobel Prize
for Millennium Falcons that fall apart
when you pick them up we'd be set.
Hey, guys.
-Hey, what are you doing here?
-Hey.
We heard there were some sexy scientists
working hard all weekend.
Yup, so we brought you some lunch
and we are gonna go look for 'em.
Soup, sandwiches and emasculation,
just like my mom used to make.
-So, how's it goin'?
-Good. Slow.
There's a lot of tedious set-up,
but once we get through that
it should go quicker.
Is there anything we can do to help?
You know what,
this part isn't that technical,
you actually could.
Wow. Really?
Called my bluff, all righty then.
Can we really help?
Yeah, while we finish soldering
these boards,
it'd be great if you guys could wrap
these pipe fittings with Teflon tape.
I'll show you how to do one.
Hey, wouldn't it be funny if
after all your years of hard work,
I'm the one who makes a scientific
breakthrough? (SNICKERING)
He doesn't think that's funny.
(STATIC)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR KNOCK)
I got here as quickly as I could.
You're too late.
(FUNERAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Sheldon, this is silly.
You got emotional
when that lab monkey died.
That lab monkey told me he loved me
in sign language.
(STAMMERS)
Great, now I'm gonna have that song
in my head all day.
Look, I'm sorry for your loss,
but I think I have something
that might make you feel better.
I got you a new computer!
(SNICKERING)
How could you do that?
Do what?
Choosing a new laptop
is an incredibly personal ritual.
But, you have taken away
weeks of agonizing thought,
tedious research,
sleepless nights filled with indecision.
(STAMMERS)
Haven't I lost enough today?
Well, the guy at the store
said this one is great.
Oh... The guy!
Oh, pardon me, I didn't realize
you'd spoken to the guy.
Tell me, did the guy choose one
with a 4K display and a Thunderbolt port?
-Yes.
-Yeah?
Well, did the guy make sure
that this has
a one terabyte solid-state drive?
-Yes.
-Yeah?
Well, was this guy Rick from
Computer Solutions on Colorado?
Yes.
Yeah, well, he does know his stuff.
After you wrap the body
in reflective tape,
the ends get Teflon tape
so we can get a tight seal.
-Like this? Oh.
-Yeah, perfect.
And it helps to have small,
delicate fingers.
So, don't be discouraged
if you can't do it
as fast as me and Howard. (CHUCKLING)
I don't know if we have enough solder
to finish these circuit boards.
We had a full spool yesterday.
What can I say, I play hard,
I solder even harder.
Sometimes he solders at home
with his shirt off,
it's like a beer commercial.
Well, we gotta make a run
to the hardware store.
How can you call yourself a scientist
and run out of solder?
(CHUCKLING) Well, funny story.
So, we have plenty of
the 60-40 tin to lead ratio solder,
but the spools look a lot
like the 63-37 tin to lead--
Honey, honey, honey, let me stop you.
That is not a funny story.
You wanna come with us?
Kinda getting into the groove here.
Yeah, you guys run to the store
and let the women
handle the science for a change.
-Okay, we'll be back as soon as we can.
-(PENNY CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Okay, so what is solder?
I suppose I should set this up.
Or would you like to rob me of that, too?
Knock it off,
or I'll start making W-H sounds
for words that just have a W.
-You wouldn't.
-Watch me.
Fine, I'm sorry.
Thank you for the thoughtful gift.
I really do appreciate it.
Well, as you know, I had become
attached to my old laptop,
but I'm sure, in time, this one--
(GASPS) Jeepers-creepers,
that started up fast!
I thought you might like it.
Look at the 4K resolution!
Next time we Skype,
I'm gonna count all those nostril hairs.
Or you could just look into my eyes.
But you only have two eyes,
you got a lot of nostril hairs.
Well, you know, as long as you're happy.
I am. (CHUCKLES)
And Rick said you could bring in
your old one to recycle it.
Oh. No, no, no, thank you.
But he said you can get store credit.
Well, no, I don't want to recycle it
and, you know, I don't want store credit.
-But, why wouldn't--
-Can we please change the subject?
Okay, how about we change it to
why you're being weird about this?
I'm not being weird.
It's hard to explain.
Sheldon, just tell me.
It might be easier to show you.
Okay.
We have to take your car.
All right.
And I'm gonna need you to sign
a non-disclosure agreement.
Well, I signed one before
we slept together, why not now?
Penny says they're having fun
working on the prototype.
Remember when her fun was
night clubs and drinking games?
I know, I'm lowering the bar so slowly
this time next year
she'll have a coin collection.
Excuse me,
you guys interested in a free screening
of an upcoming movie?
-Sorry, we can't.
-Well, hang on.
What movie is it?
Oh, I can't tell you,
but it does star Will Smith.
Wait, I bet it's Suicide Squad.
Let's check it out.
What about the girls?
Pennyjust said they're having fun.
Honestly, you wanna wrap tape around
a bunch of pipe fittings all afternoon?
-Okay, we'll take 'em.
-Okay.
LEONARD: But I swear, if it's Will Smith
in Shark Tale 2,
it better be at least
as good as the original.
I mean, it's crazy, isn't it?
I moved here from Nebraska
to be an actress
and now I'm sitting
in an engineering lab at Caltech
helping to build a prototype
for a high-tech guidance system.
It is crazy.
It's also crazy that I've made 14 of these
and you've made three.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Hey, where are the guys?
Oh, they went to the store to get solder,
which is metal you melt
to make science things.
Since when do you work on weekends?
I'm an astrophysicist,
the stars don't take a day off.
You were home alone
and had no one to play with?
Well, the cleaning lady was there,
but she doesn't like me.
You need any help?
Not with Lightning McQueen here.
I think we're good.
Okay, that's cool.
Guess everybody's involved
in this project but me.
So, see ya.
I feel bad,
should we have asked him to stay?
RAJ: (GIRLY VOICE) Yes.
Will you please tell me where we're going?
Sorry, you're on a need-to-know basis.
I'm driving the car, I need to know.
Right.
So where are we going?
No, I meant turn right and you missed it.
Maybe you do need to know.
(LEONARD SIGHS)
What are we gonna tell the girls?
-It's not a problem.
-I mean, without lying.
And now you've made it a problem.
Come on, we're a couple of smart guys,
I'm sure we can come up
with a way to explain this
that doesn't make us look bad.
(PHONE CHIMES)
Oh, the boys had to drive
all the way to San Bernardino
for the solder and got a flat.
-(PHONE CHIMES)
-They bought it.
But we're gonna have to
put the spare on before we go back.
Oh, you're good at this.
(CHUCKLES) Well, I lie a lot.
Hey, guys, thank you for being
a part of our test screening.
You're about to be one of the first
audiences to see Suicide Squad.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
You were right.
I keep telling you,
good things happen to bad people.
(CHUCKLING)
We're gonna get started
in a couple of minutes, enjoy.
Who you texting?
Raj. He really wants to see this movie.
-Oh, he'll never make it in time.
-I know.
I wanna make him feel bad.
"Ha-ha, Leonard and I are
about to see Suicide Squad.
"Spoiler alert.
When I see you I'm gonna spoil it."
You're a good friend.
(CHUCKLING)
(PHONE CHIMES)
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
Would you ladies please
leave the room for a moment?
Why?
I need to rub my genitals
on their prototype.
What's going on?
Leonard and Howard don't have a flat.
They went to the movies. Look.
-Un-freakin'-believable!
-Son of a bitch.
You know what? I'm gonna let them know
that I'm here with you
and that they're busted.
No, you know what, don't. Don't.
Let's let them think
they're getting away with it.
Yeah, let's see how deep a hole
they could dig for themselves.
-Mm-hmm.
-Interesting.
I mean, it's not testicles on a cryostat,
but I like it.
Why do you have a storage unit?
(SIGHS) Just wait.
How long have you had it?
Just wait.
Do you want me to hold that computer?
Just... You know what, actually, yes,
thank you.
Welcome to my fortress of shame.
I'm sorry, what am I looking at?
Basically everything I've ever owned.
Um, every book, every T-shirt,
every piece of broken electronics,
just... All of it.
All of it?
I have a Ziploc bag
filled with all my old Ziploc bags.
Okay. Well...
I would like to tell you
that there is nothing here
to be ashamed of.
So I'm gonna need a minute.
All right, how are we gonna
play this when they return?
I know, you guys should
totally be making out with me.
Sweetie, I know you think
jokes like that are funny,
but do you really think you could
handle makin' out with both of us?
(INHALES DEEPLY) No, ma'am.
Okay, okay, how about this.
They don't know you're here with us,
so you hide in the closet.
When they show up, we'll hear
whatever their dumb story is
about where they were,
we'll pretend to believe them,
and just when they think
they got away with it, you jump out.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
I love it! I'll be all like, "Busted!"
And they'll be like, "What?"
And then we'll all be like, "Oh, yeah!"
Yeah, I get it, I wouldn't make out
with me either.
In here is every clock radio
I've ever owned.
Calculators, VHS tapes,
yeah, sporting equipment.
You have sporting equipment?
Well, it's a golf ball
that my brother threw at my head.
You can still feel the dent.
It's right next to the hockey-puck dent.
Okay, why do you have a bin of pinecones?
I used to collect them as a child.
The spiral of scales open
in the Fibonacci sequence.
A fact that, when you tell your brother,
gets a golf ball thrown at your head.
So, why do you feel
you need to save these things?
I'd like to say it's nostalgia,
but every time I think
of throwing anything away
my ears start to ring
and I get butterflies in my stomach.
And then it feels like
the butterflies get eaten by rats.
-And then the rats get eaten by--
-Okay, I get it. I get it.
It ends with dinosaurs.
I'm sorry if you think less of me.
I don't.
Really?
Because every time I come in here,
I think less of me.
Why?
Because I'm a fraud.
I purport to be a man of the mind.
I've been such a vocal champion
of The Singularity,
but how can I leave my body behind
and become one with the Internet
when I've never even thrown
a toothbrush away?
It's okay, Sheldon, you know,
I've saved a lot of weird things, too.
Like what?
Well...
Um, did you know I have a microscope slide
with a little bit of tissue
from the first brain I ever dissected.
I have an old teddy bear I secretly
wiped my nose on for years.
It's not a contest.
-Okay, here they come.
-Go hide.
Oh, man, when I come out of the closet
I'm gonna nail those guys.
Yeah, I heard it, shut up.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Hey, what's this?
Listen, we did a stupid thing.
We went to a movie and lied about it,
but we feel bad
and wanna make it up to you.
So, these are for you,
and if you're not too mad,
we'd love to take you guys to dinner.
Yeah, anywhere you want.
Well, thank you for being honest.
Yeah, you know, I wanna be upset,
but we did kinda have fun
working on the prototype.
RAJ: Don't forgive them! Stay mad at them!
What is he doing in there?
Busting you!
It's okay, they apologized.
Yeah, it's fine.
Well, this is kinda anti-climactic.
You know what wasn't anti-climactic?
The end of the movie! Get this.
No spoilers! No spoilers!
And he's back in the closet.
-Ready for dinner?
-Yeah.
Should we invite Raj?
RAJ: (GIRLY VOICE) Yes.
So, no one else knows about this?
Only you.
Thank you for trusting me.
What good is having a girlfriend
if you can't unload your
psychological sewage on her?
That's me, your emotional outhouse.
You know, if you ever decide
you want to do something about this,
I'm here for you.
Thank you.
I wouldn't even know how to begin.
Baby steps, I guess.
I suppose I could try
getting rid of the golf ball.
Oh. Okay.
I will always have the dent
to remember it by.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(SIGHS)
You did it.
Do you feel okay?
Actually, yes, I do.
Well, I'm proud of you.
Thanks.
I'm glad I told you
about the storage unit.
Well, I feel closer to you now.
I feel closer to you, too.
You know, it's still a couple of hours
until my bed time.
What did you have in mind?
You look amazing.
I mean, this resolution is remarkable.
I really had to go home for this?
Yes, but it's like
you're right here in the room.
And yet, I'm not.
But I feel like I could just
reach out and touch you.
And yet, you can't.
I know!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH