What a wonderful day! Thank you!
Oh, we're glad you had fun.
Blue Icees and a trip
to The Container Store?
It's like I died and went to the
post-mortem, neuron-induced hallucination
commonly mistaken as Heaven.
I still don't understand
why you bought that pill caddie.
You're a young man.
Age is a state of mind, Leonard.
ln here, I'm 90.
-(KEYS JANGLING)
-(DOOR UNLOCKING)
Why are you taking your bins over there?
Uh, that's just where I need them.
You know, she doesn't have
a lot of closet space.
Mmm, what's wrong with your closet?
Uh...
Well, honey, you know,
now that Leonard and l are married,
it kind of makes sense
that we actually live together.
So, that's all this day was?
A plan to butter me up
before delivering bad news?
-Come on, buddy.
-No, I thought we were friends.
You asked for a sip of my lcee.
If you'd had your own straw,
I might have said yes.
Sheldon, please,
we already feel bad about this.
Yeah, you know what they don't sell
at The Container Store?
Something large enough
to contain my disappointment!
Although, if anyone did, it would be them!
(THEME SONG PLAYING)
Thank you for letting me
come speak with you.
Of course.
As my relationships with Penny
and Amy are currently strained,
I'm turning to you
for female comfort and encouragement.
Aww.
I'm honored.
I tried reaching out to my mother,
but she was in Bible study.
Leonard's mother is on a book tour,
my Meemaw was taking a nap,
and after a while,
Siri started repeating her answers.
So I'm your seventh choice.
Yeah, I know. Top 10, pretty exciting.
How can I help you?
In addition to Amy leaving me,
Leonard's moving in with Penny.
It's difficult not to feel abandoned.
Well, why don't you
look at this as an opportunity?
You had other roommates before Leonard.
Maybe this is a chance
to find someone new.
Hmm, perhaps I could find
someone better than Leonard.
You know, someone I could rub in his face.
Chris Pratt's all the rage right now.
I wonder how he'd feel
about taking the smaller bedroom.
-Hey.
You know who'd be the perfect roommate?
Gandalf, but he's a smoker.
Stuart! He's been living with us
for a while now.
I'm sure he'd love
to get us out of his hair.
Nope, couldn't be happier.
-Well, Sheldon's looking for a roommate--
-Nope.
-He'll think about it.
-STUART: No, I won't!
(DOOR CLOSES)
Have you seen this Archie comic?
It's actually Archie versus Predator.
How could Archie defeat Predator?
I don't know,
maybe Jughead's a Terminator.
-Hey.
-Hey, Stuart.
-Do you guys know any musicians?
-Why?
l was thinking it might be cool to have
live music here a few nights a week.
You know, give this place
more of a "staying in business" vibe.
What kind of music are you thinking of?
I like all kinds of music,
but my favorite genre is free.
Hey, we've always
talked about playing together.
Well, it could be fun
to try a little acoustic thing.
Oh, we could play filk music!
What's that?
It's been around for years.
It's like folk music,
but with a sci-filfantasy theme.
I like it.
It sounds exactly like something
I shouldn't be expected to pay for.
Hey, dude, if we do this,
we're gonna need a cool band name.
You know, I've actually (CHUCKLES)
had one I've been sitting on for years.
-Really?
-It was for this power trio
I tried to put together in junior high,
but I was short two friends.
What is it?
Footprints on the Moon.
ljust got chills.
So did I.
Me, too.
But I might have Lyme disease.
Just a few more signatures
and we'll be finished.
Uh, initial here to acknowledge
that you've returned your key.
Okay.
Oh, yes, as my future neighbor,
I'd like you to have a key.
lnitial here
to acknowledge you received it.
I'm proud of you.
You're taking this really well.
Oh, it's not like I'm never going
to see you two again.
Yeah, which brings us
to article 23, subsection C.
"Please check here to reserve your spot
at the 10-year roommate reunion."
Do I really have to do that now?
No, but if you want chicken
and get stuck with the fish,
that's on you.
All right.
Oh, and lastly,
please initial here to confirm
that ownership of the living room couch
is hereby transferred to me
in perpetuity all throughout the universe.
And all alternate universes.
Except for those universes
where owning a couch
is forbidden by the hive queen.
In which case,
all glory to the hive queen.
All right, so all that's left is
for us to sign and date the document,
and we will officially
no longer be roommates.
What's the matter?
(SIGHS)
It's harder than I thought.
-Let me help you. L-E-O-N-A--
-That helped!
So, I have an idea for a filk song.
It's kind of a power ballad,
superhero crossover tale
of epic proportions.
-Is it cold in here? 'Cause... Oh, my!
-(BOTH GIGGLE)
Okay, so it's a David and Goliath story.
It's about man against God.
It's called Hammer and Whip:
The Untold Story of Thor
versus Indiana Jones.
Thor versus Indiana Jones.
-You just blew my filking mind.
-(CHUCKLES)
Okay, I don't have it all worked out yet,
but I was thinking something like, um...
(SINGING) Oh, Indy
Oh, Indy
The skies are so windy
Is that a flying man with a killer bod?
Wait! That's no man, it's a Norse god
-Oh, yes, definitely. Okay, wait. Hang on.
-Yeah.
(HUMMING)
(SINGING) Thunder clapped
as Thor raised his mighty hammer
Indy rapped, "That's one bad mamma-jamma"
-That is so good!
-Right?
"Mamma—jamma" just came to me! (CHUCKLES)
Okay, and here's the hook. Uh...
(SINGING) Thor and Doctor Jones
Thor and Doctor Jones
One plays with lightning
The other plays with bones
BOTH: (SINGING) Thor and Doctor Jones
Thor and Doctor Jones
One plays with lightning
The other plays with bones
Oh...
Oh, man, that rocks!
-Hey, remember the Ark of the Covenant?
-Yeah?
That's how much
we're gonna melt people's faces off.
I appreciate your interest
in the apartment.
ljust need to ask you
a few standard questions.
-Sure.
-It says here you're a chemist.
Which element on the periodic table
do you feel is too big for its britches?
Is that supposed to be ajoke?
Looks like argon's not the only one
with an attitude problem.
In general, would you say that
you smell better, worse, or the same
as you do right now?
l was going to ask you
what is the best fruit,
but then I realized
what I wanna ask you is
why is there a Band-Aid on your forearm,
but then I realized
what I really wanna ask you is,
can you just go?
You're healthy,
you have ajob in the sciences.
I've got to say,
if this credit report comes back good,
you're the front-runner.
I'm not gonna be your roommate, Sheldon.
(SCOFFS) But I met with 11 people
and they all walked out.
And that Hollywood phony Chris Pratt
never tweeted me back.
I'm sure you'll ﬁnd somebody else.
I suppose.
What happened to me, Amy?
Years ago, l was
completely disengaged from my feelings.
I'd say it was a happier time,
but I was disengaged from my feelings,
so who can tell?
I don't know how to help you.
You know, feelings are a part of life.
Well, they didn't used to be.
You and Leonard and Penny,
you all poisoned me with emotions.
l was like the Tin Man, perfectly content,
until that evil wizard gave him a heart.
I don't think that was
the point of the movie.
Fine, then I was like Pinocchio
before that jerk Geppetto
went and made him a real boy.
There you go.
-So, what are you thinking for dinner?
-Well, it's Thai food night.
Oh, honey, you don't live
with Sheldon anymore.
You can have anything you want.
(CHUCKLES) You're right.
But what?
Mexican?
Italian? German?
lndian? Greek?
Cuban? Chinese? Pizza?
Barbecue? Korean? Korean barbecue?
-How about Thai food?
-Oh, thank God.
Hey, we're going to dinner.
You wanna come?
Oh, lwish I could.
But I realized I've become
too emotionally vulnerable.
So like an operating system,
l'm restoring my life
to the last stable version,
which was in 2003,
the day before I met Leonard.
-You heard him, no.
-Hang on.
Wait, you actually think it's 2003?
No, just because I'm living my life
like it was 12 years ago,
doesn't mean I'm delusional.
And, since it is 2003,
I don't know who you are,
so please exit the premises
before I call the police
on my stylish, new flip phone.
Are you doing okay?
I guess. Just, you know,
worried about Sheldon.
Well, come on. He's a grown man in his 30s
pretending to be a grown man
in his 20s. He's fine.
I hope so.
What else can you do?
Move back in with him?
No, of course not, ljust feel bad.
Well, so do I.
But don't you want to live with your wife
and set the thermostat
to whatever you want?
And have your body tell you when it's time
to go to the bathroom?
You know, not a schedule slipped
underneath your door every morning.
I did like that he had the weather on it.
Trust me, this is the right thing.
No, I know.
And it's not like we're abandoning him.
Plus, we can FaceTime him
whenever we want.
You know, once iPhones
are invented in his universe. (CHUCKLES)
(MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY)
I can't believe Sheldon
asked you to be his roommate.
I can't believe he ran my credit.
Hey, if you're open
to living with someone great,
I'll give you $1,000 to take Stuart.
You really should've gone on the Internet
and checked how long
that kind of thing lives
before you got one.
I'm sorry, ljust thought you might have
a pasty, weirdo-shaped hole in your life.
Hey, I know Sheldon's quirky,
but he's also brilliant and insightful.
lthink calling him
a weirdo is a little unfair.
Hello, 2003!
Hey, we brought you Thai...
Where is everything?
In my present, it's in the future.
In your present,
it's been crammed in the bedroom
by an enterprising, young man
I met in The Home Depot parking lot.
I know what you're doing.
You're trying to get attention
so we'll feel bad for you,
but it's not happening.
No, what I'm doing is
trying to figure out how to live my life,
now that everyone is leaving me.
Knock it off! We're across the hall.
As the kids are saying today,
"Talk to the hand."
They're not saying that.
They are in 2003.
No, no, they're really not.
(SINGING) Thor and Doctor Jones
Thor and Doctor Jones
One runs from Loki
The other runs from stones
So, what do you think?
-Wow!
-Yeah.
"Runs from stones" means that big boulder,
but ljust couldn't
rhyme anything with "boulder."
Colder, shoulder, soldier, folder--
Right. Yeah, right.
But what do you think?
I think it's very cute.
Cute? It's not cute.
Cute is children dressed as vegetables.
Okay, fine, it's not cute.
(SCOFFS) Just be honest,
you don't like it.
I didn't say that.
ljust like music you can dance to.
You can dance to this!
Uh... Uh...
(SINGING) Thor and Doctor Jones
Thor and Doctor Jones
One plays with lightning
The other plays with bones
I'm telling you, dude,
the song has no groove.
You can't dance to it.
Who cares? I thought the whole point
of Footprints on the Moon was
to write songs that make people think.
You can do both.
Like Michael Jackson's Billie Jean?
While you're dancing you're thinking,
like, "Darn it, whose baby is it?"
Where's this coming from?
A few hours ago, we both loved this song.
I still love it.
| just think there's room for improvement.
You played it for Emily, didn't you?
-Yeah, so what?
-You are such a wimp!
I mean, she didn't like it,
now you don't like it.
No, no. I'm just evolving as a musician.
You're the one who's stuck in the past.
"The past" was lunch!
You know what's really happening here?
Your girlfriend is breaking up our band.
Wait, she has nothing to do with this.
I am my own man.
Oh, please! Your brain belongs
to whoever's willing to sleep with you.
That is so not true!
Really? Remember when you were gonna
get circumcised for Rachel Bernstein?
That had nothing to do with Rachel.
It was an overreaction
to a bad zipper injury.
I don't need this.
-l'm quitting the band!
-Fine, I quit, too!
-Then get out of my house!
-With pleasure!
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Raj, wait!
What took you so long?
Buddy, I know me moving in with Penny
feels like a big change, but it's not.
How can you say that?
Amy's gone, and you two are married now,
so it's only a matter of time
before you're gone, too.
Okay, you don't know what's gonna happen.
No, I do. Eventually,
you'll want more space,
and you'll move into a house.
And then instead of dinner
a couple of times a week,
it'll only be a couple of times a month.
And then it'll only be
on special occasions,
like when Bernadette
divorces Wolowitz, you know?
Or like when Koothrappali's
weird girlfriend admits
where she buried his body, you know?
Or Amy's wedding, where she's
marrying someone better than me.
Okay, look, we don't need
to rush into anything.
All right?
Maybe instead of Leonard
moving in with me, wejust
leave things the way they are.
And sometimes we'll sleep over there,
and sometimes we'll sleep over here.
But mostly here.
Sure.
What about what you said
in the restaurant?
Well, it's not forever.
It's just for a little while.
If you want,
we could think of him like he's our dog.
You can, you know.
I'm happy when you come home,
and I'm scared of fireworks.
By the way, on July fourth,
we're all sleeping here.
-Fine.
-All right, great!
Just give me one minute,
and I'll get started
on a new roommate agreement.
Yeah, nothing from Pratt, we're good.
-(BOTH PLAYING MUSIC)
-(S|NG|NG) Indy's whip snapped
Thor's hammer missed
It was Avenger versus archeologist
Indy held his ground
and straightened his fedora
Thor said, "That's a nice look in 1944"
BOTH: (SINGING) Thor and Doctor Jones
Thor and Doctor Jones
One plays with lightning
The other plays with bones
Thor and Doctor Jones
-Thor and Doctor Jones!
-Thor and Doctor Jones
One plays with lightning
The other plays with bones
Play something we can dance to!
English - SDH